In the year of 2001,
Subbed and timesetted by: Slayeer(Alex)
Credits for Checking go to: Shibatabread
http://gaki-no-tsukai.com
The most humiliating batsu game has been delivered to Matsumoto
So...
Matsumoto Batsu Game:
Lonely 2 days and 1 night Haunted Hotel
In this batsu, Matsumoto has to face his inner fears.
In the Haunted hotel, he will have to face all
The Challenges that have been layed out for him.
Only Matsumoto knows his own destiny.
In the year of 1999,
Matsumoto VS Team Hamada
100m running team match.
Hamada's team lost to Matsumoto, so...
Team Hamada had to face a 24 hour tag batsu.
This was one of the harshest Penalty Batsu's ever held in the history of Gaki no Tsukai.
So, Then the following year...
In 2001 team Hamada tries to take revenge on Matsumoto by doing a 50m swimming race.
First Swimmer: Hosei Yamasaki
Second Swimmer:
Cocorikos' Naoki Tanaka
Third Swimmer:
Cocoricos' Shozo Endo
Fourth Swimmer:
Masatoshi Hamada
Team Hamada wins an easy victory.
And are finally able to take revenge on Matsumoto.
By losing, Matsumoto had to take part in a batsu game.
Team Hamada takes preparations for revenge.
-Shall we?
-OK, let's go.
And now Matsumoto finds out what
the other four have prepared for him.
-Yamasaki?
-Yes!
Matsumoto: What are you shouting for?
-Give him the booklet!
-Ok, here you go but first...
-Please read this.
-Ok.
"Matsumoto Hitoshi, Batsu Game...
.. Haunted House?"
Hai-ryokan Ippatsu futsuka (Instead of Ippaku)
"Matsumoto misreads "Ippaku" and says "Ippatsu" instead.
One night and two days
Yes, that's right.
What is this?
We have written the schedule of the batsu down for you.
It's a tentative schedule
It looks like a fun night with many activities planned for you
Well, it looks good so far
Don't be putting it away
You need to take this with you
Let me explain why it's "Haunted Hotel"
Rumor has it that the
previous worker has committed suicide at this hotel a couple of years ago
You gotta be kidding me
I really can't deal with these ghost spirits
I've heard something similar, too
I heard one of the territorial lord back then
had his fortress nearby this hotel
and also many fallen warriors are known to roam around there
It's called the "Alleyway of the ghost sprits"
Alleyway of the ghost spirits
And why the hell do I have to spend the night there ?
Well, this is your Batsu Game this year
Well...
Why call it the "Game" ??
Let's look up this word
I'm gonna go out on the limb to say that the "Game"
should mean something upbeat and fun
I just might be right about that
But this is clearly nothing more than the "Batsu"
BATSU
Don't worry about that
Besides, look at all these fun activities planned for you
Look at them all
You get to do some Karaoke before the fireworks
Look, you get to even go for a nice walk
Wait a minute
I'm already hating this
Seriously...
I'll be all by myself, right ?
Yes, you'll be alone
This just doesn't look like a fun time
Straight up
Yes, you'll be alone
What am I, Rentaro Mikuni ??
*Rentaro Mikuni is an actor
Well, I don't know if Mr. Mikuni is like this but...
Well, we should get going
Good luck !
Good luck, sir
See you
Wish you luck
And...
Well, well, well
You give such a nice greetings
I've always done this
Really, are you always this polite ?
Of course, I'm always like this
Thank you so much for coming today
Thank you very much
Thank you all
You might have already figured this out
after seeing the four of us,
about what we'll be showing you today
We're showing the Matsumoto's Batsu Game
It is finally here
We did it
Yes, we did
He was such a wimp throughout the game
Honestly
We can't find anyone more wimpy than him
I'm certainly no more wimpy than him
You might be right after seeing him
Without further adieu,
why not bring the guest of honor ?
Here he is
Wimp !
Let me just say a couple of things
First of all,
Why am I the only one so formal ?
You're right
What's with you guys though
Like a street gangs
Seriously
But this is your day
I understand that I'm the star but...
I hear this will be a long one...
It'll be a long night
Of course since it went from 8pm to the next morning at 8am
And he was in it the whole time
The whole time
he would get scared like this at every little things
Like this?
You know what ?
the next morning
my neck was killing me right here
Because I was being jumpy all night
I'm going "Ahh" like this the whole night
You must've been jumpy all night
I couldn't turn my head when I was shooting this other show
You know what else with him ?
He literally got scared at everything we had set up
You were like "Ahhh"
at every single one of our tricks
Just remember this before we show you the tape
We could not fail
"OK, try this"
He'd be like Ahh !!
He fell for everything
In this batsu game Matsumoto has to spend two days and one night at a hotel..
...far from civilization and any nearby living people or roads.
The hotel is located on a hillside, 45 miles from the closest town.
Causing that Matsumoto arrives after the sun has gone down.
Matsumoto will have to enter the hotel shrouded in darkness.
7:30 The car, with Matsumoto, stops in front of the hotel.
Automated cameras have been set up inside and outside the hotel.
and except for a few technicians and staff members, there's nobody else here.
The rest of the staff are working from another building at a distance away.
He approaches the entrance of the hotel where he has to face his darkest fears.
You were so ready to spend the night there
It gives you the chills, doesn't it?
"Kowai" here means "scary", Endo says, "Scary scary"
It sounds kinda.. you know..
Ah, Kowai, Kowai!
That's what makes it funny...
...I really wouldn't spend the night there!
How creepy is this place ?
What kind of creepy drawing is that ?
The hotel consists of an old and a new building.
Matsumoto's room is on the 2nd floor of the old building.
You wanted the AC on, huh ?
Fujiwara
Excuse me...
Thank you for staying at our hotel.
Yeah.
I will be your host this evening.
They call me Fujiwara the Manager
How do you like the room so far?
I hate it...
...and what's with that picture?
Ha, you're being funny right now
That's just creepy
...Yes
I'll be leaving then...
Sure
Uhm...Matsumoto-san..
What do you want?
Well... Uhm...
I was wondering if I could get... a tip or something...
Sorry, I didn't bring my wallet with me.
I see... I'll excuse myself now.
I'm looking forward to being of service
I should change
Hello, we've prepared your dinner,
..please come to the main hall now.
Main hall?
Yes, there are arrows pointing the directions..
.. please follow them.
Yes.
Why can't they serve it in here ?
Why do I have to leave my room?
First event: Dinner
The main hall is located on the 2nd floor of the new building
A scary sound in the hallway
Jack-in-a-box
A secret guest
A fart cushion
A spider web
Countdown to the noise
Of COURSE you'll get scared!
[Hamada]: You're so easy to scare.
So deserted~~
[Matsumoto]:I was definitely deserted
[Endo]: This was a hard one right?
[Matsumoto]: It definitely was a hard one!
Okay, let's eat.
Countdown to the Jack-in-the-box
Miserable Matsumoto can do nothing but laugh.
[Hamada]:That was stupid...
It came out of my MAIN dish:(
...and the food was bad...
...I guess nothing would taste good there.
Countdown to the Secret Guest
Good evening.
This is Tsuno Dajirou, known as one of the top
graphic comic author in Japan.
He's also known to have extensive knowledge about
the paranormal photography
You know, let me tell you something...
15 years ago, I was researching this hotel and the area around it.
In that time..
I made some paranormal photographs...
and this photo is taken at the entrance of this hotel, but..
Is this where you entered?
Yes, this is where I entered.
You can see something in this picture, can you?
Wha..what is this?
This..looks like someone's head, doesn't it?
Can you see it?
This is a fake picture taken by the staff.
What is that?
I think it is someone's face.
After that, I wanted to let the ghost out, but..
Sadly speaking..
the person did not have enough powers to expel it, so it escaped.
ya..
So the ghosts are still here.
So, in fact..and I don't know how to say it uh...
It may be by accident, but...
you guys are recording this TV show in the wrong place...
*This is a lie to make
Matsumoto terrified.
So, do you believe in ghosts?
Hmmm...no...
- You don't want to believe, right?
- Yes, I don't want to.
But...they ARE real.
Have you ever seen this kind of photo?
Look, he doesn't have a head.
- The shadow doesn't have one either, see?
Man's head is missing
Well..
I heard that this hotel was open until a year ago.
ya
But...not at that moment...
Speaking of the reason...
When the hotel opened, one of the guest woman committed suicide by hanging herself...
IN HERE.
Also..
*This is another lie to make
him even more terrified.
And since then, the number of guests have been decreasing.
- Ok
- Ya
In the end, the hotel had to close and go out of business.
I heard you were staying here....
Do you best tonight,
...and please be careful.
[Hamada]: How can he leave like that?
[Endo]: That guy is can be very persuasive.
Completely depressed Matsumoto
[Yamasaki]: So that's how it is.
[Endo]: He didn't even finish his dinner.
Super-Sensitive !
He seems to have lost his appetite.
Countdown to the noise
[Hamada]:It's that fart cushion!
Give me a break already...
*A puzzle with cute little puppies,
Matsumoto seems interested*
[Matsumoto]:I didn't have anything better to do.
Hello, We've prepared a hot bath in the onsen for you...
Please follow the arrows.
9:00pm
Onsen time!
To get to the onsen, Matsumoto must take
the suspended passage way,
Go down the stairs and through the garden.
Japanese doll at stairs
Noise from the window of changing room
Visitor at the bath house
Another Fart Cushion upon returning to the room
Japanese Doll
It's dark in here
Sudden sound in
Cautiously Matsumoto checks
the inside of the locker.
Matsumoto
Countdown to the visitor
Fujiwara knocking on the window.
Shut the hell up !!
How's the water?
Just right, now go away!
I've been married
for a year now!
Eh?
You've been married for a year?
.. What's that got to do with me?
I'm learning how to
cook cold Chinese food
So what?
Your punch line delivery needs more work
Eventually, Matsumoto comes out...
But !
What he didn't know...
While Fujiwara kept Matsumoto busy,
Manager Tashima quietly slipped into the locker
I had no idea he was doing that
Hamada: I'd definitely be scared by this
Countdown to the manager Tashima
Just look at Matsumoto's face!!
I brought you some water.
Tashima returns in the locker
for some reason.
[Hamada]:Why did he go back?!?
[Matsumoto]:You know I had already checked that locker, right ?
What the heck!~
Scary picture from before
GEEZ!~
Fart Cushion
Matsumoto breaks down in self-pity
Meanwhile, Hamada, Endo and Tanaka arrive!
They head straight for the staff HQ with more
nasty pranks in mind!
What now?
Some reporters from the African Channel Television want
to take a quick interview about the batsu game
to take a quick interview
...since this is your first batsu game in 7 years.
There's not much to talk about you know...
In any case, I'll ask them in
African TV Crew
Random dude: OK?
Roll the camera!
This is your first batsu in seven years
..How do you feel about that?
Board: Act funny!
Yeah..uh..
..Yeah, well, I thought it's been 8 years ??
Well, I don't believe I deserve this Batsu Game per se
Random dude gestures
Matsumoto to wrap it up.
What? What do you want me to do?
All right then, next question...ehh..
Do you have plans for another job?
No, not at all
Act funny!! (again)
This job is all I need.
Random dude gestures
Matsumoto to elaborate
If the opportunity presents itself, I'll think about it
I'm happy to hear that.
On a more personal note,
how much money do you have saved ?
Be serious this time!!
Uhm, this is a private matter, so...
Random dude: Wrap it up !
That's it then
Thank you for your time
Alright, we got it !
Huh ?
What the hell ?
Countdown to the painting falling
Why does it have to be so scary?!?
At the staff HQ, Hamada and Tanaka were already cooking up a new plan.
Whenever someone hits the door,
Matsumoto gets all "WoaHh"and stuff!
Countdown to the bang on the wall
[Hamada]:You just stretched the hell out of yourself
What the hell!?
Countdown to another bang
Shut the hell up !!
The three look very pleased
He jumped twice.
But Hamada wants more...
He explains his next strategy without mercy!
Fujiwara should come into his room, hit his head and get out of there.
Countdown to Fujiwara attack
What happened to the ghost and spirits ??
He must be feeling the humiliation now
Yeah, pretty hard.
Matsumoto, why don't you sing a song in the karaoke to get away from everyday's stress?
We've got it ready for you, so please come to the main hall once again.
I don't want to~
10pm:
Karaoke time!
This time's mysterious phenomenon: Tajima Manager wearing the Japanese armor will begin to move when Matsumoto starts singing.
Can he conquer this horror?
Landlady Fujiwara
Tajima Manager
I was waiting for you.
This is the laser karaoke.
I already chose a song for you, so you can start soon.
Please come here.
Song: Ashita Ga Aru Sa
(There's Always Tomorrow)
Ehi!
"I always see her at the same train station
The girl with the sailor uniform and the breads in her hair"
Fujiwara leaves the hall to leave Matsumoto alone.
"Its almost time...It’s almost time..."
For some reason Matsumoto continues singing,
even when left alone.
"but today, I wait again in vain..."
But there is always tomorrow, there is always tomorrow, there is always tomorrow...
Countdown to
the Tashima Armor movement
Please stop! Really!
I brought you a bottle of water.
Meanwhile, Hamada and Tanaka
hide in Matsumoto's room.
Matsumoto returns to his room...
Nice editing !
Fart Cushion
[Matsumoto]:"I'm no idiot, you know, I can learn"
Countdown to Hamada
LOOK! This is his motion!
OOOH! You scared the hell outta me !
WHAT!?
What?
Here, a present for you.
What's Country Dumpling?
UHm..you need some sweets...
you shouldn't reduce your blood sugar level.
How is it?
You were moving your hands and legs!
Hamada is happy to have surprised Matsumoto.
Are you scared of them?
Were you scared of them?
Were you?
What are you?
I'm just asking to you if you were scared of that.
None of your business, go back!
Why!
What's this?
No, don't ask me about that..
No, because it's scary.
Pic?
ya...
Huh
Why is this scary? Is there something on this picture?
I don't know, but I guess so..
eeh, where?
No, not where! You can find it by yourself!
Aah! No more!
You can explain it to me!
I really don't want to see it!
Really?
Yes, no more.
I don't want to see it too.
Hamada is surprised by Matsumoto's fart.
You were just like this, hu!
Are you gonna fly? You fly! Like Hu!
What's with this guy..what's that?
You foolish man!
You can go back, can't you?
Tanaka appearing in...
Nah, I'll still be there.
You were very surprised, huh?
No, not much..no more! It's hot, MOOH!
What's that?
It's a present for you.
It's a nice present, huh.
Isn't it?
Yea, I think so.
Endo appearing in...
You scared us 10 out of 10! What are you!?!
Yea, he did!
He was caught by all that!!
Listen, who wouldn't be scared in this situation ?
10:30PM: Matsumoto's has company now,
but his nerves are still on the edge
I'm sick of it!
We understand.
Tanaka, you appeared very well from the closet, huh?
Yes, because I practiced it SO MUCH!
It's like you..
hey, Hamada is foolish.
He got scared by my fart!
He's not much better than me
I just let out a fart, and he went "Ahhh !"
It's like he's never heard a fart before
Well...really..
What?
Uhm, you know...
I was lonely.
Yea, I can see it.
Matsumoto is actually happy his 3 friends are there.
It's scary here...
Well really...
The telephone is really old..
Yea, scary...
I chose to go to a video rental store,
and what I chose was...uuh..
Well..you know..
The video of "Shining".
The story is about someone staying in a hotel, after season, isn't it? And,
the person in the end gets all crazy. He takes an axe and goes rampaging around the hotel!
So, I thought:"Why did I watch such movie so timely..!"
The guys get pretty surprised by a
sudden sound of a crying woman.
Why do they try to scare us, besides Matsumoto..?
How irritating...
They should stop it, really.
Sometimes, someone kicks at the wall!
And simply, I'm angry at it!
Matsumoto is angry at the prank Hamada thought of
and when I get back here, it seems someone messed up my Tobacco like trash!
These pranks have nothing to do with ghost spirits
They're just annoying
If I were alone, I would be scared to death!
Just, uhm..
what?
What? What?
This can't make anyone laughing...
Look.
Who brought these in ?
You know, there isn't a head on this guy.
His head is gone.
You're kidding..
Moreover...
His shadow is headless too...
That's just too scary..!
Hey, you don't see this, why?
I'm still surprised!
Hello?
(Matsumoto's older brother: Takahiro)
hey!
This is brother!
Oh, hello! I'm Hamada!
OH! Hi.
Your brother is trying his best now.
OH!
Shall I put him on?
Yes please.
Ok!
hey.
Hey you
ya
Your brother
What/Who are you!!?
You should have nothing to do with me now!
I heard from Hama-chan you're in trouble now.
Oh, where?
Eh? No, I'm at home in Amagasaki
Why are you calling me from such place?
No, but you are coming back for the bon festival, aren't you?
No, I won't come back for the festival...
Mom and dad are waiting for you.
.na...but...
That shouldn't concern you...should it?
HEY!
Because it's a special occasion, I'll cheer you up, so
ya..
Are you hearing me?
What?
I made a song for you, so, can you listen to it?
Wait please, I'll sing, wait a bit...
♪As i thought, whatever you say you're dutiful, Matsumoto~Hi~To~Shi~♪
It's hard to listen..
♪Don't forget to thank Hama-chan, your senior, your junior, staff, back uppers
Matsumoto~Hi~To~Shi~♪
♪ You know, I'm worrying about your body health, cut down the number of tabacco you smoke
♪Brother ilfis(I am)
♪I am Hitoshi Matsumoto's brother
He uses his little brother's name too much in the lyrics.
Everyone can be amazed.
Eh?
What's up?
The four are getting nervous.
What about it?
You can hear stuff from time to time...
It is the staff's fault, or maybe something else...
uhu, uhu
Moooooh! I said it! Its very scary!
You...
You're overreacting !
This is just like the pattern. They always scare us and we're like:"DooGH"!
I'm sorry Matsumoto, I destroyed your Jigsaw puzzle..
Hey, come on man!
without it, I have nothing to do around here!
Man!
Come on man!
I mushed it...
I beg you not to rob my enjoyment..
I'm sorry, please make it again! Sorry!
no way, we shouldn't do such thing..
The guys, forced watching the horror video from Matsumoto.
Breaking the vase in...
So, time to go back!
NOOOHOOW!
The guys are getting scared and going back.
You must watch the video! It's cursed!
Good luck!
Matsumoto is alone and lonely
The 3 members return to the staff room.
Look at his face!!
Tajima wearing armor
What the hell was that !?!
Matsumoto is left by himself again, but the night isn't over yet!
We just watched 7:30pm to 10:00pm
of his Batsu Game so far
As I said before,
It was really quiet, even the phone made me jump!
We were dead-on with every tricks, weren't we ?
Well, I don't know about...
You didn't let us down for sure
I was always on guard, but then my brother started singing on the phone and
to be interviewed by some African TV
I thought: "What the hell!?"
What was I supposed to do?
And than he destroyed my jissaw puzzle!
I was almost finished with it, too !
But I lost my motivation after he killed it
Seriously what a night...
You figured out the Fart Cushion quickly
What ?
Like the third time
Of couse, I'm not an idiot
I didn't know what to do with it at the third time
I mean, when I came back to the room,
I see a little hill on the chair
So you knew it then
You guys were just bullying me at that point
I kept thinking,
"Should I go ahead and sit on it or not ?"
You couldn't decide whether or not to be a good sport about it
But Hamada got scared of Matsumoto's fart.
And don't you compare MY reaction to Hamada's when he saw the armor.
You were scared of it too!
Yeah, but I'm still handsome
I just went like this, see ?
When Tajima came out of the locker you were all:"AAAAH!".
No no no, I was just like:"AH".
But Hamada was all like:"AAAAAAAHHH!"
But your reaction is a bit too flamboyant
Agreed
Or when you hugged yourself like this to hide your breast
11pm: It's been 4 hours and Matsumoto is starting to look tired.
Hello? We've prepared some fireworks outside the hotel, please come down and enjoy!
I don't wanna~
Fireworks time!
This time traps prepared for Matsumoto:
Tajima Armor stands at the door
Bear taxdermy moves
Fallen warrior Heipo's pie attack
Lotion on the door knob
Fart Cushion upon return
Tajima Armor suit in...
Who's there..?
What was that?
He falls for all our tricks
Countdown to Bear Taxdermy
Scary! Scary! Scary!
I'm sorry, sorry, sorry
Matsumoto is enjoying the fireworks all by himself.
It's a curse!
The cursed Samurai!!
Heipo keeps repeating "Tatari ja~(It's a curse!) and "Ochibusha~"(the cursed samurai). Matsumoto repeats "Nani?"(what?).
Get out of here, stupid!
Heipo loses his peripheral vision
Heipo gets scared at the staff who came to bring him back
It's a curse !
What? Go away!
I'm scared!
I don't care
Heipo slips and panics
What?! Just go away already!
I can't see..
I don't care
Come with me.
I'd love to go home, too
I'm scared
I'm scared!
What an idiot
I'll bring you some water..in your room.
Bring me some cigarettes
Right away, sir
Don't bang on the door this time.
Countdown to the Lotion on door knob
Fart Cushion
This is bad for my heart!
Here's your water.
Hello, we've prepared a sexy night show for you,
so please come to the mail hall.
Matsumoto checks the schedule
11PM: Sexy night show time!
An old man wandering around and the old man and the 'armor' hiding in Matsumoto's room.
But the biggest trap is the show itself!
Roaming old-man
[Hamada]:That was scary, right?
[Endo]Yeah, it was.
This sucks.
An over-aged woman as sexy dancer
[Hamada]:That's not even dancing!
[Hamada]:Lame!
10min later
[Matsumoto]:That was REALLY long!
[Hamada]:What's with occasional kiss ?
[Matsumoto]:When the song was over, I thought she would leave me alone. But no...
Shes just kept going...
20min later
While Matsumoto is enjoying the show, Hamada, Endo and Tanaka enter his room again.
Matsumoto has had more than enough.
Roaming old-man
Tashima Armor
Fart Cushion
Matsumoto completely ignores the cushion
You should've seen your face
What was up with your face just now ?
We brought you some snacks
We thought you'd be hungry
since you didn't get to eat much tonight
Your face was like this just now
And that's something to be proud of...
Exactly. What happen d before?
Well...
..there was a monster.
A monster?
It finally got you
You must have been scared, right?
Really scared.
Moooaah, so I went to the sexy show!
And that old hag with the perm just kept dancing around!
She just wouldn't stop!!
For more than 20 minutes!
She smelled bad and she kissed me so many times too!
That's just cruel!
Isn't it?
I just wanna go home.
Countdown to the painting falling
Tanaka, your reaction is way too much
By the way,
..Give me a break with that fart cushion.
Every time I get back..
It was funny the first two or three times but..
Every time I come back to the room
I see a nice mound
I'm not an idiot
Stop sighing
You're way too jumpy
Well, I'm the closest to the wall
I almost choked on this
That scared the hell outta me
What do we do now ?
What can we do ?
Since you're here, why don't you sleep over ?
No, I don't think so
Seriously, there's nothing to do
Actually, there's plenty to do
That's bugging me over there
I wanna go pee so bad
Bathroom?
...I'm scared..
Matsumoto is scared like a little child.
Wait until I get back...OK ?
Don't do anything funny when I get back!
Tashima Armor is setup
What's the matter?
What the heck was that?!
Matsumoto laughs at his own helplessness
What?
Endo, go see for yourself.
Matsumoto is 38, right? What's up with that reaction?
That's SCARY!
That's not fair, Hamada, go check it out!
I don't want to..
Just go already!
You know, he's been everywhere tonight
So you've seen him many times tonight ?
Oh! He's gone.
Are you sure?
Yes
What's with him? He gives me the creeps..
Matsumoto fell into Endo's trap.
That's just mean!
You've been letting out some screams tonight
Cut it out already.
He's gone now, it's alright.
The toilet is in front of Matsumoto's room.
But what he didn't know..
The toilet is haunted!
Hold on!!
That is too cruel!!!That is too cruel!!!
THAT IS TOO CRUEL!!!!~~~
Matsumoto is seriously scared.
Oh, what's wrong with him ?
I just screwed up my bladder
What was that supposed to mean?
I didn't know how I can stop the peeing
So, you were in midst of peeing ?
Yes, I was
I'm not going back in there..
How about you give it another try?
Just let me pee, ok?
People have to pee...
seriously!
People have to pee...so...
Matsumoto is talking to himself out of fear
Come on..ok? This is..
people have to pee...
LEAVE ME ALONE~~~!!
I'm creeped out!
I'll pee in here, ok?
You can't do that! Go back to the bathroom!
What is in there anyways?
There's one scary looking woman in there
Just stop it, ok? I need to go. People need to pee right?
I don't want to mess up this location either
Wait..come with me.
Well no, I don't need to go
Me neither
Hamada.
Matsumoto pleads Hamada for help.
Who said I have to pee alone ?
What's up with that "creepy girl"?
Hamada lends Matsumoto a hand.
Where?
In here!
What?
Come on, come on, come on.
Look.
What the hell are you doing?
Did you see it?
Don't you get used to it?
Yeah.
It's been 3 times already.
Did you finish?
I didn't..
I'm so hating this...
But you got used to it, right?
She will leave you alone this time...
Matsumoto avoids looking in the window.
Hamada: What's he doing..?
That's enough. ENOUGH!
That's it. I've had enough, really, I've had enough!
I can't pee like that.
Go ahead and just pee
No way
No way I can pee in that environment
It's not good to hold it in though
What are you doing? You can't do that!
Matsumoto decides to pee in a cup.
At this point, I don't care if this footage will be aired
Staff: Tell Matsumoto he can go now.
You can go now.
He already started...
Do we really have to see this...?
He's just standing there.
Crap!! the cup is too small !
Is this guy for real?
You look exhaused, Matsumoto-san
He is peeing very long..
He has too much pee.
You're still peeing...
How do you manage that? Go throw that away in the toilet!
If I do so, I have to go to the bathroom again...
The ghost is gone now.
Yes, it's ok now.
You must throw it in toilet now!
What?
Why did you come back with those cups?!
Hey! Why did you?
There is no place to put these...
You should have put it in a corner in the bathroom.
Yes..
huh?
yes.
Not just "yes"!
But it's ok.
No, it was too scary, no way!
No way....
So time to go back. -Yes.
Good luck.
Eh..why?
Oh...well..
They are surprised by Tanaka kicking the door.
What are you doing man?!
Countdown to Tashima Armor
What does that guy think he is!
So, good luck Matsumoto.
We're leaving.
Matsumoto is left alone again.
Excuse me
Hamada: Did he have to do that ?
Landlady Fujiwara
Don't kick the door.
Sorry.
Matsumoto..
Yeah?
Its the hotel usage, in fact, we ask all the guests...
to join the purification to purge of ghosts.
So we want Mr. Matsumoto to also join the purification,
at the shrine outside...
So please join us.
That can't be true...
So, there are ghosts, huh?
0:30am: Time to visit the shrine.
This time mysterious phenomena:
- Konya Ga Yamada waiting for Matsumoto.
- Tajima wearing armor and attacking.
Night camera
This way.
What is that ?
There is something there, huh?
There's something.
No, no, ma.
Konya Ga Yamada waiting
Who?
Ohhhh...he is Konya Ga Yamada...
He has nothing to do with this
Please, this way.
Eh? A hill, this way?
yes
From here on, Matsumoto, you have to go alone.
Was that your joke?!
No, no ,no!
It's a joke, I'm with you..
-yes.
What is this? Woah~
Its a torii...!
Woah, we shouldn't go through here...huh?
Ohh...it's grim...
Over there Matsumoto.
Eh?
Paying homage at a shrine?
We shouldn't be here...
No...whatever, we shouldn't...
Here, hold this.
Countdown to Tashima Armor
Hey, it's dangerous to do such thing in this place!!!
Don't do it!! We can slip away dude!
Fujiwara can't help it to laugh at scared Matsumoto.
Is he gone?
-Ok?
-Yes.
Why do you gotta come out while I'm praying ??
Why now show yourself before I started my prayer ?
That was so backwards !
You took me too such a high place...don't be silly.
It's really scary here, man.
Yamada is still there...
Konya Ga Yamada
Musn't he have said that when we went to the shrine?
He must have missed the timing to say it.
He must have waited there to say that.
Matsumoto's night isn't over yet...
Grandma night show..
Ya, ya, ya
I was like, "give me a break"
uhm...that must have taken over 20 minutes, I think.
Her arms and legs were short, and..
It's ok
And that room was dark, so you may couldn't see, but
really, my shirt was full of lipstick marks
She gave me over 40 kisses
She couldn't take away my soul though
We appeared from the doors with loud bangs.
Here's the reason why we visited you then: We wanted you to go to the bathroom
so we brought you a bottle of water
and have you drink tons of it to get you into the bathroom
ya, you did?
And I found out why the awful sexy show went on for so long
was because you needed more time to set up for another pranks ?
Yes, we were running late
So I had to take a hit for that
Why should I have to be kissed by some old bitch because of your inadequate preparation ?
It's like the Murphy's Law
Yes, like that
But who could forget your bathroom incident ?
You were like this ?
It was so scary even if I knew she'd show
I tried to avoid the window by kneeling like this
And...
my junk was touching the urinal
Imagine flickering the cigarette ash like this
You're saying your junk is like cigarette ?
Yeah, I'm sure I made contact with bacterias then
I didn't care though
You were just plain terrified
When you see this footage,
it doesn't look all that dark outside
especially with the lantern lit
But I gotta tell you how much I couldn't see around
Maybe this much around was visible
and I couldn't see anything beyond a meter or so
And how useless is Heipo san ?
Now you mention it..!
He really pissed me off
Every time I asked him something he kept repeating himself:
Aaah, Kowai!
So one of the assistants came to get him and
he was like, "Kowaii !!!"
He got scared at an assistant director, too
He was real pain in the butt.
When Heipo ran into the staff,
Even when the staff signals "OK, Heipo, well done !"
Heipo thought they were trying to scare him like this
He got mixed up between these two gestures
He mixed up these two?
Yes, like this.
He annoyed you guys too, right ?
He needs to "get it together"
Midnight, 1:00 a.m.
Matsumoto receives another invitation
Hello!
Yes?
We have prepared a Beer meeting with one of our guests.
Could u please come to the 3th floor?
And follow the signs.
Yes.
I don't want too~~
1:30 Beer and putkong (kongjongryu) time
To get to the beer, Matsumoto has to climb the stairs and walk his way op to the 3th flloor.
Good evening.
Hello.
Yamasaki: He was really scared.
I was asked to keep you company tonight
Ah ok.
Let's have some drinks
EH.
Tsumami Edamame is known for his keen connection with the after-life
and also known to have witnessed countless paranormal activities
I wouldn't advise you to continue this game
Well, I would love to quit right now but...
Is it the batsu game?
I don't like this location
Well...
As a celebrity, I travel a lot for my work
and spend a night or two
at different hotels
hmm
I stayed at this particular hotel about two hot summers ago,
*Matsumoto is beginning to get frightened*
Including 2 in this room.
And as I turned off the light to go to sleep,
I was on third floor by the way,
I heard these running footsteps
from one floor down
It sounded like it ran down the hallway
It was definitely a running sound...
Matsumoto gets even more afraid.
And I wonder why it was running in the middle of the night
Then, at that point,
The same running sound
came from the floor above me
Just like that
Matsumoto refuses to make an eye contact out of fear
I was freaked out and when I looked up
I saw an old man hovering by the window with an child on his back
I got scared and quickly went to go close that window
And I told myself to move to the next room
and as I was trying to leave that room,
I saw the same old man squeezing himself out between two Tatami floor mats
That's enough !!
Go home !
Why are you guys still here ?
We didn't mean to bother you..
And what's with your stomache growling, idiot
I thought Matsumoto would hear that
I heard it
So, you heard it
I heard it, so I decided to talk a little louder
It was a loud growl
All kidding aside,
This type of hotel is known to be haunted
Of course, some are myths
but some are not
So I wouldn't horse around here thinking this is all a big joke
Just watch yourselves
Hamada: Look at all of us jump
Yes, Endo here?
Apparantly, the Beer and Snack time is over
And we should head back
to our room
Huh ?
I'm going back alone ??
Why two separate phone calls ?
Walking down that hallway gives me the creeps
OH! I forgot to tell you one last thing
uhm..
You won't need to look if you're too creeped out but
sometimes you'd feel this weight on your shoulder
This really does happen
It just happens out of nowhere
my wife experienced this as well
And you get freaked out and turn your head like this
only to find this hand on your shoulder
I'm definitely not gonna look
Thank you for your time!
Be careful out there
Japanese armor suit
The above floor looks even scarier
Right, we need to avoid going up there
Why did they put that here...
BANG!!
The team runs away like little girls.
What's your problem ?
No, listen, listen
My head hurts from screaming so much
I don't think this moves
Matsumoto just ignores the Fart Cushion.
2:00AM
Matsumoto is left alone in his room.
Don't do that to me
Yes?
The ghost in the toilet is gone now, you are rest assured...
You need to stop with that
Do you want me to get sick, idiot ?!
Please enjoy yourself.
"The ghost in the toilet is gone now" ???
So you were behind all this
Matsumoto is still super-sensitive to the phone rings
Yes?
Eh..Matsumoto-sama,
We have prepared a late night bath for you,
So please come to the bathing area to enjoy yourself.
There's more ??
What the..?
Onsen (Bathing) time
*Woman in white at the entrance
*Konya Ga Yamada in changing room
*Fujiwara hidden in the bath
Just about the time for the woman in white
Wow, that scared me!
MOH, why do I have to come here~
Countdown to Konya Ga Yamada
Konya Ga Yamada
Why go back in there ?
Matsumoto gets scared over a group of insects
It was just really scary
-Naaaa~
Fujiwara hiding in the bath.
Excuse me, but I'm here to scrub you down
No thanks
Matsumoto gets scrubbed by Fujiwara.
So how am I doing so far ?
Hello ?
Yeah, what do you want ?
Well, the Lumine Theater has been open for three months now
And it's been going well but...
I thought maybe you can show up one of these days
Why don't you ask Hamada ?
Of course, I have already asked Hamada-san before
If Hamada's not doing it, then I'm not doing it either
So you're saying that
if Hamada-san agree to show up at the theater,
you will at least consider it ?
Yeah
Oh, thank you very much
OK, that's enough
Why can't you evenly scrub my back
and not concentrate on one area of my back ?
Enjoy the rest of the night
Don't kick the door anymore, OK ?
I don't see why he has to kick the door
A scary singing girl...
Your head is up while the sound is going off!
I was trying to figure out what was going on
But nothing happened !!
Yes?
Hello hello!
It is almost time to sleep so
we have prepared your futon(bed) in another room.
The room is on...the...3th...floor,
please follow the arrows to the room.
Eh?
Why can't you just bring me the futon ??
Sorry for the inconvenience
On the 3th floor?
In the room with the arrows.
Yes.
What kind of service is this ?
Futton Finding Time!
The room with Matsumoto's bed is located on the 3th floor.
Matsumoto has to climb the stairs and walk the hall towards the room.
This time paranormal phenomenon:
- A scary old man
- A scary long haired girl
- And 2 old grandma's
Why don't I just sleep in this room ?
Scary little girl hiding
Lotion on door knob
Kind Tashima Armor hands a wet-nap to Matsumoto
to clean his lotioned hand
3:15AM
A complete darkness engulfs the haunted hotel
Yamasaki shows up at the HQ
Staff needs to trick Matsumoto into stepping outside
so that Yamasaki can hide in his room
I have your favorite cup-noodles ready for you in the cupboard
I hope you'll enjoy it
Thank you
Note:
We're out of hot water
Come get it at the neighboring house
How do you run out of hot water ?
Just boil the damn water
3:30AM
Late night meal
Matsumoto needs to walk about 2km to reach the nearest
neighbor to obtain a hot water for the cup noodle
Man, it's still dark out here
Yes, it is
This will be a long walk
A complete darkness
What was that ?
Matsumoto get´s scared by a rock
I thought it was a person
Where to ?
Here comes Konya Ga Yamada
Konya Ga Yamada
You scared me, Fujiwara
Your scream is scary
Arrives at neighbor's residence
Excuse us
yes?
uhm..
I'd like you to give me some hot water.
Hot water?
yes.
Could you wait a minute?
I'd like you to give me some hot water.
Yamasaki stands by when Matsumoto goes out.
I can better hide myself in this closet.
Oh...There must be something here...
Hey, Who are you?
huh
WOAH!
Roaming old man
Yamasaki in...
I have had enough
My nerve, around here, will cause me pain tomorrow.
Because I made this weird motion.
Matsumoto is feeling relief that Yamasaki is visiting him.
This is...Scary, yes.
A little while ago, I went to a small residence that was hidden in such a dark place...
WAAAH
Matsumoto cant help laughing at his miserableness.
But you know, this will be over in a little while.
This feels forever to me
But...
But why doesn't it get light faster?
Yes, it's still dark around here.
Well, regrettably, there is something in here Matsumoto.
Absolutely.
How many times do you think the wall was hit?
There's no way you can get used to that.
yes, there's no way.
I will never get used to that
You can't help bouncing.
So, good luck Matsumoto.
Good job!
Hello?
hello
yes?
Oh, excuse me. Can I speak with Matsumoto please?
hello
I'll put him on.
The staff tells Matsumoto to set the revercedokiri.
Reverse dokkiri=Is some kind of reverse joke.
What's up?
uh, Yamasaki?
yes?
uh
Go to the toilet.
Toilet?
Why? Why do I have to go to the toilet?
So suddenly..It's strange!
After you talked to the telephone, you tell me this! It's strange!!
Go pee, huh!
pee...
Whatever, just go pee. Because I also went to the bathroom...
Its natural, because you're here all the time.
But I don't have to pee!
I said you must go pee, really.
Why?
You wanna go pee, don't you?
No, not so much.
Just go pee already..
Seriously
Ok, be I'll get going after I pee
Good luck..
-You've got to pee!
Yes, I'll go.
-Ok.
Now go pee, properly.
-Ok
Don't shout so loudly!
Go pee.
Who's there?
Who's there...?
Matsumoto cant stop laughing because of his successful joke.
Yamasaki gets lost and begins to run wildly.
Heey! I completed.
Finished.
Hey, come!!
Hello, it's almost time to go to bed.
So please turn off the light.
Have a good night.
Really..?
4:00AM
This is...I don't wanna be here...
I don't want the dark...
It really smells like that old guy.
I told you not to kick the door!
The sun starts to rise after 2 hours of sleep.
The time to get up is coming.
Good morning.
Sorry, It's morning now.
We have prepared breakfast for you so please come to the main hall.
AM 6:00: Breakfast time.
Bu       bu      Cushion (1 guess what that means )
Matsumoto got used to dealing with fart cushions.
I'm coming in.
The Central Africa TV would like to get another interview, so please
Please comment on Hamada, Endo and Tanaka.
Do an impression
of Antonio Inoki
uuhh.. you guys are shit, don't be silly...
Thank you.
Finally, please say comments to the Central Africa's TV crews.
Finish it with:
Your fooling plan.
eh
Because you are from Africa...
eh..you look easygoing.
thank you.
Sudden water comes out of the mic.!!
Thank you very much.
What!? MOOOH!
Thank you. So much.
At last, Matsumoto reaches the end of his hard schedule.
Moh, I'm very tired, Moh
I had no idea what would happen.
Question: What are you feeling right now?
It was sooo scary, but..
I have 2 things...that need some explanation.
They are...uh
Heipo's meaning and..
My brother's stupid song.
I still don't know what their meanings are
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on the fulfillment of the Batsu Game.
Good job
Thank you.
*Pretending the Batsu Game is over...
Yamanba (Japanese old woman), appearing from the back of the car.
Matsumoto Bastu Game
The Best of...
How many times can you scream ?
So many "Whaa, whaa"
Huh ?
You don't get to hear an over-the-hill screaming out like that these days
It looked tough, didn't it ?
Yes, it did
Well, as you could imagine,
since I had no prior knowledge about anything,
everything was scary
I mean you have no idea what's about to happen
Yamasaki, you got lost there ?
I had no idea how to get back
And I started to get scared, too
I was like, "Hey I'm done"
"I am done !"
But nobody helped me
And I was hearing him going
"Hey, I'm done over here !"
I was getting confused
This was a tough one
and I'm glad it's finally over
I was really dreading to do this
I'm proposing us never to do this kind of event again
You mean the "scary" ones ?
Right, no more
It's bad for my image
This will ruin my first meeting at the arranged marriage
Right, no woman wants to see that of me
Like this ?
It sure would be an awkward first date
I have to say
we sat here for a long time just to watch this
It's almost like a feature-length film
especially the ending where you thought everything was over
and it wasn't
This production team is really smart in a most malicious way
Take this for instance,
you would think once you shut off the light,
there would be some scary stuff, right ?
It's a perfect set-up, right ?
But no, nothing happened
And that suspense nearly killed me
I was like, "Why, why nothing ?"
Why didn't they do anything then ?
But they decided to throw in that scary old woman in a morning
When she got to me like this
she really got me right here
She hurt me
She scratched my side right here
Oh one last thing,
we told you the hotel is haunted,
but it isn't
They're still in business
I'm sensing a little contradition here
Why didn't you tell me that before ?
We merely rented the whole place out just for the show
All the talk about the ghost spirits are made-up
They're a legitimate hotel
So if I stayed over there again and went to pee
I wouldn't see that woman now
No, you won't
No Fart Cushions ?
No way
What if there are hotels like that ?
It could be a big hit
Really ?
It could be a great business model
I'm not sure about that
I'm sure it's only cool at first
I mean nobody wants to go get their own futons
and also have to deal with the Fart Cushion every time you're back in your room
"How many times is enough ?"