Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
Special Thanks to Alex
slayeer@home.nl
One Way to Dehumanize
is to
Deprive One's Emotions
The Notorious Gaki No Tsukai Series!!
"No Laughing Hotel Men"
Household Name Celebrities
Assassinate the Cast Members  !!
An Array of Explosions!
And Unlikely Co-Stars
Traps Impossible to Predict!
Dragging Them Straight into a Laughing Hell !!
That's pretty amazing, isn't it !?
Top Celebrities Speak Out !!
One Big Celebrity Becomes the Victim...
Trembling Fear
Screams Echoing into the Dawn !?
All Five Men Challenged During the Longest Footage Yet !
A 6 Hour Special !!
DownTown Presents
Gaki No Tsukai
New Year's Eve Special
"No Laughing Hotel Men"
24 Hours Batsu !
Hello
Thank you
Downtown
Hiroshi Matsumoto      Masatoshi Hamada
So we've done yet another "No Laughing" series
Hosei Yamasaki
The footage is six hours long
Cocorico
Shozo Endo         Naoki Tanaka
Long enough to welcome the New Year
This was a really tough one, wasn't it ??
I'd say this one was the toughest one yet
It was long, too
Yes, it was
I mean, it was supposed to be for 24 hours
But I think the shooting went way past that
But seriously folks
Aren't we pals ?
Aren't we pals ???
Yes, we're in this together
We're a team
Anyway, what's your take on this ??
Let me just say again,
it was a very long day
It was long and...
Where are you looking at ?
And WHAT are you looking at ??
Let's just start already !
Right, we're lagging
Could you introduce the video ??
What a crappy reaction !!
What a CRAPPY reaction !!
What?
Are they playing the "No Laughing" game now ??
Work Day
Unfortunately, rain greets the cast members at the local ballpark
Here come the five members
It's raining!
They seem to be in good spirits
Don't we always dread this first day ??
We should be pretty accustomed to this by now
What's this ?
It says "Wait Here"
Can we just have Shoji show up and be done with this ?
The we could all go home in 30 minutes
This is how Yamasaki was on our way here
"Don't let me get hurt"
I was casting a spell for all of us
A Spell ??
Please don't be using words like that once this starts
What's with "casting a spell" anyways ?!
Someone is coming
Wow
I've seen that van before
Gaki-Nori Van Arrives
I'll never forget you guys !
My journey is over here but,
Enough with cheap drama already !
Why is he trying to make us laugh right now ?
I...
I love you guys !
There's no need for this right now
Good luck~
Hiro~
Those girls had to get up early just for this ?
Crappy gig for sure
What a long intro !
Downtown Former Manager
Hiroshi Fujiwara
Look at his face !
I've seen him in "Monsters, Inc."
You need to knock it off with your face
Your face is really foul when you're squinting from the rain
Here he comes
Where do you wanna be ??
How irritating !
Make up your mind !
Will you guys face this way, please ?
What the hell ?
What are you trying to do ?
I not only lost my relationship, but I also lost my ride
That's one tough rule !
What's he talking about ?
Are you guys ready again this year ?
What was that all about just now ?
Love...
I had to break it off
I'm sorry
No need to apologize
Yamasaki ?
Why do you think I'm in this outfit ?
Let me see...
You're in a woman's suit
Are you supposed to be a teacher ?
Anyhow, why aren't you being funny ?
Be funny ?
Ok then
Are you playing baseball or something ?
Don't flatter yourself !
With that being said let me announce that
This year's batsu game is at a Hotel
You will be working as Hotel Men for the next 24 hours
Hotel Men ?
Hotel
Toot~
Yes, hotel
How would you take care of that ?
Good luck to you all
Five newly hired Hotel Men Facing
A Challenging 24 hours Ahead !!
And I'll be taking care of you...
What's with your speech ?
Well...I..
I will be taking care of you all day
I'm the hot Hotel Woman in charge
Call me Fujiwara !
As Hotel Men, what's with your outfits !
Go into that dressing room over there to get changed
This again ?
Go ahead and get changed
Before work starts
Changing into an Appropriate Uniform
As a man in his mid 40's,
I sure don't like getting changed outside
You all ready ?
Yes.
Then come out one by one
Hamada
You look like you'll be a good worker
A Shrewd Middle Aged Hotel Man
Thank you
Good luck
Matsumoto
Yes
You look good, too
A New Dad Hotel Man
Good luck to you
Endo
You're looking sharp
Handsome (Once Divorced) Hotel Man
Thank you very much
I'm counting on you
Tanaka
You're thin, but you seem righteous enough
Righteous and Tall Hotel Man
Yamasaki
Cropped Hotel Man
What is that ?
You're being disrespectful to our customers !
What's going on here ?
Well, this is all I got
I know they're short
Don't think you're funny !
Line up over here so that I can explain some rules
Work as Hotel Men for 24 hours
1st Rule
You are not to laugh at any time
during working hours
2nd Rule
Laughing results in delivery of a severe punishment
3rd Rule
And that is all
Are we good ?
I wouldn't say we're good
Why don't we wait over here for the bus
which will take us to our hotel
And the game starts once you get on the bus!
Here we go with the bus again
I know
It was a long bus ride last year
It sure was
Let's move on to the bus stop
Wow, here it comes!
That was quick
It's here
Here, check it out
This is where you'll be working
Gasu Kurobikari Princess Hotel
Or, Suga Puri for short
Wait, should it be "Gasu Puri" ??
Suga Puri is the only 9-Star hotel in a world!
Wow, 9-Star
That's unheard of
You're gonna have a long day
if you're laughing at that !
Why don't we get inside so we can get to our hotel ?
At last, here we go again~!
The game starts once you step on !
It really is a drag getting on that bus
Let's go~
24 Hour No Laughing Hotel Men
Sit in order please
Man, I've got a clear view of the door !
I don't like how we can see people getting on the bus
Patrons Get On
Why can't we just start at the hotel ??
Alright !
Bus heads for the Hotel
What kind of traps are set up for them ?!
Let's get there quickly
Tension builds up as the bus arrives at the first stop
Quickly
It'd be nice to just get there now
Arrives at Bus Stop
Elderly Man Gets On
Stands in Front of Tanaka
I wouldn't like this
Why wouldn't he sit?
There's plenty of empty seats !
This sucks
False Teeth Fall Out
That's not cool
That was a quick first strike
Why don't you have a seat ?
I know, there are seats available
Plenty of seats
Gimps Deliver Serious Butt Whippings
4th Rule
Here comes the first one !
I had forgotten how this felt
Sir, why don't you have a seat over there ?
There are plenty of seats for you
I wish he would sit
I was definitely expecting the first laugh trap to come quickly
so that old man caught me off guard
Elderly Man Refuses to Sit
Arrives at Bus Stop
Masahiro Chono
Listen, you assholes
Why are you letting an elderly person stand?
Angry at Their Lack of Etiquette
Aren't you ashamed ??
Get your ass up
Yeah, you !
Can't you see he's standing right in front of you
Well, let me just explain
that there's plenty of seats available
Which seats are available ?
Why didn't you just offer your seat to him ?!
Don´t you have any manners ?
See, there's plenty of seats around
I was just wondering why he's not...
willing to sit like back there ??
Why didn't you offer your seat ?
Well, I thought there were seats available
You're just repeating yourself
And I was actually wondering why he wouldn't sit
But why didn't you offer your seat regardless ?
Brace yourself !
Punishment for the Lack of Etiquette
Will you wait a minute, please ?
Seriously, give me a sec
What's your problem ?
This is too sudden...
What'd you mean: "too soon" ?
I can't do this right now
Why are you....
Hey, don't blame me !
Let's try something new this year
Alright, man up
Wait !
Here we go !
The day just started
and I can't do this now
What ?
I can't do this
I'm not mentally prepared for this
Not one bit
This is way too early for this
I'm mentally not prepared
Why don't you prepare then ?!
Give me a sec
You'll be alright !
Give me some time
Impossible
It's all because you didn't offer your seat !
Hamada Abandons Tanaka
That was terrible, Hamada-san
Time's up
Get ready
I'm not waiting any longer !
Put your hands down !
Be careful
Brace yourself Brace yourself
Man up, here we go
Alright
Bump !
Bitch Slap for the One With No Etiquette
Excuse me, sir
This is your stop
You hit your head right there
Look, he's still pissed off
Why doesn't he just leave ?
Thank God
What a close call
At one point,
I wondered what kind of problems he would have with me
Are you OK ?
Well, I'm just flabbergasted
It's difficult to digest what just happened
Nothing you can do about it now
Yes
Just let it go
Although your left cheek is super red
Well, you more or less asked for it
Agreed
You didn't offer up your seat to him
Man, my heart sinks every time the door opens
I just saw his head
Arrives at Bus Stop
Hayashiya Pee
Gekidan Hitori
So, he's the next guest
I'm a bit worried
Are we OK ?
Everything will be OK ?
God, I'm worried
Man, she's late
Arrives at Bus Stop
Hayashiya Mahko:    Mao Daichi
Ha ha
Are you serious ?
You took some photos
They're good
Am I in ?
Oh, you got it
Please, excuse us
That's rude
You can't just take anybody's picture
Stop it
Forgive her, please
I'm sorry
Mahko !
You stop it !
Don't be taking pictures without asking them first
I'm in deep trouble here
I'm so dead
Yamasaki, get it together
Daichi's Laughter is Contagious
I have to make it out of this
Your laugh makes me laugh, Yamasaki
We're very sorry about this
Yama-chan, get it together
We can do this
We can do it
I'm very sorry
Mahko !
Yes ?
You're too relaxed !
Don't you realize we have an audition today ?
If we don't make this audition today
we might as well give up in this business
Don't worry about it
I just came up with the ultimate comedic move
An ultimate comedic move ?
And innovative, too !!
An Innovative Comedic Move
You got my attention now
Before we get to our audition,
could you guys maybe check it out ?
They're OK with it, Mahko !
Hello, thank you for coming !
I'm Pee
And I'm Pahko !
We're Hayashiya
Pee-Mahko !!
Thanks for coming today !
No way !
Anyway, as we are actually on our way
to go fishing in this BUS
What do you think we can catch around here ?
A black BUS (bass)
No way ! No way !
Innovative Comedic Move
Ping Pong Paddle
That's enough !
I don't want her here anymore
We got it now
Her voice is piercing
Very piercing
Mahko !
Let's do the "Face Performance"
Mahko Shows off the "Face Performance"
This is one of her specialties
Here it is
How're you doing, morons ?!
This makes no sense !
I'm sure you'll do great at the audition !
Can you go now ?
These pictures look good
You got some good ones
Have you had enough ?
I think they're requesting an encore
Let's see who's behind this veil
Sheee !!
OK, will you guys stop ?
What an idiot
Haven't you had enough ?
No more "Face Performance" !
Seriously, we've had enough
I don't want it anymore
Let's just be done with it
Seriously no more
Shall we go for another encore then ?
No, no more
Here we go
You've got nothing left!
Please, no more
What a great turn out
It was a great show!
Thank you very much
Can I do one more funny thing ?
This is our exit
Do you still want to go on ?
Please excuse us
What a greedy duo !
They exhausted their material
All of it
Look, they're still at it
She's got nothing left
Ah, she was doing Mr. Inoki then !
It was definitely unexpected
What a surprise guest !
It's been 30 minutes
All 5 members are already in an abstracted state of mind
But there will be more attackers coming
from all directions
We're making so many stops
Arrives at Bus Stop
Can we just get to the hotel ?
Attention, everyone !
We've received an information that there's a bomb on this bus !
Please give us your full cooperation
as we search this bus !
SWAT in Search of Bomb Suspect
Excuse me
Clear !
Check over there
Hey !
Captain Deluxe Enters
So far, all clear, sir !
SWAT Captain
Matsuko Deluxe
By the way
Did you frisk these guys ?
Not yet, sir
One of these guys is obviously the suspect !
Am I right ?
Yes, sir
I'll do this on my own then !
Jeez
Ah !
He's freaky
His grip is something else
Did that hurt ?
Are you hiding a bomb in these lips ?
You love your baby !
I heard he gets up at 8am for his baby
I'm saving you for later
Why is he saving me for later ?
Why does he talk like that to you ?
Are we done yet ?
Hah ♥ Thanks for waiting
Get up
So I can frisk you
Get up so I can inspect you !
A Thorough Physical Inspection
Nothing suspicious up here
Move !
Hold it !!
Suspect Flees
Captain !
Captain, there goes the suspect !
Damn, what an idiot !
Here Comes the Bazooka
Suspect Blasted by Bazooka
Sorry about the interruption
I shouldn't have questioned you
I'm sorry
Don't worry about it
It's quite alright
See you later♥
What the hell...?
Why make it so dramatic !?
Man, that is quite a stare-down
It was...
Amazing
At least Endo was spared from a butt-slapping
You're right
But he was victimized in a different way
Agreed
Being molested by Deluxe should count as 10 butt slaps
That was incredible though
Bus makes a U-turn and heads for the Hotel
Why make a U-turn ?
Look, he's still there
Man, he is still there
I think he wants to get back on
Freaky
Man, he's pissed
How come ?
It's probably my fault
Why so much anger ?
What made him angry all of a sudden ?
The others had to restrain him
Can't Deluxe get in with this door open ?
He's coming He's coming
There, look !
Damn, he's coming for us !
Driver, let's get going !
Let's go
Quickly
Close that door
We're good to go
How scary
I guess he wasn't done with us just yet
What did I tell you,
we've been on this bus for about an hour now
Wow
And we're not there yet ?
We are SO not there yet
I don't see anything that's remotely like a hotel around here
Again ?
Arrives at Bus Stop
Teacher Bids the Students Farewell
Don't go
We'll miss you so much
Don't go !
We'll miss you !
Good Bye~ !
I'm sorry !
Sensei (teacher, released in '72)
What ?!
Original Singer
Masako Mori
It was drizzling outside
when my first love ended
I hid under the umbrella,
standing alone at the pier and cried
My young heart never stopped
thinking about you
Sensei (my teacher)
Sensei
And you're my teacher
Thank you very much
She must've been hiding somewhere on the bus
Of course, we're OUT
That was totally uncalled for
Just amazing
Shouldn't she ride longer than just one stop
God, my back
after that dramatic farewell ??
Hahaha
You find this so amusing, don't you ?!
A perfect laugh
Please keep your eyes open !
I have seen you get away
with a lot of laughs, too
But you just openly laughed
But only I get the slap ?
And I get it !?
When he laughs solo, he doesn't get one
This is wrong !
It's unfairly judged
I've gotten slapped solo before !
Let's not start an argument
Not just yet
It's too early for that
How come the only time he gets slapped
is when I AM involved?
Are we some kind of package deal ?
Hahaha
I'm sure someone just laughed, too
Arrival at the hotel
in a few minutes !!
We're in the vicinity of "Suga Puri"
What a long ride that was
That tall building is the main building
Pretty nice, isn't it ?
That is a nice building
"This Year's No Laughing Headquarters"
A 9-Start Hotel, providing the best laughts
during the 24 hour challenge !!
We've finally arrived
Yes, at last
So this is the 9 star hotel
Arrival at the Hotel
We're here
Follow me, please
My butt hurts already
This is awesome
This is a huge place
Very grand
Suga Puri Main Building
Taxi !
Sukarno Taxi
How may I help you ?
What is this ?
I can't comprehend this situation
Sukarno Taxi !!
Where are you headed ?
To Tokyo
I'm in hurry
Yes, sir
Their service must be superior
Sukarno Taxi providing the best service
Can she drive ?
Grrrrrrrrr !!
Grrrrrr !
Grrrrrr !!
Sukarno is a Rookie Driver
Be careful
Please be careful
You don't have to do this
It's not in drive
Don't be putting it in reverse
Please, excuse me
Grrrrr !!
Beep
Beep Beep
There's another car behind you
Beep
Can we just go now ?
Let's go
Beep
The taxi behind you is...
Behind you...
Beep
BEEP
How annoying
What is your problem ?!
What kind of selfish driver are you ?
I'm trying to tell you to get outta here
Why ?
Why are you doing this ?
You're the one being obnoxious
Seriously !
Can we just go now ?
Being a taxi driver isn't easy these days
Shall we ?
Let us move on quickly
Here is the mascot of this hotel
A legendary lion-faced
Statue of Suga-Lion !
Princess Hotel Mascot
The Legendary                      Suga-Lion
I might have seen this face before
The tale of Suga-Lion precedes back to 16th century Rome
It is said that the monstrous lion used to terrorize the city of Rome
And young Suga decided to take the matter into his own hands
Keep in mind that he was just another man running his hotel business
Anyhow, young Suga fought the um... battle
battled against the... well...
Get it right for God's sake
You do this to us every year
No more stuttering, please
Wait a minute
Give us a break !
This hurts way worse outside
It really does hurt
So the young Suga took on the battle
Excuse me,
So he fought the battle and
And he managed to take over...um
the body of this beast...
And he took it over to become...
To become Suga-Lion !!
What the hell ?!
Why me ?!
Judges need to be more consistent
Since then, people come from all over the country
to stay at his hotel and to witness the Suga-Lion
Anyhow...
what became of....young Suga's battle
is now the model for this hotel
What?
This hotel is designed after Suga's battle ?
The hotel don't look anything like the lion !?
What happened to the young Suga ?
Where's young Suga in this ?
Seriously, get the story straight !
Let's get going
I'm now taking you to the annex
The annex ?
Can't we just go in here ?
We're not going in here ?
Another bus ride ?
We need to get to the annex
The hotel property fits 20 Tokyo Domes
Grand Resort Hotel!!
The Hotel Men's training begins at the annex
Another Bus Ride
To the Annex
So he said young Suga's legend
is depicted in that building
Anything's possible
I suppose
Just look at that again !
That's a mirror image of
young Suga in battle...
Stop it
Will you not do that, please ?
This isn't good
I see zero resemblance !
Of course, we'd laugh at that
Fujiwara obviously got some facts mixed up
I can't look at the building the same way again
That building sure is proud to be there
I can't help but to laugh now
I can't look at it again
It's Fujiwara's fault
Training Headquarters
Arrival at the Annex
Newly Hired Hotel Men
What Kind of Laughing Reception Awaits Them ?
Here's the Suga Puri Annex
Why don't I show you inside ?
This is just as nice, isn't it ?
It's beautiful here
Why didn't you just bring us here in a first place ?
Let's line up here in order
Face this way ?
Yes, face toward the front desk
I was going to introduce you to the receptionist
But I don't know where she went
Excuse us ?
The Receptionist Arrives
I'm your Suga Puri receptionist
Yes, my job is to welcome all of our guests
I will always welcome you with my smile
Because I am the face of this Hotel
I am Bibari Maeda
I've been in this business for 45 years
To get to work for 7:00am
I have to get up at 5:30am to get ready
We thought it was over then
But after all these years
My salary is still only $1,200 per month
She's one exceptional receptionist
Incredible
I'm pleased to meet you all !
Here at Gaasu Kurobikari Princess Hotel
I'm Suga Hotel's Top Star,
Bibari Maeda !
Hotel's Top Star
Bibari         Maeda
May I have all of your names ?
I'm Hamada
I'm Matsumoto
I'm Yamasaki
I'm Endo
I'm Tanaka
By the way Endore !
Who's Endore ?
Endore !
Where are you from, Endore ?
I'm from Osaka
I see Endore is from Osaka
Let me ask you another question
Her weird vibe is hard not to laugh at
By the way, Endore
Here's my last question
Do you
love me ?
Yes
So you love me, Endore
Endore
Cut me some slack !
We need to make it through her weird act
With that being said
Good bye !
Yeah !
Yeah ! Ha !
She is indeed a professional
A true professional
That was a tough one
Just amazing
I would never in a million years
think of you as "Endore"
Shall we move on ?
This is our hotel manager's office
He's notoriously intimidating
Don't be rude at all costs
Excuse us
Line up right here
Sir
Here are your newly hired trainees !
Hotel Manager
Riki Takeuchi
Damn it
So, you guys are the newly hired guns
Good to meet you
Yamasaki is Ignored
I knew that was coming, too
Oh, here's the fat one
I'm the one in charge of this hotel
My name is Takeuchi
Yuko Takeuchi !
What the hell ?
I wasn't expecting such an old-school joke
I've had enough already
I wasn't prepared for that
Let me say it again
I'm in charge of this hotel, call me Takeuchi
Takeuchi...
Yuko !
That's enough !
For the last time !
I'm in charge of this hotel
Takeuchi
Yuko Takeuchi !
Where did the laughter go ?!
How can there be none ?!
Why the third person voice ?
Manager's Inner Voice...
I'll say it again !
I'm in charge of this hotel
Takeuchi !
Yuko Takeuchi !!
What a sad reaction !
Where's all the laughter ?!
Nice face !
These days
People have been calling me
the Emperor of the Hotel Business
Just like I used to be the Emperor of V-Cinema
What ?
I thought this was a good one !
My back hurts
I ask you
to do your best
Manager Tekeuchi,
Thank you for your time
I'm Yamasaki
There's some commotion outside
Can´t you do anything right ?
We're very sorry about this
Hotel Guest
Kouich Hamada
Being sorry isn't gonna make this alright !
Get me your supervisor !
We're very sorry
Sir, how may I help you ?
He claims his watch has disappeared from his room
And he saw an employee exit his room just beforehand
I saw him !
You stole my watch!
Sir, please
Fake booger
Or, was it you ?
What's so funny ?!
Or, was it you ?!
No sir, it was not me
Your kid is too young to wear a watch !
Yes, sir
What's so funny, huh ?
Don't take what's not yours !
Mr. Hamako!
Junior
Gitan Ohtsuru
Did you find it, sir ?
Hell no
What's with you losers ?!
You look suspicious
Fake booger
Let's go
Yes, sir
Shall we ?
That was really long
Going to the 2nd floor ?
Yes, the 2nd floor
This sure is a nice hotel
This way to the annex
Come this way
Here's your break room
It's about time
The seats are assigned
I have to hit the bathroom
I really need to go, too
I need to use the restroom
Go for it
I can't hold it anymore
I have to take a wiz, too
It's been an hour and a half
They finally get some down time
But they use it to explore the room
I wanna go take a dump
This year all I ask...
is that we all get judged fairly on our laughter
Seriously
Agreed
Let's be fair
Yes, let's play fair
I just checked the fridge over there
and there are some gag props in there
Oh yeah ?
Why don't you open it ?
This room seems to be more cluttered than previous years
Check the freezer first
What ?
Have you seen that before ?
You can't get that in stores, right ?
Hamada-san, will you look ?
Why don't we ALL look at it together ?
I know but...
Sugari Sugari
You set me up
That looked painful
No, I'm good
Come look
There's no reason I have to do this
The three of us looked at it
You'll eventually look at it, so why not now ?
Why don't you just tell me what it is ?
Then, I'll come look at it
I don't know how to explain this to you
I can't describe it to you
What's with your swift movement ?
Sugari Sugari
Have you seen that ?
Your turn
Endo likes it
Yes, I thought it was good
I like it, too
Sugari Sugari
You can't buy that in a store
You're right
Not sold in stores
You cannot buy that anywhere
So what is it exactly ?
My guess is..
It parodies the original "Gari Gari" popcicles
That's Hamada-san
Sugari-Sugari
No, it's not
I thought this was Hamada-san
It's Mr. Suga, right ?
Yes, thus Sugari-Sugari
Why did you think this was Hamada-san ?
It's none other than the Gaa Su
You know what ?
I knew right away that it was Gaa Su
That's why I laughed
But he didn't get it
So he didn't laugh
It says "Sugari Sugari"
Well, I just looked at the picture
and thought
"Hey, it's Hamada-san"
That's not good
I feel bad for Hamada-san
You're dissing Hamada-san and Suga-san
I have to go take a dump
What ?
You're on your own
What do you mean, "what ?"
That's pretty fast but
I guess you didn't take care of it earlier
What do you mean, "That's pretty fast" ??
Since when is taking a dump some kind of a race ?
Hosei-san, don't say things like that
We're allowed to take care of our business whenever we want
So don't comment on it
And let's put our game faces on
What did that package say again ?
You didn't even read what it said
and realized it was Suga-chan?
Sugari Sugari
It says they're accepting members if you want to join
Club Sugari Sugari: Members wanted !!
Did you have to point that out ?
Damn you, Sugari Sugari
You know what else ?
Nobody's opened their drawers yet, right ?
You're right
I'm positive they're rigged
Stop looking around, Endo
Ok, I'll stop
Before their work even begins,
They're Busy Searching for Traps
Terrifying Drawer Traps Await Them!!
That's the end of the first chapter
So, Tanaka received the morning wake-up slap
Yes I did
From Mr. Chono
To be honest, I didn't think it would be Tanaka
Yamasaki-san usually takes the hit for us
I was thinking he'd come to me, too
But that wasn't the case
You got away
You know who else ?
Hitori and Mao Daichi-san
She never fell out of character
She never let up
And I was already exhausted on the bus
What about Sugari Sugari...
Excuse us
Here's some Sugari Sugari
License
Kazuhiro Fujiwara
Takafumi Inomoto
Song by Poka Suka Jyan
Please try one
Can you blame me for thinking it was Hamada-san ?
Hamada and Suga-san look very similar
You think so ?
If you compared five facial parts of you two,
it'd be more obvious to you
Pretty cool, isn't it ?
You can win some prizes, too
Every single Sugari Sugari is a winner
Really ?
But you have to eat all of it to find out if you've won
Tanaka, you'd better
But these guys just said they're all winners
We don't know that for sure
Finish that, will you !?
I really have to finish this ?
Of course
Go ahead and stop the camera
So they can finish it
Then why am I trying to finish this popsicle?
It's been 2 and a half hours
Time for infamous trickery
I really wanna see what's inside
I do, too, but I'm scared
I don't want what happened to Matsumoto-san last year
Last year's Newspaper Series
Remember that explosion ??
I could have fallen funny and died
You're not kiddin'
You could've banged your head
Endo, why don't you open yours ?
Shall I go ?
Endo is the Lead-off Hitter
We have to open these sooner or later
It's just a matter of when
I don't see why we HAVE TO open them
But you know we will eventually
I don't know at what time, but we would
It might be wise to get this over with
I'm going first then
How many do we have ?
We've got more than few
Mine's weird
I can see there's blue paper sticking out
What the hell is that ?
Blue paper ?
It's sticking out
Just hanging out
I'm ready
This can scare the hell outta you
which is not really what this show's about
Here I go
There's nothing in here
Why was that thing sticking out then?
Masking tape the staff
forgot to remove
What the hell is that ?
It was stuck there for no reason
What is it ?
Tell me exactly what it is ?!
Well, I thought it was something, too
What is it ?
but it's nothing
It says "B" very faintly
What do they mean by "B" ?
So this has nothing to do with us
Here I go
I guess this time...
Nothing
What's this ?
Wow, wait a minute !
This is kinda freaky
This isn't cool
Freaky !
Why ?
Finds a Pistol !!
There's something written on it
"Endo, do not shoot at any cost"
That's terrifying
I'm going to put this down for now
Here's my last drawer
I'm OK
Nothing
So all I got is this pistol?
It says "Endo, do not shoot at any cost"
Damn...
Hold on !
Could you slow down ?
Give us a signal
Say something so we know
We need a signal
What do you mean ?
Who knows what's in here ?
Why does he have to open it like that ?
Nothing
Mine was in the right-side drawer
Open sesami
I'm scared
What's this ?
It will be in the next one
See ?!
I told you we don't need to do this
Blue Button Found !!
Here goes nothing
Nothing here
So they're all in the second drawer !
Here we go again
Damn it
I don't like that new item over there
That pistol is dangerous and scary
Does it say "Not to shoot at Endo" ??
No, it just says not to shoot it
It's full of evil
It's part of a trap for sure
It's so full of evil !!
Why'd you do that ?
Here's a question for Matsumoto-san
Question
Name all the prefectures of Kyushu
What ?
What do you mean ?
Well...
In Kyushu area ?
There's Fukuoka
Um...
You know that one ?
Yeah...
Incorrect
How ?
Answer
Fukuoka  Kumamoto  Ohita  Saga
Nagasaki  Miyazaki  Kagoshima
*Okinawa is included on occasion
I didn't laugh
What's going on ?
You got a trivia question when you pressed the button
Blue Button --> Trivia Question
You didn't answer it right, so you got the butt-slap
Is that how it is ?
Nobody laughed
What's in your drawer ?
What ?
So you got the red one
Red Button Found !!
Just to make sure
So one button for each of us
Butterfly from the Drawer !!
Amazing
It's a nice touch
It's a real butterfly, too
This is a rare butterfly !
Wait, there's more underneath you
We should have let them out earlier
What kind of butterfly is this, Tanaka ?
I'm not quite sure about this one
It's taking a nice break
What a calm butterfly
My back is killin'
Who would've thought...
Yama-chan, why don't you open yours ?
This is scary
You know there's gotta be something in there
What ?
DVD's
Of course, there's a DVD player over there
You're right
We have two
Mysterious DVD x 2
What else is in there ?
Nothing
That drawer should be it
Here it is
Green Button  Found !!
What did I tell you ?
Green
Next one is green
Nothing
Damn..
Too many uncertainties
Your turn, Tanaka
Let's go, Tanaka
This is a bit scary
How come Endo got no button ?
There's something inside
It's a panel
Panel ?
Suspicious Panel !
Think this through before you pull it out
Pull it out like this
toward you
Well, we don't know which side is which
Thumbtacks through
Yamasaki's nose
What's with the juvenile gag ?
Thumbtacks through
Yamasaki's nose
This is so childish
Very childish
And why you two ?
But seriously,
Why me and Hamada-san ?
Anything else ?
Here I go
There it is
Purple Button Found !!
I knew it
One for each of us
Well, I got the pistol
A purple button
I'm curious about the DVD's
I've got a bad feeling about those
Why did you get two ?
Shall we watch these ?
No, no way
I don't want them
But why two ?
I was wondering about that myself
Before you move on,
why don't you push that button first ?
So that
I can change my course of action
So play the DVDs later
Yeah
I'm going for it
Here I go !
Who do you think should get a butt slap ?
Street Survey Derby
Excuse me, but I'm from Nihon TV
Yes ?
I'm from Nihon TV
Do you have some time ?
OK
Are you on your way home ?
Yes, I'm on my way home
To your loving wife ?
Well, I'm here on business,
so I don't actually get to see my wife tonight
I'm actually doing some work for "Gaki No Tsukai"
I love that show !!
Can you participate in this survey then ?
Who do you think should get his butt slapped ?
I'd say Hama-chan ! Yes !!
He kicks (other guests) too much !
So, I'm OUT ?
You're kiddin' ??
So whomever they choose gets slapped
Green Button --> Street Survey
That's all it takes ?
I thought you got caught laughing
When ?
Just now
I thought he laughed at that survey
No, I don't think so
He simply got chosen
You get a slap for each vote
Who the hell is gonna push that button then ?
What's with this survey ?
Here I go again
You serious ?
Street Survey Derby
Who do you think should get a butt slap ?
I'm praying that it won't be me
Who do you think should
get butt slapped ?
Yamasaki-san
Because that's his character
Hamada-san
Becasue he's always abusing the others
Hosei Yamasaki
Tanaka-san
Why ?
Because he's not cool
Hama-chan
Hitoshi Matsumoto
His shaved head is blinding
Hosei Yamasaki
Any reason why ?
No...
Matsumoto-san
My gut feeling tells me so
Hamada-san
Because he's gross
I'd say Yamasaki-san
Street Survey Derby
Person Most Deserving of Butt Slap
Champion:       Hosei Yamasaki
So we're free to laugh at this then ?
Tanaka was laughing, too
So we can laugh all we want ?
OK, so you DO get slapped for laughing
Man, there's no time to relax
Rules are becoming very confusing
That green button is not my favorite
Shall we watch the DVD ?
Let's watch it
I'll pick the one in my left hand
Do you know which one was which ?
Yes, I stacked it so I'd remember
Anything's safer than this pistol
Well, we'll eventually have to shoot this
There's a definite "dangerous" element to it
Look, there's that butterfly above the TV
Can we take care of that somehow ?
It's right in the middle
Angel with Broken Wings
Music and
Lyrics by
Ken Takahashi
Rain is falling down sideways
straight into the driver's seat
No need to bother with the wipers
in this hurricane
I can't hear you say "I love you"
So I put my ears close to your mouth
Rain washes our feelings away on this freeway
If I were a superhero
I would fight off your sadness
But I'm still feeling despair
because I can't agree with your whispering words
Uh...
Yamasaki OUT Angel
And Tanaka, too
Tanaka 2-Slaps Angel
Why me !?
This isn't fair
What does this mean ?
You even get two slaps
What ?
This is nonsense
This is just plain wrong
Stop it !
What was that all about ?
What the hell was that ?
What is "Yamasaki OUT Angel ?"
Well, I get "Yamasaki OUT Angel"
But what's "Tanaka 2-Slaps Angel ??"
Let's put this away
Yeah, put it away
Get that angel outta here
And put in the second angel
Should we ?
That took them some preparation
That was the real singer
How could you have avoided the slap anyway ?
Lyrics: Keiji Mizutani
Music: Yoshinori Monta
Dancing All Night
I know I'll laugh at this
When it's sweet,
my heart sings
I'm feeling nervous
at what's to happen tonight
I can see the lit candle in your eyes
And I'll carelessly dance in your eyes
MEMBERS ALL OUT
Tanaka's OUT for good
Slap Tanaka twice
Why me ?
Out of control
This must be for us laughing then
I'm taking it out
Good idea
It's definitely put together well
This isn't nice
Slap Tanaka twice ~
What do we do with Endo's pistol ?
Well, it says not to shoot it
"Endo, do not shoot at any cost"
Endo, it might be better to get it over with now
Agreed
What are you gonna do with it ?
I know enough not to aim this at anyone
Of course not
How should I....??
Should I aim down ?
If it were me, I wouldn't do it
Yeah
Give us a signal
Let us know before you shoot
I'm ready !
Pistol --> Shoot it and get shot
This is just way outta hand
This is way out of control
Out of control
It smells like fire cracker powder
That stinks
But it's only Siccarol
What is Siccarol ?
What's Siccarol ?
Siccarol ??
You know what Siccarol is...
We use it on babies
You're laughing right now
I wasn't laughing just then
You did it to yourself
It's called Siccarol ?
Isn't it baby powder ?
Or, Talcum powder ?
It's Talcum powder
I told you it's Siccarol...
It's noon
And there's more than just drawer traps...
There's nothing to do in this hotel
We haven't learned anything yet
Would you care for some drinks ?
Maybe some tea ?
We have some ?
Yes
There's juice, too
Juice ?
Some Sports drinks, too
We had coffee and stuff last year
Any hot drinks ?
Oh, I see them
But they're all teas
What's this then ?
Hot tea sounds good to me
Would you like a "Suga Tea ?"
"Suga Tea"
I'll pass
Me, too
I'll try some "Suga Tea"
What's in "Suga Tea ?"
Wow, what's this ?
It's milky white
Suga Tea
I can't drink this
Is it spoiled ?
It's spoiled
This could split my intestine
What kind of tea can split your intestine ?
There, he laughed !
Why point fingers ?
Let them make their own decisions !
You don't need to point fingers at me
He didn't even try to hide his laugh
A complete laugh
It gets my back
Man, what's this ?
We don't know
Ramen ?!
This has to be soup for ramen
What is this ?
Suga Tea ---> Pork Flavored Soup
So they made this for the show
Yeah, they did
I see it now
Did you say, "Yeah, they did" to Hamada ?
You have no respect for him, do you ?
That is strict
Hot !!
Hot !
Wait a minute !!
That wasn't part of the deal
That was freakin' Hot !!
What a disaster
That wasn't fair
Man, the floor's soaked
Let's clean it up
Wow, you dumped the whole thing
Listen guys
I know you're becoming more accustomed to things
but here's a hotel public relations video.
Why don't we watch it ?
Introduction to Hotel Video
Let's pay attention
Plenty of sunshine warms the untouched natural setting
We offer the best amenities and activities to fit your holiday needs
here at Gaa Su Kurobikari Princess Hotel
We're located one hour from the city center
Our grand entrance welcomes you with open arms
Our lobby has high ceilings, creating a wide open space
and it will make you feel comfortable and relaxed
Our orderly and luxurious front desk
is constructed mainly with marble stones
Our experienced staff will make you feel at home
She shows up way too much
and help you make your stay a pleasant one
Chiaki, are we good to go ?
Yes
Let's go
We offer a variety of rooms including our suites
to fit anybody's vacationing needs
Not only can you enjoy the view from your room,
but also take in all the fresh air by renting our bicycles
What the hell's this old man doing here ?
We also offer many outside activities including
full 18 holes of golf
and tennis courts just to name a few
It is indeed perfect for those planning vacations in groups
We encourage you to invites all of your friends and family to
to play singles, or doubles at these tennis courts
And let's not forget that this is also a perfect spot to facilitate your company picnics
Nice shot, Chiaki
Yeah
Nice
For those looking to pamper yourself,
Why not visit our esthetic's ?
Welcome
We use only the best massaging oil
to bring out the natural beauty of your skin.
For our facial massage,
our experienced staff will sure to relax and cleanse your mind and soul
How does that feel ?
Natsumi Ogawa
Hamada's wife
How does that feel ?
Your face sure will thank you later
What the hell is this all about ?
This is an amazing footage in so many ways
What the hell is she doing ??
Our esthetician can also massage your tired legs
How am I doing ?
This is incredible
This is really incredible
Huh ?
We offer extensive exercise options outdoors
Including our indoor Olympic size swimming pool
where you can refresh your body
Of course, you're free to meet and make friends
Wow, she's all over the place !
between your swimming trainings by our poolside lawn chairs
What's she doing here ?
What kind of footage is this ?
Is she supposed to be an instructor ?
As the night falls,
how about a drink or two at our classy bar ?
Cheers
Our trained bartender can offer you
best specialty cocktails that you both can enjoy
I love you, Chiaki
Do you like me ?
That was too much
Of course, the bar is setup for you to socialize
and great opportunities to make friends from all over the world
Man, she really is all over the place
Japanese Style Lodging
If your group favors a more traditional arrangement
why not enjoy your stay at our Japanese style lodge ?
Our beautiful Geisha will ensure entertainment to you and your guests
I've got a bad feeling about this
Could they possibly be...?
Chiaki
I'm pretty sure who this is then
Natsumi
Incredible
What is this ?
I wouldn't call this an adequate entertainment
What a crappy quality of performance this is
Couldn't they done a little better than this ?
Even the wig isn't fitted right
Seriously
This is not acceptable
I have seen enough of this
Onii, I'm wishing you luck once again this year
Puu !
Well, thank you very much
Piko-chan, I'm working hard for you, too
Who's Piko-chan ?
Piko-chan ??
What the heck is Piko-chan ?
Where do you get "Piko" from your name, Hamada-san ?
Let me explain
Remember, when I got married, she used to call me "Pii-chan" ??
Well, it somehow evolved into "Piko-chan"
We're looking forward to serve you.
No, she doesn't call me that anymore
She just modified that old nickname of mine
This isn't good
My back hurts more than anything
We should be thankful
to get slapped once for that whole segment
Indeed
We should've gotten at least five or six slaps
You know what though ?
At one point, I was afraid one of my family members
would show up at this.
Anybody could have shown up at that footage
She looked the part of Yakuza's wife
Piko-chan...
So, this is what you'd gone through in past years
Yes, like this
It's amazing that you didn't know about this
What do you mean ?
You know, about this ?
Right, nothing
So it was carried out behind your back
How terrifying !
Who knows what else is planned
Chiaki's new husband must have
New Onii
hurt his elbow during the shooting
Maybe when he was riding that bicycle ?
It's been 4 hours since the start
Time for what they've been waiting for
Alright
Can I get a new pair of gloves ?
I don't think you'll need them
I'll need them when we have to step outside
I brought you a lunch
Alright
Seriously ?
Today's menu is noodles with dipping soup
Really ?
Thank you very much
Enjoy it
Wait ?
Dipping soups are knocked over
Sorry, but the soups have been knocked over here
It was an accident
Oh, well
This side is OK
5 servings of noodles are salvaged
At least the noodles are intact
Note: Notice how the topping the right box are still in tact.
And there's one bowl of soup left
Here are some toppings for the noodles as well
You guys can share this as well
Is this enough for all of us ?
Well, you've got plenty of noodles
Who knocked them over ?
I knocked them over
I'm sorry
I know you're sorry but
Well, go ahead and share these amongst yourselves
Why share ?
I see that there's one for each of us
We got a bowl of noodles for each of us
Yes, we got the noodles but
There's not enough soup and toppings for all of us
Dipping Soup
x1
Bowl of Noodles
x5
Chashu(Roast
Pork) x2
Boiled Eggs
x2
Food Groups
With only one bowl of dipping soup left,
The members have to take turns eating noodles
Nobody touched any of the topping on the first round
and just enjoy the noodles
I'm not liking this "middle-aged" men festival
After a first round...
First round is all you can take ?
Why not just dump all this toppings in this soup ?
Ahh
How should we take care of this ?
Well, anyone who wants it...
All of you are full, right ?
No way, I can still eat
I'm not quite done either
Why don't we make another round ?
It's just not sanitary
C'mon, it's OK
Then, use the butt-end of the chopsticks
I really don't like this
We don't need to do that
Let's just eat like men !
But look at us middle-aged men
We're too gross to eat like this
But you're the oldest man here
What's wrong with just making another round ?
Who wants boiled eggs ?
Boiled Egg x2
I do
I'd like one, too
I do, too
I don't care too much for boiled eggs
Hamada-san ?
Well...
Let's Jyanken (rock, paper, scissors) for it ?
Jyanken = Rock, Paper, Scissors
Do you really want it ?
Boiled eggs
are one of my favorites
Let's Jyanken then
You're in, too ??
What ?
Isn't it just us three ?
I don't see why I'm not in on this
Who wants boiled eggs ?
I do
Let's Jyanken then
You're in ?
What're you gonna do, if you beat us ?
Us three are going for boiled eggs
You just wanna participate in Jyanken ?
I'll think about what to do if I beat all of you
There's no guarantee that I beat you
You're right
I don't get this
Why am I OUT ?
Start the usual way ?
First comes the Rock Jyanken Hoi !
I beat you !
So me and Hamada-san get the eggs
What ?
Wasn't it for one egg ?
Shouldn't we Jyanken again for the last one ?
I hear you
Huh ?
Why do you make it so difficult ?
That was just the first round
We need to do a separate round for each egg.
Absolutely
We need to play it twice
Why ?
So Yamasaki and Hamada need to Jyanken to decide
Winner gets to eat ONE
That wasn't the plan
Careful dipping your chopsticks in the soup
Hey, those are MY freakin' gloves !
Wait a second
I made an honest mistake
Wait, they're actually MY gloves
You're right, they're Endo's
They're mine
So, Yama-chan, you're out of this
Well...
I would like to participate again
You want two eggs ?
It's not really two
It was one split into two, so I only had half.
But you already had one
Even a real snake wouldn't try again
I'd say he was laughing just now
Alright, I'm in !!
I got it !
So you WOULD eat two
Two of them
What the hell ?
What was that ?
What the hell's wrong with you ?
That is disgusting
What's so freakin' funny ?!
That is gross
How dare you spit it out
What's with your hysterical laugh anyhow ?
How freakin' good are you at Jyanken?
Yeah, I know
No, you guys just suck at it
I was surprised that I beat you
Ok, should we move onto the Chashu (roast pork) ??
I want it
Chashu (roast pork) x2
What ?
How many are there ?
Let me count them
Use the butt-end of the sticks, OK ?
Two...
We have two slices
We got two
Can we add "Up, Down, Left, Right" also ?
See www.shibatabread.com for the explanation of "Up, Down, Left, Right"
We can't do that with more than two people
I think we can
Let's try it
All of us ?
So whoever wins confronts the losers
I see
OK
So the game doesn't stop until there's a winner ?
And the winner quickly picks one of the losers
I'm not getting it
First we do Jyanken
and if I win, I just pick one of you
to point at
So you pick anybody?
Why aren't you in it ?
Well, I just lost
So you just lost ?
You lost to all of us ?!
You all just beat me
I don't think you lost
Really ?
I don't believe you can lose to all of us that easily
since there's five of us
You're right
So ONE guy has to beat the rest ?
That would take some endurance
How about this then ?
Just have whoever wins point at the losers
regardless of the number of winners
For instance,
If Tanaka and I win
then he and I would point at you
So multiple people can win
If three of us win, then three of us will point at the loser ?
How would the loser play when he's got
fingers coming from all over the place ?
So if the loser looks in the finger's directoin,
then you lose
And if you don't
you're safe
You just confused the hell out of us
Why not just ONE winner
If four of us win,
then one loser gets picked by the rest of us
Well, let's go back to the ONE winner system
But how long will it take to get just ONE winner ?
Let's just do it once
Let's try it
Amazing
That was miraculous
Who would have thought it'd be this easy ??
It's been 4 and a half hours
After a lively lunch, a visitor arrives
Thank you
Thank you very much
So you guys are the newly hired Hotel Employees
Huh ?
I'm in charge of all the in-house entertainment
Guest Entertainment Manager
Haruna Kondo
My name is Haruna Kondo
Nice to meet you all
You, too
We have our own resident entertainers
here at our hotel
And Mr. Fujiwara has asked me to introduce
some of our resident entertainers to you guys
Resident Entertainer Show
Here's our first act
C'mon out !
Alright
I'm Ken-chan
I'm Ban-chan
I'm Mah-kun !
And we are
*The term "Battery" means a
pitcher and catcher pair in Japanese baseball
BATTERIES
As usual, we're ready to hit some home runs
Yeah, ones that go over the stadium !
Mah-kun, are you ready to hit a big one ?
Well, since I'm a pitcher
I'm not great at hitting home runs
Why're you so stiff ?
Just go with the flow
and say you're ready to hit some
Indeed
Let's try this again
My league has a DH
thus, as a pitcher, I don't get to hit
Right, no time to practice hittin'
Why so stiff ??
Just pretend you're a hitter, too
Mah-kun, I couldn't agree with you more
Really ?
What did he say ?
Um, I forgot
What ? You forgot ??
We're BATTERIES !!
Anyway, let me point out how fit you are
This is aweful
Really awful
How tall are you ?
186cm
186cm ?
You can remember it as
ee (one) hah (eight) ro (six)
How much do you weigh then ?
90kg
How about
ku (nine) re (zero) ??
And your birthday ?
November 1st, 1988
ii (one) ku (nine) ha(eight) ha(eight) ii(one) ii(one) ii(one)
What are you doing with these numbers anyhow ?
What do you get out of that ?
I forgot
You forgot ?
Don't improvise
What's your uniform number ?
It's ii(one) ha(eight)
You're in on this, too ??
We're "Batteries"
Let's keep this momentum going
Yeah, let's go
Look, they're ALL nervous
Let's reenact a post-game interview
You know I can always talk up a storm
even during my professional career
Yes, you're very good at it
Why don't you teach this youngster a thing or two
about being a star athlete
I'm here with the winning pitcher,Tanaka
Congratulations
You threw very well today
How were you able to salvage your 9th inning ?
I'm very sorry
Why are you sorry ?
Customers were getting food poisoning
at one of my restaurants
Wait, you're talking about ME !!??
We're "Batteries"
Thank you very much
I'm fine with being OUT
but I felt bad for Mah-kun
I never dreamed of having Mah-kun out here
That was pretty cool
Amazing
I don't think they were that funny
They were too much
Hilarious
Their comedy just kills it
What a weird bunch
But very funny indeed
Well, I didn't think so
But there's more
We've had enough already
Here's some yonng talents, moving up the ladder
C'mon out !
This music is really annoying
Hello
And thank you
We are "Audrey"
"Audrey"
Masayasu Wakabayashi     Ichiro Itoh (ELT)
Let's get this show started with a bang
Tooosu !
That was the least audible "Tooosu !" ever
Kasuga ! Kasuga !
Again, you could hardly hear him but...
I don't think they can hear you in a back
Let's get the show started
I can barely make out what he's saying
Damn you !!
Don't worry.
I, Kasuga, will never hit on any fans
Well, you have no fans anyhow
His voice is so freakin' low
So I was thinking of maybe moving
What ?
Don't be the one wanting to move
The reason I want to move is
I can't hear him at all
because my house is so old that...
My house is falling apart and...
Because the house is so old that I can't invite...
Who the hell are you talking to ?
My audience, of course
C'mon, get this right !
So the house is too old to stay there any longer...
Then stay out of Japan
You stay out off the earth, moron !
As I said, I need to find a new house
So we can happily live together
Get outta here !
I can't talk to you anymore
Are you serious ?
If I were serious,
we wouldn't be here together right now
That was totally uncalled for
Thank you very much
Damn it !
What's with his voice ?
That was way too funny
Let's bring out the next act
Ready ?
Whenever you're ready !
I'm here !
For the past 50 years, I've wanted to be the next teen-idol.
Tama-ottei
Tamao Nakamura
The other day,
I was walking downtown
This lady came up to me and said
"You're in that period-drama !"
But she must've been talking about someone else
But don't sweat the small things
Tama-chiko Tama-chiko
When I was at the beauty parlor the other day
The stylist said to me,
"Tamao-san, you're still so young and beautiful"
"Nobody would ever think you're in your 80's"
Well, I'm still in my 70's
Don't sweat the small things
Tama-chiko Tama-chiko
I'm finished
Why do you get slapped ?
That was indeed hilarious
Thank you very much
Good bye
Damn...
How cool to see Mah-kun here
Really
All of them were awkward
This is a pay-per-view channel provided by Gasu Princess Hotel
Hello everybody
We're the MC's for "Po Channel"
License
Kazuhiro Fujiwara   Takafumi Inomoto
How's everyone doing ?
As you work as a hotel men for the next 24 hours,
we have Heipo-san over in that shack by the woods
Yes, he's alone
and will spend the next 24 hours in that shack
And we will be checking on him from time to time
So this is live
It's in real time
Yes, we're broadcasting live
Let us see how Heipo-san is doing at this moment
Pay per view channel showing Heipo's experience
What do I do now ?
Since he still has daylight,
he appears to still be ok.
So,
we're going to shut off all the lights
Right now ?
Yes, right now
Go ahead and proceed
This isn't cool
That scared the heck outta me
What    what   what ?!
Oh, nooooo
What's going on here ?
Hey ?
Could you guys cut me some slack ?
Seriously, don't let him talk
I'm scared
We'll be interrupting you guys to show
how Heipo-san is doing from time to time
We're looking forward to it as well
No, no more
You don't need to do this anymore
How annoying
They can definitely get us OUT every time
I see Heipo's got the short end of the stick, too
He could go crazy in there
Yeah, he could
He'll start saying weird stuff
He was already like, "What, what ??"
It's been 5 and a half hours
A gourmet event for a gourmet hotel
Listen up, guys
Critics from the Michelin Guide are here
to see how this hotel fares against other top hotels.
Shall we go observe them ?
Observation of the Michelin Guide Critics
We'll be transferring to the Main Building
Fujiwara kept my gloves super warm
Are we hopping onto a bus again ?
This way
What ?
Since this is a massive resort,
we're biking to the main building.
Bike to the Main Building
Man, it'll be a cold ride
Pick the bike with your name on it
Why do I get THIS one ?
Yamasaki has a baby seat in the back
It'll be cold
Let's get going
Hey, you guys all have electronic bikes
Electronic-assisting ?
Don't forget to turn your electronics on
I don't have that feature
Give me a break
Mine's just a regular bike
Wait !
Wait up ! Wait up ! Wait up ! Wait up !
Seriously
Wait for me !
What're you doing, Hosei-san ?
Turn left here
Wait up ! Damn it...
This sucks hard
Let't get up this hill
Wow, the electronics make it really easy to pedal
Follow me
Wait for me
C'mon, Hosei-san
I can't make it up the hill
Seriously
Wow, this is pretty cool
Pedaling is a piece of cake
*Permission obtained to shoot on this road
Wait for me !
Wait, everyone !
Hey
Switch with mine !
Hey !
I'm not kiddin'
Wait up !
First outside activity
A Brief Refreshing Time !!
But don't forget you're still in Suga Puri territory
There's no time for any breathers
It's quite a ways to the main building
Yes, this is a big place
Itsuji Itao
But seriously...
What ?
Cool
Ha !
Neigh !
Just amazing
How funny
I've heard he can ride horses but...
It hurts more out here
The horse was really neighing, right ?
Yes, it was
Amazing
That timing couldn't have been more perfect
He's a good rider
We're almost there
Turn to your right
Main Building
Good, we're here
It's cold
It is indeed cold
Why are we...?
Something about Michelin ??
Let' go inside
It's nice and warm in here
Down this way
Event Hall
Why don't you sit in the middle
Sit in order
Michelin's Fifth Annua
Hotel vs Hotel Humor Challenge
This is the fifth one already
Without further adieu
Let's start Michelin's Hotel vs Hotel Humor Challenge
Michelin's Fifth Annual Hotel vs Hotel
Humor Challenge
Employees from different hotels are judged on
their expertise in customer entertainment
With that said
Let's bring on the humorous contenders from each of the hotels
Entry No.1
Ryuichi Kosugi
"Not-Much-Hair-Left" Plaza Hotel
Entry No.2
Takayuki Haranishi
"Gang" Prince Hotel
Entry No.3
Takayuki Kinoshita
"If I don't, who will?" Hotel
Entry No.4
Hiroki Konno
Hotel "Chest-Hair" Ohtani
Entry No.5
Kazuko Kurosawa
Hotel "Pessimist"
Entry No.6
New Onii
Idiot Villa Hotel
What the hell is "New Onii" ??
Entry No.7
Mitsuo Ohkawa
Gasu Kurobikari Princess Hotel
Is Mr. Ohkawa present ?
Listen guys !
Ohkawa is a no-show
Would one of you step in for him ?
Decide among yourselves
I'd say Endo's a good candidate
Why me ?
I'm afraid you're the best candidate among us
You go
Can't decide yet ?
OK, Yamasaki will be representing !
Yes, it'll be Yamasaki
Wait, we had someone already
We JUST decided
We chose Endo !
From Suga-Puri, Hosei Yamasaki
Go ahead and approach the stage !
We said it's Endo
Hosei Yamasaki
Gasu Kurobikari Princess Hotel
Damn...Why me ??
Oh man...
Now that we have all the humorous contestants on stage
We will begin with our first topic
Here's
"Humor Word Relay"
As a Hotel Man, you're required to have
an abundance of vocabulary for any type of occasion
Humor Word Relay
Based on a given topic
contestants are to say a humorous word
Let us begin
Here's your first topic
Name a word that could be used as a brand of Japanese sake
Topic
Word for a Brand of Japanese Sake
Give us a humorous word that could possibly be a brand of Japanese sake
Let's start with our first contestant
Mr. Kosugi
Yamada Samurai
Returning of the Drop of a Star
Damn...
Let's keep going
Fish
He's not taking this seriously
Sweet Potato Chips
You know, that's already the brand name of a snack
You know that's already sold in stores...
Seriously, it's already being sold
We eat them as snacks
Will you shut the hell up, please ?
Please
Your laugh is contagious
Proceed
Lightening Food Goddess
Method to Kill a Swallow
Anything goes at this point
Nobody is following the rules
Why would you use the
word " Kill " ??
May I criticize ?
Nobody is following the rules
Next category
As a Hotel Man, more often than not
you will find yourself having to
gracefully move from point A to point B
With that, I introduce...
Humor Dancing
Dance humorously to the assigned music
Let us begin
He plays dirty
Look, he dropped his hat on purpose
*Cast members have laughed but enjoy the segment without interruption
He did that for the effect
This is taking too long
She's so helplessly dumb
What's he doing ?
Ding
How sad was that ?
Why were you staring at me like that ?
You had no sympathy for me
Yamasaki got no laughs from us
Let's move on
As a Hotel Man, you have to be available
for your customer's needs at all times
Humorous "What if" Impersonation
Answer with an impersonation
"What if xxxx was a Hotel Man ?"
C'mon up here
Challenger:
Ryuichi Kosugi
What if
Shigeo Nagashima were a Hotel Man ?
Like I said...
It's known as Hotel...
How may I help you ??
Like I said
Damn it
He sounds more like former Prime Minister
Former Prime Minister, Kakuei Tanaka
He's supposed to be Shigeo Nagashima
Thank you very much
Challenger:
Hosei Yamasaki
There goes our hotel's representative
Let us begin
Here's your first topic
What if Kenichi Mikawa were a Hotel Man ?
Welcome
How many ?
Just you ?
How may I help you ?
Please come in
What is this ?
Let me say that
the quality of his work is sub par
Let us move on
What ?
What if SAKANAKUN ("Fish Boy") were a Hotel Man ?
Wow, so you've made it
Ahahaha
Gyo gyo gyo gyo GYO~
Gyo ~
So it's just you
Gyo gyo gyo gyo gyo gyo~
Seriously
Let's move on
What ??
What if "Demon Kogure" were a Hotel Man ?
Welcome to my hotel
Shall I turn you into customers ?
Let this be the end, please ?
That's all from Yamasaki
If was almost as if the real people were here
Let's move on to the next contestant
This isn't over yet ?
Next up is
New Onii
Challenger
Let us begin
First topic
What if "Antonio Inoki" were a Hotel Man ?
Welcome !
Put down your names here !
Did you get that ?
Then, LET'S GO !!!!
This is way too terrible
What's this all about ?
My butt has just about had it
Let us proceed
Why "Let's go !" ??
What if "Eikichi Yazawa" were a Hotel Man ?
Welcome
Sometimes, it's refreshing for a woman to travel alone
What is this ?
He's completely ignoring the rules
Here's another one
What if "Paris Hilton" were a Hotel Woman ?
Hello
Did you have a
Did you have a reservation ?
What's your name ?
This is wa
"Where're you going ?"
Where are you going to with Tokyo ?
Incredible
What's with this format ?
I asked where you wanted to go
You said you've never been to Tokyo Tower
So, I asked if you wanted me to guide you there
Tokyo is quite a big city
And I don't know where I should take you to but...
What is he doing here ?
Where's Paris Hilton in this ?
Finished ?
Are you still good ?
I don't really know who she is so...
I couldn't impersonate her
but I thought it'd be a good idea
if I threw in some English
This is amazing, isn't it ?
New Onii is too awesome
New Onii owns this
Thank you very much
What a relief !
Next up
As a Hotel Man, you might have to be an actor
Humorous Big Drama
Given a topic, all seven contestants
have to improvise to create a story
Please gather at the center of the stage
Big Drama Pointer
It's important to take on a specific role
so the story can be built around it
I'm expecting to see lots of creative characters
Let us begin
Here's the topic
Theme
Murder of a Hotel Man
Begin
No~~~!!
Looks like a murder
We need to call the police
What's going on here ?
I'm a police officer
What happened here ?
This man is down
He appears to have been stabbed
*Cast members have laughed but enjoy the segment without interruption
Did you see what happened ?
No, I didn't
No, but I was informed of it
Who are you then ?
I'm just a Hotel Man
And what time did this happen ?
Yama-chan was wise to pick that role
About two hours ago
I see, two hours ago
Yama-chan is playing very cowardly
How do you know him ?
I'm his daughter
Is this a woman ?
No, I'm his daughter
So, this man is your father ?
I got it
And your name ?
His name is Masataka
I'm Masako
And you ?
I'm Koichi
Family name ?
Family name is Maejiba
What's going on here ?
Please, this is a police matter
This is a murder scene
Is that right ?
And I'm in the middle of my investigation
Are you his family member ?
No, I'm not
What exactly happened here ?
Who are you then ?
Please, stay behind this barricade
Excuse us ?
Yes ?
I had a reservation
You need to talk to him then
Excuse me, but I had a reservation here
Could you just confirm ?
Your name ?
I'm Kosugi
Your reservation will be honored anytime after today so
feel free to...
Just incredible
And that should conclude today's event
What a relief !
It's been 7 hours since the start
After the incredible Michelin event
Time to head back to the Annex
Man, his impersonation was something else
Indeed
Ah
Look
The bike seats have been stolen
Bike Seats are Gone
What are we gonna ..?
Well, we can't go back by bike
This is criminal
I'm in trouble here
What's this ?
Gaki Nori     Van Arrives !!
Foreign Driver
Our bike seats are gone
and we have no other way of getting back
Can you take us ?
Yes !
Cocorico and Yamasaki sit in a back
And Matsumoto and Hamada can sit in front of them
What's this jacket ?
We can wear it if we're cold
I'm thankful for this
Let's go
Thank you
What's this ?
Gaki Nori   Drive off to the Annex
I remember Fujiwara-san showed up in this van
Hiro !
I'm puttin' some music on
Everything started once we met
Why the hell are you singing it ?
I know there's times we hurt each other but
How annoying is this ?
Damn it
There he comes
And we have to get off the van, don't we ?
Yes, we do
The way Fujiwara interrupted
was irritating as well
It's been 8 hours since the start
It is already dark out
The cast members take a brief break
New Onii
How unconventional was his impersonation
of Paris Hilton ?
Very innovative
He sounded like he knew English
He was telling us what he was saying in English
Right, he translated what he'd said in English for us
Then, judges were like "Keep going"
You could see in his expression that he was annoyed
He was like, "Yes, so ?"
And then he'd start babbling again
Isn't he laughing ?
Seriously ?
You were no more than an average
middle-aged man on his break
Damn you, New Onii
Has Itao-san always ridden horses ?
Yes
Out of the blue,
He decided to take up a horseback riding
I had seen a photo of it before but...
And the horse neighing at the perfect timing
That couldn't have been more perfect
Almost too perfect
I seriously thought the sound was coming from some speakers
The horse was big, too
Yes, indeed
The horse was huge
I thought there were some speakers set up
to play the neighing sound
That was real neighing
Is a horse supposed to be that big ?
I thought the sound was coming out of speakers
There he goes
He's trying to hide his laugh
You were straight up laughing
Like a secret live
Hamada-san
you've been hit quite a few times this year
Many times
You've been laughing quite a bit this year
Did you guys see any speakers set up ?
Gulp
Why you...
My butt hurts...
I wonder what's up with Heipo-san right now..
Yeah
They've only broadcasted it once for us
I had forgotten about him
He was already terrified then
Should something tragic happen to him,
we can always edit him out of the show
(The judging) is very lenient
It was a perfect laugh
If it was really New Year's Day,
that would have marked your first laugh of the year
See ?
You wait a minute !!
Wasn't it just Matsumoto-san ?
Here it comes
Enjoy how Heipo has fared so far
Man, I don't wanna see this
What am I to do here ?
I don't wanna be here
I'm scared !
Do I have to stay in this awful place ?
What !?
What ?!
What's this ?!
There he goes
I'm staying here ?
What's with this mobile home ?
Seriously, this aint fair
They can't keep showing this to us
He loses his short-term memory, doesn't he ?
Because all of a sudden, he goes,
"Huh, what's this ? Where am I ?"
But I'd say you haven't left
C'mon guys,
I can't stay here for 24 hours
Let me just go home
You're kiddin' right ?
Man, I'm gettin' thirsty
But what ?
That fridge is freaky
But I need a cold beverage
Huh ?
What ?
Ramune (Soda) ?
Freaky ! Freaky ! Freaky !
The fridge is freaky !
Eh, eh, eh
This isn't good
Seriously, let's finish this
I can't watch this anymore
Ramune (Soda)
It's a cap
What now ?
I have stomachache
Please, no more
Pop
I see it's a soda
Ugh, what's this ?
I see, it's just a soda
I would rather watch the whole Po Channel in one sitting
Yes, rather than just clips here and there
The clip was a summariz...ed, ed, ed  ??
What ?
Summarized, what ?
Has the sun set yet ?
No, I don't think so
It may be around 5pm right now
I just heard someone laughing
Keep your eyes on Tanaka, please
Here's some ideas for the Hotel Men with lots of breaks
Listen up, guys
I thought you guys could kill some time with this
Here is a set of celebrity photos
I thought you guys could play "concentration" with these
Concentration ?
We could definitely kill some time with this
Shouldn't we have more work to do ?
Have fun playing concentration
I suck at concentration
Let's Jyanken to decide the order
First comes the Rock, Jyanken Hoi !
Order
1. Hamada 2.Yamasaki 3.Endo 4.Matsumoto 5. Tanaka
I'll go fifth
I'm fourth
I see
Hamada starts
I'll just pick randomly then
Here's one
Gajiro Saito
Who is this ?
This is Gajiro-san
Oh, yeah
It's him
I'm in bad shape
It helped that I didn't know who this was
Look how young Gajiro-san is
I thought it was Jimmy-san at first
I didn't know who this was
but I laughed simply at his funny face
There's way too many cards
Lots and lots of cards
I'll attempt to look at these as nothing more than a design
Here I go again
Yukio Hashi
I see, it's Mr. Hashi
I'm not gonna fare well with this one
I just forgot where the cards were
Who's next ?
Oh, it's my turn
Akira Nishikino
Eisaku Ohkawa
Wait a second
This isn't fair
I'd laugh at all of these
This is a tough one
Eisaku Ohkawa (2)
Michael Tomioka
There's Michael Tomioka-san
Let's move on
Peter
Why use a photo like this ?
How old is this photo ?
Peter
Gajiro Saito (2)
We've seen his photo before
We've seen a set of Gajiro and Eisaku
Where was Gajiro-san ??
I think it was around here
Antonio Inoki
Oh, there's Inoki-san
I got Antonio Inoki-san
First time
Antonio Inoki
Jaguar Yokota
I've got a set of wrestlers though
It was close but not close enough
I've got Gajiro-san then
Gajiro Saito
Very good
Teruhiko Saigo
That's new
Toshio Kurosawa
There's Toshio-san
Yes, he was laughing
Oh, he was ?
It's my turn
Eisaku Ohkawa
You got a pair
There's plenty new faces under these
I suppose I have to pick one
Shinichi Mori
It's Mori-san
Naoko Ken
Excuse me ?
I've gotten lots of hits here
It's Naoko-san
I believe Endo just got away with laughing
Endo, you just got lucky
I have absolutely zero clue
Shiro Kishibe
He's still very charismatic
This card just owned us
Shiro Kishibe
That was a first Kishibe-san card
Why not just pick one next to it ?
You were just laughing straight up
Hamada-san, you, too
No way, I wasn't
I was just surprised, that's all
I let out a scream because he got the pair of Shiro Kishibe
Kishibe-san were laid out next to each other
Look how young he is
What to do, what to do ?
Shiro Kishibe
This guys is...
Gajiro Saito
Shinichi Mori
You were laughing at Mori-san, Tanaka ?
Actually at the telephone
So he's making a call
Why don't we shuffle these around again ?
What do you think ?
Let's shuffle them around
Gajiro Saito
Now, we're completely lost
It'd be more fun like this
Hamada-san, are you up next ?
Yeah, we'll just start everything over
Should I put these back then ?
Shiro Kishibe
No, keep them
That's OK
You should keep them
Since you earned it
Alright
Pinko Izumi
Here comes Pinko-san
I got Pinko-san
Pinko Izumi
Alright
Yukio Hashi
Yukio-san again
Akira Nishikino
Is this right ?
You got a set of stars
I got these pairs
Matsumoto cards
Yamasaki cards
Hamada cards
No way, I'm OUT !
You got one tough pair
I wish Hamada-san would trade with mine
I'm just clueless
Let me pick one at the end
Naoko Ken
Oh, Naoko-san
She's right here
Alright
Very nice
Hamada cards
These are awesome pair
Check out this combo
See ?
Your voice started to wobble just now
I could tell you were going down
He's laughing
just by hear you talk
What's he doing now ?
Stay away !
He just laughed
I just caught him laughing
You two were getting out of hands
Don't be using our fellow celebrities as
some kind of laser gun
And he was still laughing just now, too
You laughed at Matsumoto-san's comment
about "laser gun"
Haven't you had enough horsing around ?
I wish I could've seen all of them
Why don't you stay put for a little while.
My butt hurts
My back hurts
Mine, too
This isn't good
9 Hours of Working
All Five Member's Butts are Being Tested !!
But the Real Hell
is about to begin!!
I saw Natsumi-san on Hotel introduction video
That was her debut on this series
Yes
Her debut indeed
All she did was talk with foreigners
She was having fun
Obviously, she recorded that prior to our show
How was she blessed with nice weather and not us ?
I got sucked into the New Onii's antics
NewOnii
He was incredible
He's a monster, isn't he ?
Yes, he's just a monster
What exactly happened with him and Paris Hilton ?
Well, he was told to impersonate her
But he realized he couldn't do it
so he more or the less lost it
And he started acting like a pest
Bang
Shocking Turn of Events
Then, let's go !
Top Celebrities
Ruthlessly Attacking the Casts!!
Unlikely Co-Starr
Laughing Hell Awaits !
What is About to Happen to These New Hotel Men ?!
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
Special Thanks to Alex
slayeer@home.nl
It's been 9 hours since the start
Time for one of the main events they hold at the hotel
Listen, guys
Let's go see how the wedding reception is held at this hotel
Here it is
It's held at the main building
Main building again ?
We'll be going by van again.
The atmosphere was kind of romantic at night
I guess the decorative lights caused it.
One of the main events: Wedding Reception
Off to Main Building by Gaki Nori Van!!
More Assault on Rookie Hotel Men
What Other Tricks are Waiting ?
Here's to the main hall
This way
Sit in a order of Yamasaki, Matsumoto, Hamada, Endo, and Tanaka
Be polite and congratulate them, OK ?
Look, there's a celebrity
We've seen him on TV
Attendee:
Haruka    Uehara
Stop, Taka-chan
Hold it, Taka-chan
Taka-chan, Taka-chan
A Child is Running Around
I told you to sit still at the wedding reception
Are you chewing ?
Are you chewing gum ?
Spit it out
And throw it away
Throw it away
Taka-chan
Ah !
Chewed Gum in Hair
I'm sorry
It's OK, no worries
*Please, don't try this at home
God, it's SO glued on his head
No way, he can get that out
That's not acceptable
Mirror
Thank you all for waiting
It is time for the bride and groom make their entrance
Bride and Groom Enter
Who is that woman ?
Groom
Yoichi Numumizu
Bride
Hisako Kuroi
I don't believe she's a celebrity
Please give a warm reception
to the bride and the groom
Many of their friends and family are here to give congratulatory words
Congratulatory Words
Here is the bride's workplace manager
Kazuo Nishio from Pizza Cap
If you would come out please
Pizza Cab
Kazuo Nishio (Tomochika)
Well, I pre-arranged to park my motorbike by the front of the hotel
only to be told by the bellboys that I can't park my bike there
So I had to park by the main road
My ass hurts
Please, Yoshio-san
Why "pre-arranged" to park ?
Well, I'm in this booming and booming business of delivery service
Anyhow,with fewer staff in hand,
I'm now taking orders, too
At the end of this year we get new customers
who usually don't order pizza.
Tons of them
And they don't have any clue on how to order
They just tell me to "put on some corn"
or, "put on some ham"
But I need to know the size first
Nishio-san is tough
And you know we're all in the same age group,
so we like to have BBQ and go for a drive on our days off together
Anyway, you know our store manager is really into Mark II,
and he would buy this car every time there's been any little changes
So, now he has been driving the heck out of the new Mark X
What a moron
I personally know one (who likes Mark II)
I wish you happieness
Banzai !!
Damn it
Nishio-san never misses this series
Nishio-san sure gets around though
Here's one of groom's celebrity friends, who over the years,
has also become aquiented with the bride
Please give a warm welcome
Ah~
Friend of Groom
Chiaki
Chiaki here, Pu
As I see you two together like this
I'm reassured that you two a perfect for each other
Well, I'm getting married again soon
Stop the Presses ! Chiaki's Engaged to be Married !?
He would be my third Onii
Huh? Who ?
And...
I brought him here today
so that we can give our speech together
Third Onii Third Onii
Here's Comes the Third Onii !
Let me introduce to you
He's my third Onii
His name is Jyunji Endo
That's my younger brother
Endo's Younger Brother
Jyunji-san
Why is he here ?
Let me tell you what I'm into
Or rather, why not show it ?
Chiaki's Favorite Skit
Seriously, don't do this
What does he do for living ?
He's a Hotel Man
But he's definitely not like this
This is way out of his character
Don't do it
Seriously, don't do it
Borrowing Brother's Skit "Hohohoi"
Don't do this
This is not who you really are
Can you get down with Samba Rhythem ?
Wow, this is tough to watch
Ho Hoi !!
I want to go to a ghost town
Ho Ho Hoi ! Ho Ho Hoi !!
Quick drum roll
Just incredible
He's your real brother
Onii
I'm sure I'll truely be happy this time ♥
*Thank you, Jyunji-san, for your cooperation
Let us move on to tonight's entertainment
Entertainment
First, we have a celebratory Taiko Drum Ensemble
Taiko Ensemble Leader
Kazuo
Man, he is only skin and bones
This was really powerful
Yes, it was powerful
What is this...?
Ureyaaa~
Amazing
Awesome
How thin is he ?
We've invited one of grooms' friend
for a magic show
Please give them a warm welcome
Here Comes Chono from the Box !
Be more greatful,  because this is MY magic show !
First, this is my "Card Tricks" !
Mr. Chono, what seems to be the problem ?
Hey !
My cards are missing !
Chono's Cards are Missing !!
What the hell's going on here ?
I can't go on like this !
Hey !
What gives ?!!
Anger is Aimed at the MC
We're very sorry about this
Please
This is not your responsibility
Groom Accepts Responsibility
I should be accountable for
anything that happens during my wedding reception
So go ahead and punish me however you see fit
I'm not sure...
Wait !
I observed everything that just happened,
But let me first introduce myself
I'm in charge of the hotel's personnel department
My name is Fujiwara
We understand your frustration today
Because of the hotel's mistake,
you can't congratulate your friends
in the way you intended
So here's my suggestion
Well...
Wear this blindfolding mask...and...
Put these on and...
and if you can catch one of these five men,
you can deliver a slap to him
Fujiwara's Suggestion
Catch Someone While Blindfolded and Deliver a Slap
How does that sound to you ?
This doesn't sound legitimate at all
Get over here then !
All of you
Hurry up
Wait a minute, just wait
We're going ?
All of you, line up here
Line up, in a single file
Let me put this blindhold on
See-through Mask
I just need to grab one, right ?
Anybody, right ?
What's going on here ?
Yamasaki is Targeted
Hey !
Don't try to get away
Get back in line, all of you !!
How's this ?
Is this it ?
Or, who's this guy !?
Don't try to get away !
Who's this tough guy ?!
Not good, not good
Damn you, Yamasaki
Look at me !
The rest of you ! Take your seats !
You stay here
Don't you leave, asshole !
Please wait
Put your uniform back on
Why me ?
I'm not finished yet !
C'mon, give me a minute !
Hey !
Hey, Tanaka~!!
Why ??!!
Yamasaki, seriously
I'm begging you
Just get this over with
Please, let's just do this
What the hell do you want ?!
What does this mean ?
What are you asking ?
You could see me with that fake mask !!
It was semi-see-through !
Are you accusing me of cheating ?
How about a Double-Slap then ?
Please, wait a minute
Just wait !
Get over here !
Please give me a second !
Give me some some some some some some some time
Seriously, I need some time
What is exactly going on here ?
Quit it already
You have no choice !
Yamasaki-san, just get this over with
You (Tanaka), you had your turn this morning
Please, just do this
It'll be good for all of us
What do you mean "good for all of us" ??
Aggghhh
Seriously, why me ?
Of course I couldn't see with it on
I can clearly SEE YOU !!
Yes, I can see you !
I can see you, Chono-san !!
Just get over here
Wait !
I can see you!
No
No No
No, No, No !!
We've seen enough of this !
Let go of me !
You stayed close to him
so he couldn't slap you
This is taking too long
Too long!
I know what you're saying
Yes
Arrrggghhh~!!
Ouch ! You got my ear !!
Damn it, we've had enough of this !
How phony are you ?
Your friends get punished for your antics
Get over here
Could you use your left hand?
No, I can only use my right hand
Then will you not take that stance ?
Your requests are getting more annoying every year
I'm sorry
but if you could grant my request, I'd do this
Get over here then
Ah, I'd be scared
Yes
I got it
Wait !
Hold on !
I'm scared !
You must've been scared
Because this isn't just
an everyday slap
If you try to get away, it'll hurt more
I know, I know
I know you're taking a hit for everybody else today
You're starting your new year's right
What now ?
I'm ready
Here we go
Man up !!
Unfair Slap Moment !!
This really does hurt a lot
Out of control
And we got slapped for laughing
at you getting slapped
It is out of control
This was hellish
What an awesome wedding reception that was
Let's head back
He never gave up trying to get that gum out of his hair
He never took his eyes off that mirror
It's been 10 and a half hours since the start
After the reception,
they're back in their break room
I need to go pee
What's my world coming to ?
I'm 46 and getting my ass slapped everytime I laugh
What's our average age this year ?
What ?
What's this ?
Again ?
Today's Third Mysterious DVD
We have another one
Photo of Gajiro on his chair
Sets it up for Matsumoto
Eisaku Ohkawa
Wait a sec
Why is this here ?
Why ?
What's so funny ?
Wait a sec
Why, why, why ?
We returned these photos
Ouch
Man...
Staffs are evil for doing this to us
Eisaku Ohkawa
Places it inside Matsumoto's desk drawer
You got anything in yours, Tanaka ?
I got this one
Quickly
Gajiro Saito
What the hell were you guys doing ?
Hide that, he's coming back
How irritating is this setup ?
We got counter-struck
What now ?
What's going on ?
We were laughing at some things that happened here today
Gajiro Saito
Who ?
And what do you have there ?
This is a new one
I'm sure they want us to watch it
Should we ?
Let's watch it now rather than later
Touch
Lyrics: Ken Chin Fua
Music: Hiroaki Serizawa
Here it is again
Here we go again
The same routine
Holding his breath for a moment
Tanaka gives a serious look
And he hears nothing after that
Tanaka is lonesome
He won't admit just how much
he loves the ones he cares about
He simply ignores his tear drops
How many times does he have to
follow the same path
to save Tanaka
So, please
Kick, kick, kick him in his ass
Just give it to Tanaka
Stick your ass out and get kicked
Kick him so hard all he can do is sigh
You're kidding me, right ?
Tanaka Receives Thai Kick
This isn't cool at all
This isn't cool
Why me ?
Stay still or it'll hurt more
That's difficult to take
Getting a Thai Kick right now is merciless
Why me ?
That killed
Shirou Kishibe
Why don't you open this drawer ?
That caught me off guard
This is exactly what I didn't want to see happen
We should have returned all of these props
I DID return them
Yeah, we did
Matsumoto-san, why don't you check yours ?
Eisaku Ohkawa
This is what happens when you don't return things
I suspected this kind of thing would happen
Gajiro Saito
Let's cut this out
Let's stop
No more of this
Nothing good can come out of this
Here we go again
Here comes the Po Channel
Enjoy how Heipo has fared so far
Ding Dong
Who is it ?
No, No way
What do you want ?
Who is it ?
Who ? Who ? Who ?
Excuse me, Heipo-san ?
You scared me
What is...
What happened ?
You're bored, aren't you, Heipo-san ?
I'm bored
But I don't wanna stay here any longer
I wanna go home
I thought you'd be bored
So I brought you some videos to watch
No, no way
I'm scared
I don't wanna watch any videos
Fun Video
What the heck is this ?
I see they're beetles
I'm terrified of the beetles
Man, look at them fighting each other
How scary
Why're they so shiny anyway ?
And he's up, he's up, he's up
He's picked up ever so high
He's picked up
I'm scared
This is scary
Man, the lion's going at it
Well, no, I mean, he's actually attacking it
How is this video OK ?
No more
I'm scared !
That is gross
No good
Not one bit
This is something else
Man, I hate blood
I hate this
I can't do this
Ouch! ouch! ouch! ouch! ouch! ouch! ouch! ouch! ouch! ouch!!
OUCH! OUCH!
Man, that hurt
What ?
What's this ? A dragonfly ?
What is he, a newborn baby ?
He's fascinated by everything he sees
I see, it is a dragonfly
Ahhh, Amazing
Couldn't you have edited without static ?
Huh ?
What the hell ??
What're they doing ?
He can't keep his mouth shut
What ?
That's disgusting
I don't like this channel
I'm not a fan of "Po Channel"
Why don't we visit
the opening of the hotel's musical night ?
Opening Night
Experience the Musical
Where are we going to see it ?
We're going to third floor
Musical ?
We haven't done any Hotel Men duties today
Really
3rd Floor Event Hall
You guys can sit in premium seats
Here we go again...
I'm starting to feel
uneasy about this...
Thank you very much
to all of you for coming tonight
I'm proud to announce the musical number
that will be shown for the next 12 months
here at the Gah Su Kurobikari Princess Hotel
It is an epic musical
And here's the title
Romantic Musical
ROCKY
Before the premiere
I'd like to introduce you to our star-studded cast
First, he's a 29 year veteran in this business
C'mon out !
29 years in business
Hitoshi Ozawa
Our next actor has been in this business for 45 years
45 years in business
Jin Nakayama
Here's an actor who's been in this business for 40 years
40 years in business
Akira Nishikino
And she's just had her 37th wedding anniversary
That has nothing to do with this
Married for 37 years
Claudia Umemiya
This is a tough cast
There goes Claudia-san again
I'd like to ask the actors to get ready for the start of the musical
I still don't know who's playing Rocky
I can tell who'll be Adrian
Tambarine Player
Gonzo
Cast has laughed but get to enjoy the segment without interruption
What is this ?
What ?
What are you ?
Director: Mr. Ohnuma
What the hell ?
Get on with Rocky already
Where's Rocky ?!
He must've practiced his ass off for this
That's pretty cool
An amazing performance !
He must've practiced really hard for that
Show us Rocky
Rocky
Yeah, really
That time-filler was uncalled for
Here we go
Opening
1976, America
It was the year people witnessed
the strongest and most cold-blooded
Heavy-Weight boxing champion
Apollo
Hitoshi Ozawa
I'm Apollo
the undefeated and undisputed champion of the world
Why did I pick that street thug as my next opponent ?
I'm doing it to create a buzz and gain popularity
That's all
In the meantime, Rocky is...
Rocky !
Micky
Jin Nakayama
Damn it...
Let me ask you
Have you seen a man in a black hat with a leather jacket
And he has a husky voice
Where're you, Rocky ?!
Rocky !?
Rocky
Claudia Umemiya
Shouldn't she be Adrian ?
He's supposed to be drunk ?
He's drinking
What's she doing ?
Why're you swaying back and forth ?
Rocky ! Where've you been ?
Her Lines Are Written on a Cheat Sheet
Well, I was heading to your office...
You mean, the gym ?
Office ?
You know I'm your best friend, right ?
No, you're not my best partner
Adrian...
You're my everything !
Adrian
I see, this is a musical
I love you
She's clearly laughing
She's not even trying to hide her laughter
I'm crazy about
everything about you
She's straight-up laughing
Damn it...
Terrible
Once again, she didn't memorize her lines
A Dog's Bark Introduces the Next Scene
Apollo is Ready for the Next Scene
5 Minutes Later
I'm not kiddin'
Man, this is taking too long
I was getting agitated
Don't they have any other SE (Sound Effect) ??
As Rocky prepares to challenge the world heavy weight champion
Apollo for the title
His rigorous training with Micky
has begun without any time to rest
Both Fighters' Training Begins
Wahoo !
Wahooow !
Uwah !
And finally, the day of the fight arrives
Where's Adrian ?
In the red corner
Weighing 220Ibs
Apollo Creed !
In the blue corner
Weighing 200Ibs
Rocky Balboa !
Go Rocky
Use your feet
There he landed one
What is this ?
Go Rocky !
Crash
Referee Falls Off the Stage
*Star is so serious
*Star is his nickname
What do you think you're doing ?
I'm just gettin' started
Shut the hell up, old man !
Ohhhh ~
Let the Slow-Motion Start !!
Huh ?
Down !
He's no match for you, Rocky !
Shut the hell up, stupid old man !
Final Round !
Now, Rocky, Get him !!
Down !
A Dramatic Finale Follows Rocky's Victory
Where's Adrian ?
I guess she's not in this play
Adrian !
Special Guest
Adrian
Tatsuo Umemiya
Claudia !
Adrian
Adrian !
Claudia !
You're kiddin' me, right ?
Claudia
I love you !
I love you, too, Adrian !
I love you
Damn it
Great performance
This will be a long year for her
She needs some help real quick
It's been 12 hours since the start
Game is at half way point
Hamada is cautious of the drawer
Gajiro Saito
Set it up for Hamada's desk drawer
Naoko Ken
Have you seen this yet ?
Anything goes at this point
I don't agree with that
What you gonna do ?
Seriously ?
There's not much you can do
I think they just got the wrong guy
What's going on ?
He got caught laughing by himself
Did it just get chilly in here ?
Endo, can you grab me an orange juice ?
Maybe you should gargle
I've already done that once
Naoko Ken
Hamada san
When I went to grab the juice,
I noticed Ken Naoko-san inside
Are there any toothpicks around ?
I've seen them in here
Gajiro Saito
Please remove your cup
Yes, please
Please
Remove it, please ?
There's no arguing about that one
That wasn't good, Hamada san
Wait a sec, guys
You set him up nicely
by asking about the toothpicks
Very natural
Gajiro Saito needs to be banned
I agree, Gaji san should be...
Well, I would be OK with his current photo
But not this one
It's his hair-cut
Agreed
Why the hell are you still in possession of that ?
That needs to be destroyed
Well, let me just put this away for now
I'm requesting an official "3 Laws of Non-Gajiro"
Here we go
Man...
I already can tell this will be bad
Instructor: Keiko Suzuki
The hotel receives many complaint calls on a daily basis
This video will assist you with complaint situations
I'm 100% sure who's in this
Of course
He's definitely in on this
Let's learn what to do when you receive a complaint call
Here he is again
Hotel Man
Saito san
Suzuki san
Here are two Hotel Men who have agreed to be on camera
Hotel Woman
Onishi san
and a Hotel Woman, Onishi san
Amazing already
Hello, front desk
I just had one of the worst experiences dealing
with your concierge service
Kanshuji...
What kind of training are you guys providing ?
I see, it's Kanshuji ??
I'm talking about the Concierge
Here he comes
This isn't good
Why can't we watch the whole video first ?
Instead of coming in and out like this
We're in trouble if they're stopping the footage every time we laugh
What's "Kanshuji ?"
Don't recite him, Endo
Sorry about that
I'm talking about your Concierge
Kanshuji ?
Concierge
Kansho-jyu...
Kansho-jyu is...
Do you understand what a Concierge is ?
Of course, I do
Then tell me what it is
Well...Oh, I see it now
So You're saying
how you didn't care
um...about how you had felt
What's he saying ?
What's he talking about ?
No more, please
That hurt
I'm really hating this
Seriously...
I demand an apology
I'm really sorry about this
and acknowledge how much I'm regretful about this
Can't you give a formal apology ?!
A formal apology ?
To never have this type of incident occur to...
To never have this type of incidentoccur to...
On behalf of the store manager,
I'm, I´m offering my deep and deepest gratitude
I'm offering my deepest gratitude
Damn it
Why "store manager ?"
What an incredible person
He gets better and better every year
Hello, front desk here
I still haven't received my luggage from the Bellhop
I'm very s~o~r~r~y~ about that
What is going on ?
What kind of training have you completed?
Well, I've taken some literature classes and
Well, a social studies class..
I've taken all the necessary courses
Aren't you a Hotel Man ?
Then tell me the 3 Rules of being a Hotel Man
Well, then I'm only gonna recite the First Rule
Recite only the First Rule
Can't he name all three ?
Damn you...
My ass hurts
I'm only gonna recite the First Rule
Democracy of the people
by the people, and for the people-people
He's so unruly
This isn't good
Out of our hands
Hello, front desk
I've been really itchy since I checked into the hotel
Is it supposed to be bug-free in here ?
Well, everyday, well..
We're doing some spraying here
Well... I don't believe...
we're keeping any insects like that here
Whatever it is, help me get rid of this itchiness
I...I'm assuming you're by the flowers
The flowers ?
What do I do with it ?
Hold onto it and then
Yank off the petals one by one ?
One petal at a time
Yank them off one petal at a time ?
Amazing
Just incredible
Impossible !
I'm expecting to be compensated
for all this trouble
Yes ?
Compensation
Are you seeing a doctor for this ?
I'm asking to be compensated !
Will this come out of my own pocket ?
To compensate her ?
If it's from my own pocket,
how does... $50 sound to you ?
You're not really sorry about this, are you ?
Of course, I am
I don't think you're sorry enough !
Well, let me tell you what I have to do to get by these days
I had Onigiri (rice ball) with fish eggs and mayo
and also a sausage tempura
with a side of tuna for lunch today
So if you could find it in your heart
to cut me a deal between $50 to $100
I would appreciate it
Forget it, I'm asking for at least $1,000
I can't pay you $1,000
Can't you cough that up on your own ?
Well..
I suppose...
I can cancel my life insurance
Just amazing
He's one amazing character
I almost made it through
I was so close
Do you think that's the last we'll see of him ?
I know what you mean
No way he's done with us
I don't think Jimmy san is done with us yet
He'll come at us with something different
Absolutely
This is the busiest time to check people in
at the front desk
Why don't we go help them ?
Seriously ?
Helping the Front Desk
I can't tell what time of the day it is right now
But it doesn't feel like a busy time of day for a hotel
I'm feeling the gravity
I need all of you to get behind the front desk
How're we supposed to know what to do ?
Sit tight and patrons should start to show up
Checking in
Cobra & Lady
(Yuki Meguro)           (Obachan 1)
I have a reservation for two
My name is Cobra
Fill out this form ?
Yes, please
Never thought I'd see Cobra in real life
Lady rubs his butt
C O B R A, there, I did it
She wouldn't stop rubbing his ass
We all know woman like her, don't we ?
And my address ?
Psycho-Gun Goes Off !
That scared the hell out of me!
You ready, Lady ?
That really scared me
Damn you, Cobra
We have a reservation for three
We're the "Boing-ers"
We're here to protect peace on earth
May I ask who you are again ?
We're the BOING-ERS !
We'rethe BOING-ERS !
I've never heard of you before
Me neither
Our goal is to save the planet
Since there's no more male superheroes
we have taken on the role
Right, sisters ?
Yes
Here come the Villains
First rule is to sniffle our Boings
Second rule is to absorb an inexcusable Boing
And the third rule is to defeat all the ugly perverts
Boing-Rangers
Here's our chance, my sisters
Here's our finishing move
Boing-Galaxy
To call this entertainment is an insult
Villains disperse
Why don't we check in then ?
That kind of thing happens a lot ?
Sure
We don't get to see it at all
That's my first time as a matter of fact
Is that so ?
You know what, guys ?
What's so funny ?
Listen
You've been staring for a while
Excuse me ?
You're staring at our Boings
with your perverted eyes
No way, ma'am
I don't think so
Yes, you have, too !
Tomoko-san, men will always be men
Tomoko-san, why not tip them ?
Yes, I will
Man..
How do I not see that ?
Dollar bill
Hey
You moron
Yeah, you
Here
Get it with your mouth
How humiliating
You guys fight for justice, right ?
But you have such foul mouths
Not very superhero-like
Get your tip
Good job
Sister, are you OK ?
She's got the giggles
Aren't you cold just standing here all night ?
Let me see your hand, please ?
Oh boy, his hand is freezing
Tomoko-san, you can warm him up, right ?
Hand warmer
Why not just give it to me ?
Hey !
Here
Get it with your mouth
Man, you're gross
Yeah, you !
You're gross
Hurry up and get it
She's got such a potty mouth
How disgusting are you ?
Just get it
Just do it
We're so relieved
Shall we go now ?
Why is she one of them ?
She's the odd one out of the three
Yeah, that one in the yellow
Excuse me, but I've been looking for my golf bag
Have you seen it ?
Don't come at me so serious
Look at his eyes, he's not messing around
Golf bag ?
The golf bag has blue and white on it
Blue and white ?
Yes, sir
No one has reported that to us
I'm pretty sure I checked it in
Can you look it up ?
Oh, here it is
What a relief !
Saburou Ishikura is in the golf bag
Yes, this is my bag
Damn it
Is he supposed to be the 3-wood driver?
Thank you for your help
Why is he looking at us like that
He's so locked in on us
Locked in on us
I haven't seen a head cover made of wool in awhile
Yes, it was pretty old-school
I'm expecting a VIP anytime soon
Really ? I don't want it
VIP: M.C. Egar
Yes, we're all out
My ass hurts
Where is he ?
He took off without checking in
What was that all about ?
He was the VIP ?
12 hours have passed
Their shift is half way over
But there will be more laughing tricks and traps,
sending them into hell
We just saw footage from the wedding part
and Tomochika is definitely talented
Kazuo Nishio
Tomochika
Yes, she's good
with many skills
Who knew my brother would show up ?
Endo's brother
Jyunji-san
You guys don't look alike
No, not looks-wise
and he's definitely not the kind to horse around like that
He did a good job with "Ho-Ho-Hoi" skit
Right, and you had your annual...
Can we put an end to that ?
Chono's Slap
It seems as though it's become an annual event
An annual event ?
Then can he just come out and slap me
without all that hoopla leading up to it ?
Chono even muttered "every year"
Yes, he did
He said, "Your request gets more annoying every year"
It's been 13 hours since their work started
It might be time for their dinner
I would imagine Claudia is asleep by now
Claudia Umemiya as "Rocky"
Listen, guys
It's time for your dinner
Since you worked so hard today,
I've prepared gourmet meals for you
Thank you
Are we eating in here ?
Yes
I can tell this will be a pain in the ass
Why bring in these guys ??
Before I let you enjoy your dish
I need to tell you one of our chef's pet peeves
Garcon
Hiroaki Ogi   Ken Yahagi
which is to hear customers say "delicious"
Our chef is perfectly aware that his dish is "delicious"
so come up with other ways to compliment him
Well, let's pass these around then
I've got exceptional meals for each of you
Thank you very much
Thank you
Our chef is very proud of this dish
Go ahead and open it
Wow !
What a gourmet meal !
Amazing
Top of the line Bento box made with only the best ingredients
But they must compliment the chef without the word "Delicious"
It's difficult not to use the word "Delicious"
Hamada-san, will you take a bite please ?
I'm going first ?
Please
I have to report back to the chef with your comments
How's this one ?
That is *Umaki
*Umaki is a roasted, skewered eel wrapped in a fried egg
OK, I'm trying this then
Umaki
How is it ?
Well...
I don't know how everyone else feels,
but I like it
Great flavor
I'd say that was OUT
What do you mean OUT ?
You need to be Butt-Slapped
Really ?
Serious ?
You're kidding ?
I didn't use the word, "Delicious"
I'm looking for nice, creative comments
It's hard to tell what the criteria is
We'll show you an example then
Yeah, let's see it
Take any of these, please
He's got the sashimi
Tuna sashimi
Ah !
Yes ! Yes ! Yes !
Ah...Pretty good !
"Pretty good" is acceptable ??
What's going on here ?
I don't get the rules !
"Pretty good" is a safe phrase
Chef would be pleased to hear you say "Pretty good"
"Pretty good" ??
Tanaka-san, you look anxious to start
I'm going for this deep-fried crab thingy then
That's a great choice
Crab Croquette
w/ cream sauce
I'm impressed with the weight of it on my chopsticks
You like how it feels on your chopsticks ?
Chopsticks ?
Yes, on my chopsticks
I'm taking a bite
Wow, it is tender
with a copious amount of cream
I can appreciate the chef's choice of crab pieces
which can be enjoyed by all ages
And complimented well with fresh ingredients
Can't you make your comments shorter?
What the heck was that ?
(Tanaka-san) was OUT, too
Really ?
Don't you think that's too strict ?
Why don't you show them how it's done again ?
Yeah, show us again
What constitutes SAFE comments ?
His example didn't help us much
The job starts even before the first bite
Oh, I get it
I would say...
it's easy to pick up
I see, it's easy with chopsticks
Uneaten pieces fall off
That's nasty
Endo, did you have to point that out ?
I know
It was his fault
He's got zero manners
And it was before he even ate one
You cannot be dropping food like that
Yes Delicious !
You just said "Delicious"
You just said it
You said it
No, I didn't
You did, too
No way, I said it
What did you say then ?
I said "Magnificent"
"Magnificent ?"
I said "This crab is magnificent"
I thought you didn't like crab
I'm pretty sure you're not fond of crab
Matsumoto-san, I don't see you eating any yet
Of course, I haven't
I haven't touched any of it
Will you have some, please ?
Prawn
Oh !
I like the weight of this prawn
as well as its firmness
and its dynamism...
What is this all about ?
I thought I had it down
I started off great, didn't I ?
Yes, the way you started off was good
He was just gettin' started
He hadn't even taken a bite yet
Please continue
Check out its dynamism...
Sorry about that
What's "dynamism ?"
What do you mean by "dynamism ?"
Show them how it's done
Please, show us the proper way
I'd like to see the correct way
And don't drop any crumbs
How is it ?
Amazing !
Ah, it's grotesque
Chef will be angry to hear that
How is that OK, and not my comment ?
I definitely did it right
Chef won't be happy to hear that
I complimented it !
He was merely emphasizing how the "prawn" looks
You know what else ?
You were inspired to use an English word
because of my previous comment
No way, no way
You're not to criticize us
Please, go ahead and enjoy your dinner
I still get this one ?
Yes, here's your chopsticks
Left over
I guess we're done with you guys
We'll see you guys
He messed up your dinner
It has been 14 and a half hours
Nothing hurts but my ass
Enjoy how Heipo has fared so far
Mmm !
Sigh~
He hasn't done anything today to be tired
What did he do today ?
Ah !
Ah, ah, ah, ah !
What ? what ? what ? what ? what ?
What's going on ?
C'mon, I was smoking a cigarette !
How about some lights ?
Lights !
C'mon, lights ! Cigarette !
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm~ !
Seriously !
Can I have some light, please
Hah, huh, mmm, mmm mmm~ !
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm~ !
Ah ! Ah !
Ouch!!
Ha !
AHHHGGHH !!
That scared me...
He was trying to get light from sucking on cigarettes
*Members laughed already but will resume without any interruptions
Oh, I see
I am scared, that's right
I'm scared !
I'm scared, that's right
He's clearly lost it
I haven't seen him like this
I'm scared !
What am I to do ?
I hate this
Ding dong
Ah ! what ?!
What ?
What do you want ?
Good job
So far so good !
I thought you'd be hungry
Yes, I am
Here's some dinner for you
Thank you very much
Enjoy it
I'm too scared to open this lid
How can you be scared to open this ?
It looks freaky, doesn't it ?
Go ahead and open it
I'll stay here with you then
Really, I owe you one
Open sesame !
What's this ?
Udon noodles ?
Yes, it is Udon noodles
OK, then
I'll be around
Go ahead and enjoy the meal
I'm digging in
Ah ! I broke it !
Do chopsticks break so easily ?
I guess I can still eat it
Ahhhh !!
Who ?
I don't feel like eating now...
My appetite has vanished now
Well, I take that back
Spice
Pours
Give me a break !
What the...
Oh boy...
That sucked
Ah !
There's something in it !
What is this ??
It's a cap ~ !
I see, it's the spice cap that fell in
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah !
What the hell's wrong with this guy ?
I'm OK with being out but...
That's a side of Heipo we haven't seen before
Ah~, this is getting painful
My ass had had it at this point
Current Affairs Talk
~2009 Analysis~
Here we go again
Journalist
Akio Ohtani
Good morning
I'm your host
My name is Akio Ohtani
Our show is called "Current Affairs Talk - 2009 Analysis"
We discuss different topics with various experts
And today is no exception, we have a very special guest
Please, come on out
How're you doing ?
Good morning
My guest is Hideaki Onishi
Nice to meet you, sir
The pleasure is all mine
Please have a seat
Today's Guest
Political Commentator: Mr. Hideaki Onishi
Today's guest is political commentator, Mr. Hideaki Onishi
If you would go easy on me, I'd appreciate it, sir
Political Commentator
Hideaki Onishi
Same here, sir
Why don't we begin our discussion, Mr. Onishi,
of 2009 politics, economics, culture and legal cases
Nice freakin' face !
and approach them from every different angle.
But first, how would you
summarize 2009 ?
Sho
Sho ?
What the hell's up with his face ?
What stunned him just now ?
What got into him ?
Well, he sure stunned us
He thought he was supposed to summarize the year in one Kanji word
And the Kanji word he used referenced a new year
How would you summarize this past year ?
Sho
Sho ?
Let us move on to our first topic
OK
It involves turning Haneda Airport
into the main airport in the Tokyo area
Yes
What are your thoughts on Haneda becoming the main hub ?
Well...
The way I see it is
I'd say why not bring some *Habu (venomous snake)
*Habu is a venomous snake found in Okinawa area
from Okinawa
So that instead of having to go to Okinawa
to see Habu,
We can now see them in Haneda
once we build a Habu museum and such
I'd say we should go for it, yes
Well...
I'm not sure if we're talking about the same thing
I'm referencing the issue
of turning Haneda into the main hub
Are we both talking about the same issue ?
We're absolutely on the same page, sir
Well...
Your comment was well worth the listen
Thank you very much
Let us move on
The next topic involves dam-building
I'm talking about the Yamba Dam construction project
Of course, the country's in the midst of re-examining
many of our plans for dam construction
But as an expert of dam construction, Mr. Onishi,
I don't need to go too much into the details
And as an expert in this subject
I'd like to ask you to explain to our viewers
how a dam works
Just the basic Dam construction
Basic Dam construction ?
Yes
I'd appreciate if you could explain
the mechanics in simple terms
It's like me saying,
"Hey, I have to stop you right here"
Like this ?
He said "I gotta stop you here ?"
What's wrong with him ?
He's at it again...
I'd appreciate if you could explain
the mechanics in simple terms
It's like me saying,
"Hey, I have to stop you right here"
Like this ?
And when...
When it's a nice day outside and the water level goes down,
I can go, "Here, have some"
Like this ?
Sure
But here's where I think the problem lies
You cannot talk about Yamba Dam
without pointing out the projected cost
Back in 1986, the projected expense was 211 Billion Yen
However...
17 years later, in 2003,
the number jumped to 411 Billion Yen
Hah ~
With that in mind, I would like an expert opinion
as to why this increase happened
And also if you could give us an estimate
of the total expense in 2010
1, 10, 100, 1000, 10K
100K, 1Mil, 10Mil, 100Mil
1Billion , 1.1 Billion
1.2 Billion
1.3 Billion
1.4 Billion
What's his problem ?
Spectacular
1, 10, 100, 1000, 10K
100K, 1Mil, 10Mil, 100Mil
1Billion , 1.1 Billion
1.2 Billion
1.3 Billion
1.4 Billion
Well, no
I see that it's going up ?
Can I say it's a positively sloped graph ?
Yes, a Positive Slope Graph
This isn't fair
I'm getting tired of this
Please, let this be done soon
Do you understand anything about this Dam ?
Yes, of course
So it takes lots of money
If you could explain this to our viewers
by first pointing out the title of this graph
YAMBA DAM: CHANGE IN TOTAL EXPENSES
Yappa Dam
Total #$%^$%
Well, let's analyze this graph then
First, total expense was at 211 Billion Yen
As an expert, don't you find this increase to be odd ?
Well, I guess building a Dam...
Bump
I'm sorry
Ouch
Bump
What the hell ??
Damn it
This isn't good
That was a nice "bump"
Well, I guess building a Dam...
Bump
Ouch
I'm sorry
Please proceed
Sorry about that
Thank you for your explanation
Hah
I'm sorry about that
Is it OK if we move on to the next topic ?
Current Affairs Talk
~2009 Analysis~
END
Yes, let's move on
I wanna go home
It's been 17 hours since the start
They are too exhausted to carry on a conversation
My ass...
I wanna go home
Yamasaki !
I got a gift for you
Why don't you come with me ?
What ?
Come get your gift
What's this all about ?
I don't want it
I don't need any gifts
What, you gotta go get it ?
Just me ?
Yes
Man, I'd be sketched out
I'm freaking out
Yamasaki is taken to...
You can go back once you're dressed
Wait a minute
What is this ?
When I just tried to look through the window
I couldn't see anything but I heard Heipo's voice
He's going "Ahhhhhhhhh !!"
Jeez
Something's going on in that shack
Yeah, there's something going on
What's with that small mustache ?
I'm freezing
No joke, I'm freezing
I was so determined NOT to
laugh at this point
Did you have to put on that small mustache ?
That is a one messed up gift
If you only knew how freezing this is...
And that damned face...
I was freezing
Can't you stand up straight ?
You guys were going down one by one
Freezing !
Those guys running by created a breeze, right ?
I'm sure you're freezing
Endo, Can you take my place ?
I'm sorry, but no
Please, switch with me
You don't understand, I was already cold this morning
This is...
something I really don't want to be a part of
Please, Tanaka !
No, no, no,
Sorry, but I cannot do this either
Why can't you ?
Seriously, I'm beggin you
Just put this on once,
and I'll take it back right away
He's lying
I agree
Man, I've been freezing all day !
I'm not kidding
Will you stop that comedic run-around ?
I'm not kiddin'
I wish you'd stop pacing around like that
Put something on top then
That might help you
Excuse me, Hosei-san
Can I see your underwear ?
I'm asking because you've worn some weird underwear before
You still got that on ?
I just got a glimpse of it
Are you serious ?
You put that on at home today, right ?
Can you pull down those tan-colored pants ?
Why are you being so timid ?
Why do you wear those ?
What kind of underwear are you wearing ?
Allow me to ask you why
Why not ?
There's nothing wrong with it
Yes, there IS something wrong with that
I'm beggin' you now
This jacket doesn't keep me any warmer
You didn't put it on
See ?
And it's kinda big on me
I'm beggin you, Endo
Why're you laughing ?
No, I didn't?
You just laughed
No, I didn't
No, this isn't cool
Why ?
Wait a sec
This is gonna suck
This is hell
That must've hurt without
any kind of protection
And you were cold, too
Hoesi-san, please pull up your pants
Seriously,
I am beggin you
I'm beggin'
Endo
No
Absolutely not
Hey !
I've just about had it !!
Your senior is on his knees begging you !!
No, you weren't on your knees
What's with you two ?
Cocorico needs to at least address their senior
Get over here !
That's it !
No more nonsense !
I'm not letting you off !
Yeah, you !!
I can't take...
I can't take this !!
Come
Come with me !
Can't you see your senior's begging ?
I understand your position but...
I'm begging you...
I understand your pain but...
I'm beggin'
I know I know
What about Endo ?
Shouldn't he be included, too ?
Of course, he is
You and I are both juniors to Yamasaki-san
Why don't the three of us go then ?
No, you just go with him
C'mon, let's go
I really don't think I can...
No, seriously...
I can't take this anymore
Let's think about what to do on your bottom half
Minor Change
Despite Endo's help,
they end up only modifying Yamasaki's costume
I bet you're still freezing
And I'm supposed to be a Hotel Man ?
You're definitely not a Hotel Man
You found something after all
But what kind of Hotel Man am I ?
This might help you stay warm
Chono's Eye Mask
At any case, why not wear that jacket when you go outside
He's definitely not a Hotel Man
You're kiddin'
I don't see the meaning of all this
None of these go together
when you lift the lid open
So this is a Hotel Man ?
Don't say stuff like " lift the lid open "
What do you mean by " lift the lid open ?"
Can't you do anything for me ?
This is nonsense
If all else fails, just wrap this towel around your waist
I have to say...
You're becoming more and more
like a Hotel Man
I'm utterly lost right now
I'm starting to feel ill from this nonsense
People are gonna think I'm some kind of poser
What the hell ?
I wouldn't call you a poser
Hamada was laughing, too !!
Yes, he was
Zaki-san, could you somehow fix your outfit ?
And refrain from making comments about your appearance
Aren't your toes cold ?
Of course, they're cold
With your bare feet, I'm sure
Where're those gloves ?
I swear I've seen gloves around
Here they are
They're Matsumoto-san's
Anything goes at this point
He's just messing around
He's not serious enough
Get a hold of yourself !
You're doing this on purpose
You've gone too far with this
Of couse, he's OUT
You're screwing around too much
You've been laughing the whole time
Give me a break !
We need to negotiate
Listen, guys
As one of the top hotels
we have a blacklist of undesirable patrons
They're holding a meeting to put this list together right now
Wait, I need some clothes
Yamasaki, you're coming just like that
You're kiddin'
I'm definitely catching a cold
I'm afraid I'll be arrested looking like this
Endo can't wipe his smile off
Sorry, but I'm just embarrassed knowing HE's part of our group
Who's that guy ?
Tell me who that guy is
3F Conference Room
Look, these guys are even laughing
Sit in the order
They couldn't contain their laughter
Now that everyone is present
Let us begin with our blacklist conference
Blacklist Conference
To prevent problems,
List rude and abusive celebrities
Let's hear names of celebrities you know to be rude and abusive
Oh, you got one
This is about Hosei Yamasaki
Hosei Yamasaki Info
I heard that he's recently purchased a house
Purchased a House...
So when one comic asked him whether or not to invest in a house
Hosei Yamasaki Information
Purchased a House
Yamasaki gets weirdly excited and
he says, "All of you need to buy a house"
in a really high pitched voice
It's obvious he's trying to make people laugh,
but even the make-up person wasn't laughing
The judge's couldn't see you
laughing under that mask
I know, I was laughing the whole time, too
You got lucky with that
Anything else ?
There's this man named Masatoshi Hamada...
Masatoshi Hamada Information
he was hosting his TV show
where he showcases different festivals in Japan
Hamada's TV program "Festival"
And it showed this one festival
where it was the town's custom to offer rice cakes to their God
and then the townspeople get to scramble and fight for the rice cakes
And the question came up
"What would happen if someone grabbed some Mochi,
before they signaled OK ?"
And as we were about to answer,
Hamada said, "Don't bother with answers"
"Why not just do it ?!"
So one of the guests on the show went for the rice cake
before we were signaled a "go for it"
Then Hamada smacks his head with a bamboo stick
Then Hamada smacked his head with a bamboo stick
He sounds like a handful
Out of control
Get it together
No kiddin'
So he had a bamboo stick ?
Masatoshi Hamada
Hamada's TV Program "Festival"
Now, you would think it's over, right ?
Well, it wasn't because Hamada then said,
"You do it next, Katsumata !"
Of course, nobody objected to it
So I went to grab a rice cake,
only to be smacked by Hamada's bamboo stick
He sounds out of hand
He should be listed on the blacklist then
Of course
I heard this from Inomoto
Masatoshi Hamada Information
It happened at a Golf course
At Golf Course...
where there's no caddy service
but instead, every player gets a navigation system on their golf cart
Unfortunately, Inomoto and his staff's navigation system wasn't working great
And they weren't sure what to do until Hamada-san came to help them
Hamada-san saw a "EXIT" button on navigation system and said
"Ah, why don't you press this EXCITING button ?"
Exciting ??
I don't think anything should be excited at that moment
He didn't even question why an "EXCITING" button's there ?
That is a terrible mistake
He must be uneducated
Not educated
I also have heard one from Inomoto...
Hamada-san took some of the young comedians out
Masatoshi Hamada Information
to an expensive gourmet restaurant
At Gourmet Restaurant...
As they were about to enjoy their course meals
Hamada-san became very irritable after the appetizers
And no matter how much the comics continued to enjoy the meal,
Hamada-san just kept chain smoking looking irritated
Apparently, he went through two packs of cigarettes
So all the comics assumed Hamada-san wasn't into the meal
or didn't care for the service
But the truth was that
by the time the appetizers were served,
Hamada-san had crapped his pants
At a gourmet restaurant ?
Why did he crap his pants ?
How come ?
Isn't Hamada an adult ?
Yes, he's not a child
I heard he left a nice crap stain on the chair
Doesn't he know there's a bathroom ?
His butt had turned stupid
Let's discuss someone else
OK, I got one about Endo
This is unconfirmed but...
Shozo Endo Information
it's about his buttocks
It's about his buttocks...
He claims that a @#$%^ size bottle can easily fit into his ass
That's an OK size...
What ?! I would say that's huge
Anything about his better half, Tanaka ?
Tanaka...
I have no information about him
Me neither
I got one
Oh, you got one on Tanaka ?
Naoki Tanaka Information
I heard this from one of the 3 comics
who worked with him on a TV sketch comedy show
At sketch comedy show
Evidently, they all had a great time shooting the show with Tanaka
That's about it
So, he's a good guy
He doesn't belong on the list then
Sorry, my mistake
Yes, he's a good person
Excuse me but...
I've got a dirt on Junior Chihara
Junior Chihara Information
He used to stay at a hotel in Osaka
which is used by many local comedians
At a Hotel in Osaka
The hotel is known to be forgiving toward rowdy crowds
so they get business from young comics in town
Anyhow, when Junior stayed there,
he used so much lotion
that he was asked to purchase a new bed comforter
He must have used a crap load of lotion then
We're starting to get the ball rolling
Junior Chihara Information
Junior was having a heated argument with his elder brother in front of the monitoring camera
Argument with Brother
But none of the staff wanted to get involved
thinking they were arguing about their skit
But you could hear them saying things like
"No, you decide !", "No, you do it !"
It turned out that Junior received a gift from their aunt
and they were arguing about how to go about splitting it
And what was the outcome ?
I don't know
I'd love to know what happened
I've got a dirt on someone else
Matazou Mimata Information
This is about Matazou Mimata
He is in charge of *Takeshi's Apartment Complex
Manages Takeshi's Apartment Complex...
*Takeshi Kitano aka "Beat" Takeshi is a well known comedian and a film writer and director
By the way, this apartment complex is only occupied
by Takashi's Fan Groups visiting from England, France, and Italy
And he lets them stay there for free
as a token of Takeshi's gratitude to his overseas fans
Anyway, Matazou Mimata is supposed to manage this complex
But all Takeshi fans say the same thing
after they express how much they enjoyed their stay in Japan
" I don't ever want to stay in that apartment complex again "
They all had a great time meeting Takeshi-san
and sightseeing in Japan
But they don't like the apartment complex
There must be something fishy going on there
I'm suspecting foul play by the manager
Of course, you had no idea about this but...
Ita....#$%   An Italian....
How come you stuttered just now?
He wanted to say Italian, but couldn't
Here's one about Hitoshi Matsumoto
when he went back to Osaka for the summer
Hitoshi Matsumoto Information
Summer in Osaka...
It must have something to do with just getting married,
but when we went to the Karaoke bar,
He did not let go of his microphone until 5am
What a jerk !
Well, I didn't know he was like that
That's very uncharacteristic of him
He seems to be really into the lotion
Hitoshi Matsumoto Information
Lotion...
And he always carries it in his bag
Like a portable one ?
Yes, when he has to travel far for work
This one time, the cap came off the bottle
and it went all over his bag
So he quickly threw @#$% in that bag
He didn't want to be wasteful
Amazing
He wanted to salvage the loss
Eco-Bag !
We don't want that bag brought here
Ok, I'm continuing with Hitoshi Matsumoto information
Hitoshi Matsumoto Information
We all know that he just had his first child
Not good
So any time we're out drinking,
he would pull out his phone to show everyone a photo of his daughter
But the screen dims when the phone's idle for a while, right ?
So when one of the younger comics said,
" Oh, she's very cute "
Matsumoto-san goes,
" No, look at it with the lights on "
That's not good
He insists on showing it to you in the best condition
He sure has changed
Because you can still see the photo on dim, right ?
Of course
But he kept pushing the (Cell phone's) button to activate the light
I almost don't want to see him like that
Haven't you had enough ?
Let's go back
Shall we ?
But we were just getting started
17 Straight Hours of Work
Their strength and willpower are about to end!!
The exhausted members
ppppppprrrrrrrrbbbbbbbbrrrrrrpppppwill face more sneaky attacks
The climactic ending is near...
You can't go wrong with Jimmy-san
What an amazing character
He was particularly great this year
We mentioned this before but,
what was up with your costume change ?
It had nothing to do with the program
Maybe a spin-off ?
Your costume was the reason for a lot of my beatings
But as the costume wearer, you didn't get any butt slaps
Well, no, I got my share of slaps
No, not really
It's your fault for wearing that thong
What's wrong with wearing a thong ?
You have one on today, too ?
Today...?   Yes
So you're serious
But why ?
Well, it makes my butt look nice
And who are you trying to impress ?
So you're into anything "beautiful"
Yes, "beautiful"
The "Beauty" of things
Yes, the "Beauty"
You're just repeating whatever I say !!
Taking extreme measures in the hotel business
even at midnight
An End-of-the-Year Party is being held right now
I thought we should show our faces
Shall we ?
I don't get it
Who are these party goers
the men have been assigned to serve?
What kind of people start a party at midnight ?
Go ahead and sit in order
This will be a fun night
We long for this night every year
Here we are, the "Hand Towel" group, for our year end party
Hand-Towel Group
Hiroiki Ariyoshi
To start the occasion, let's hear from our chairman
Yes
Chairman !
Hand-Towel Group Chairman
Ryuhei Ueshima
I'd like to make a toast to our group
for making great strides this year
Of course, this couldn't have been possible without all of you
Cheers !
Kanpai !!
Without further adieu,
Let us being our annual gift exchange !
What can I get this year ?
OK, here's the first gift
It's called the "Firefly Set"
Who brought this "Firefly Set" ??
I did
Oh, you did ?
What's a "Firefly Set" all about ?
Hand-Towel Group
Nozomu Iwao
All you do is place it on your butt
and you can transform into a Firefly
I want it~ !!
I definitely want this
OK, let me pick the winning raffle ticket
Give it to me
Pick me
Shitara !
Hand-Towel Group
Osamu Shitara
I'm jealous
You're lucky
I got it ?
If you would lie down in the middle of the room
FIREFLY SETvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv
Light the flammable object on one's butt
to create a firefly !
That's cute
This is it
See, it's this easy
What do you do know ?
Is this OK...?
Here we go
I'm so jealous
Light it up
Yeah, firefly !
Chairman, your turn !
I can try this, too ?
A Firefly for the Chairman
Can you set me up then ?
If you don't mind
It sure looked great
Set it up under his underwear !
How's this ?
Here we go !
Here it is, Chairman
It got lit
Splash him
Yes, it did
That felt awesome !
*The fire self-extinguished and the Chairman's butt is OK
That stinks !
I smell something burnt
I'm glad you got to do it, Chairman
Was it pretty ?
Yes, it was
Very pretty
We're fortunate to catch a firefly this time of the year
Let's get going
The second gift is the "Stag Beetle Piercing"
Who picked this ?
That's me
Oh, this was yours ?
Hand-Towel Group
Toshiaki Kasuga
You'll make a great fashion statement
by using a real beetle as an earring
C'mon, pick me
Please, pick me
Please, let me have this
Hey, this is me !
Yeah, that's you
Is this rigged ?
STAG BEETLE EARRINGvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv
A real beetle earring
Check this out
Look, it's ready to pinch
I feel bad you guys don't get to do this
Don't worry about it
You won the prize
Here we go
Start the piercing!!
Are you nervous ?
Here it is
Clamp
How is it ?
You look fashionable
Pretty ! Pretty !
That's a nice gift
That's definitely suits you
I see a red dot
I want something, too
"Hair-Removal Bowling Set"
And who brought this ?
That's me
This was your idea ?
This set removes your unwanted hair with a bowling ball
I HAVE to win this
I'm serious
I really want to do this
Here we go
Iwao !
Yeah,
See, I have too much chest hair
What perfect timing
HAIR-REMOVAL BOWLING SETvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv
The rolling of a bowling ball
removes your unwanted hair
Good job
That'll be awesome
That's a reputable brand, too
Application of Super-Adhesive Tape
Here we go
Well done
You can't get that done at a real salon
Should we move on ?
The 4th gift is called...
"Face Reduction & Suck up Bra"
This kit shrinks your face and enlarges your breasts at the same time
Hand-Towel Group
Toshifumi Fujimoto
That sounds good
Hand-Towel Group
Yuki Himura
I'm envious
Suck-up Bravvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv
Enlarges the breasts with a vacuum
Look at that
It's working already
Go for the other one, too ?
Alright
Not quite done yet
You can do better
That's cute
Let's move on to your head
It'll make your head smaller
Face Reduction Maskvvvvvvvvvvvvv
Makes one's head smaller with a balloon blown up inside the mask
And...
Here it is
What do you do with that ?
Are you ready ?
Blow in Air
Looking good
So far, so good
That's scary
It worked !
It made your head smaller !
Technical Difficulties !?
How's that bra ?
You can't get them off
That's gotta hurt
What's with this bra ?
It's turning purple
I can't get the cup off
Put some air in it
Fujimon, blow it, blow on it
How can I get this off ??
What should I do ?
How do I.....?
What can I do with it ?
Put some air in it
Purple, they're turning purple
How do I get them off ?
Like this ?
Pull the pin out first
Pull this pin out ?
How ?
Pull that green thing out
Looking good
Why is he struggling with this ?
Ah, I see
He's got it
Thank God
That one's still stuck
That ain't gonna do it
What the hell are you doing ?!
That's enough !
What a relief !
That was good after all
Here's the fifth gift
"Beer Mug Full of Crushed Mints"
I brought that one
What exactly is it ?
You get to drink ground up mint powder in a beer mug
to freshen up
That sounds refreshing
Yeah, it does
I've always wanted to try that
Chairman~ !!
Yes !
I'm so ready
How are you always so lucky ?
BEER MUG FULL OF CRUSHED MINTS@@@@@
Ground up mints (50 boxes worth) in a glass
Here it is
Just down it
Ok, then, here's to you all
Better have some water
Down it
Chairman ?
He's shaking
He's freezing cold, freezing cold
Wow, the smell is overwhelming
Are you OK ?
Awesome !
Man, that mint smell is something else
I could go for a couple of more
of those drinks
Are you serious ?
But on second thought,
I think I'm done for today
Yes, really
You OK ?
I'm OK, why don't we move on ?
Next up is
"Sexy Space Travel"
What is that ?
That's mine
I got a travel voucher for sexy space traveling
Yeah !
This is one amazing gift
I'm going
I'm definitely going
How do you do this ?
There's a bottle rocket already set up outside
Bottle already setup outside
Do I sit ?
No just stay like that and
So it is recommended
that the launching should be from the center of the body
Sexy Space TravelOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
Plastic Bottle takes off while attached to your balls by a string
Now you're set for space travel
Join me for the countdown
Take Off
Take off
That was awesome
Ouch, ouch, ouch
Apparently, it missed its ride
Isn't he checking it out ?
I'm OK, I'm OK, I'm OK
But you shouldn't look at it
Seriously, I wouldn't want you to look
Really, it doesn't look bad
What do you say,
we head back ?
Why so soon ?
Thank you very much
Thank you
Happy New Year
At 5:00am,
It's time for a special assignment
Listen guys,
It's time for our annual
"Do not be scared" segment
Here we go
This is an annual event now ?
Special Rule for the Night
"Don't be scared - Hotel Man"
Five members transition to the 3rd Floor of the Main Building
"Don't be scared" - What is their task ??
Today marks the day of our original owner's passing
And as new hotel men,
I ask you to bring the offering bowl
from the basement
to the statue on the ground level
Member's Route: Basement to the Statue on the ground level
What kind of tricks await them ?!
This is the first time we've gone together
Let's go
Just follow the directions
Tanaka, why don't you lead us ?
All the lighting has been changed
You'd do better with all of us together, right ?
Countdown to the
CO2 Gas release
Yeah, I'll be OK
Tanaka, since you're the tallest...
That scared me...
That hurt my heart just now
Tanaka, lead us !
You know you'll be falling on your butt
you'll be safer in the front
At Elevator
Ah, ah
Excuse me, but...
Keep your voice down,
KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN !
We're going down, right ?
Yes, I believe so
Seriously, no yelling
Countdown to the
"secret" trap
Hit the LOBBY button ?
Going down to the basement, right ?
Kuidaore (Gluttony) Doll (Height 145cm)
That was scary
Seriously scary
It was seriously scary
Countdown to "Secret" trap
Kuidaore (Gluttony) Doll (Height 2m)
This isn't OK
Not good
You can't fit in here
She's staring at me
A serious stare
At Elevator
Here we are
Why ? Why ? Why ?
Oh, we need to go to the basement
But we're at the lobby
Get off here then ?
Countdown to "Takasu Clinic"
This isn't easy to get out
Ah, let's go this way then
What the hell is she babbling ?
Wasn't that                    really freaky ??
Yes, really creepy
I thought she was gone, and then I saw she was staring at me
It almost made my heart stop
Tanaka, get to the front
And I'll follow all of you guys
Are we ready ?
Stairwell
Someone's there
There's someone in there
Is that Sandwich Man duo?
Sandwich Man in the midst of a skit meeting
No Face
What are they doing here, damn it
That's scary
I see they wanted to get us bad
Really bad
I know, I know
Countdown to "secret" trap
Who's that ?
I'm Konaki Jiji
Seiji "Konaki Jiji"
He's not even scary
Should we beat him up ?
For real
I'm Konaki Jiji
You're not scary
I know you're Seiji
This is your usual attire
Basement
What do we do in the basement ?
We're supposed to get the offering
and bring it from the basement to the ground level ?
How does he expect us to remember everything
after he only told us once
Door
Countdown to "secret" trap
What, what ?
That's one crazy looking thing
That's freaky
It's moving fast and stuff
Will you look at it ?
That is one scary thing
This guy should be protecting a bunch of eggs or something
Taro Yabu "Exorcist"
You gotta be kiddin'
Don't be freaky
We got it now, Yabu-chan
We've seen enough
OK, OK, OK, OK
Yabu-chan, that's enough
Yabu-chan, Sit !!
Basement
Woh, this is way too scary !
Tanaka !
Zaki-san, could you just go ahead and...
And what are we supposed to do ?
Will you go over there and check ?
Try not to knock anything down and get hurt
Countdown to
"Air to Feet"
He's hit again !
He's down
Get up, Tanaka
Of course, we'd had enough of you at this point
What now, Tanaka ?
Go that way !
I'm hating this
We're all hating this
Countdown to
"air to feet" (again)
Let's hurry up
We can do this as a team
Seriously, my heart is in pain
Tanaka, get up !
What's your problem ?
I see, we can turn right here
Countdown to a "secret" trap
Ah, this way, this way
Chair, I see chairs
A mysterious MC appears
What is this ?
Siren
Something's moving !
What ? What ? What ? What ? What ? What ?
What ? What ? What ? What ? What ?
The machinery activates
What's wrong with you guys !!
That thing just started moving !
Yeah, I saw it, too
Scary Entertainment Opening
Thank you
W Engine
This is a story about a homely doctor falling for his patient
And here's the girl after the operation
Doctor Kawai
Doctor
Akiko-chan, you need to stay in your room
Don't worry, because of you, I'm already full of energy
I can even do this
Ouch, that hurts
I'll miss you after I'm discharged from this hospital
Don't be silly
Now let me go get your chart
I'll be right back
OK
How do I not fall for her ??!!
This is a story of an introverted man falling for an extroverted woman,
similar to the story between Yokota Jaguar and Mr. Kinoshita
Doctor ?
Yes ?
I need to talk to you about something
Sorry, I have to take this call
Hello ?
Oh, Akiko-chan is here with me
What ?
Akiko-chan is dead ?
The operation didn't go well ??
But Akiko-chan is......
I'm taking you with me !
All of you guys, be careful !!
Thank you very much
You're watching another infomercial
Beauty Kokubu
And here's what you can order tonight !
It's a 47 inch high-definition TV
The picture quality is so clear
and check out its stylish body !!
And that's not all
I'm throwing in a Blue-Ray disk player
as well as this set of speakers
with a TV stand
You just pay one price for all four items
You can't get this deal anywhere else
but here
Now, how much would you pay for this ?
Countdown to a "secret" trap
Well, you'll have to find out in tomorrow's morning paper
Air from his hands
Grabs his feet
Wait !
WAIT !!
What's going on ?
That was insane
Wait a minute
That sucked
That guy had my feet the whole time
He had my feet
I was freakin' scared !!
I didn't know what you meant
That sucked
I see another entrance
I'm sure we have to go in there
Go ahead
I see an arrow
What is this, Hamada-san ??
Who are you trying to be ??
Enter this way
Man, I see another door
This is taking too long
Tanaka, will you go, please
It's the scariest when I have to open (a door)
Countdown to the "Intro Music"
Oh, I see it's over there
Offering
What does that say ?
Take this offering
It says "Take this offering"
Oh yes, we need to take that to the ground level
What's this mean ?
Do I have to take this sign ?
No, no
It means you have to take that offering with that plate
Countdown to the CO2 Gas release
Take the whole bowl of fruits
What the ......
All the Characters Arrive !!
I can't keep going like this
I just saw bunch of them
A whole bunch
What is this ? What is this ?
Matsumoto kept pushing me just now
I can't hold this
You know I'm going to drop them all !
I just saw all the scary characters coming at us
I'm suffering
I'm suffering !
I got a headache
This is impossible
The odds are against me
And I'm suffering
I'm suffering
You'll be fine
I'm really suffering !
It's light outside
Basement      Ground level
That was scary
Matsumoto wasn't shy about pushing me around
"Get on the cart"
You would've done the same
I was so scared
We all gotta get on this cart
It's so bright outside
We don't need this flashlight anymore
Get on it quickly
Let's go
Drive to the Grounds
Here comes something
Here comes the Jiang Shi !!
Is this the same girl we saw in the elevator ?
She must be the same girl
It's getting cold
Yeah, it's cold
Here we are
Don't forget to bring the offering
Countdown to a "secret" trap
Yes
I see an arrow
So we meet again
Yutaro emerges from a pile of leaves
How annoying is that guy ?
Tanaka, you've dropped too much fruit
Forget about all the grapes !
Wow, amazing
Is that it ?
The monument
I've got a bad feeling about this
Me too
Something's really freaky about this
I say don't stray from the cones
Definitely not
Tanaka, since you've got the offering......
Man, the banana's smushed
What's here anyhow ?
Over there ?
What a long walk
We've passed the point of no return
Why don't you go put that bowl over there ?
Yeah, in the opening underneath
Yeah, right there
Please accept our offering
Let's go back
Countdown to a "secret" trap
That should do it
Hattori Militia + Series of Huge Explosions
I felt the heat
Who fell down there ?
Tanaka, that's you again ?!
You were still falling on your ass!
Puddle
Tanaka, you're so helpless
I hate this !
It's been 21 hours since the start
We screamed so much
My voice has just about had it
We couldn't have finished without each other
Agreed
Imagine just the two of you at night ?
Sandwich Man was scary
"No Face" Sandwich Man
even though I knew who they were
That was scary
I don't like that kind of stuff
I'd say the scariest was when that guy grabbed my feet
If that happened when I was in middle-school,
I would have soiled my pants for sure
You're just laughing like nobody's business
It's been 21 hours of straight work
They have no more strength to give
Despite having no strength nor will left to spare,
one final task remains
Listen guys
There's a patron who refuses to leave the sauna room,
Could you give us a hand ?
At this hour ?
What a nutcase
Whoever refuses to leave the sauna
should be charged for a full night's stay
Before their work day is over,
the members perform their last task
Bath
What a pain in the ass
Sauna ?
Here it is
The patron's still in here
If possible, talk her out of there
Oh, man.....
Who is this ??
Excuse us
Oh God
Oh, man !
Half-Naked Ohshima from "Morisanchu"
Well.....
It's time for us to close the sauna
Could you leave now, please ?
Huh ?
It is time to close this up,
if you could please leave ?
Do you know what time it is ?
Why not give me some more time ?
Well, you look pretty tired,
I'd say you should get out of here quickly
I'm taking a nap then
Bad idea
Excuse me
Are you....a.....woman ??
You're in the men's sauna
Huh ?
Your eyes are gone, by the way
Have you been drinking ?
That's not good
Seriously, you're showing your.....
Excuse us, but your legs.....
The towel isn't even covering your breasts
Why don't you fix that a little bit ?
And your legs, close your legs
Excuse me, but you're married ?
I notice you've got a ring
And you know what ?
How does Osamu (her husband) feel about this gig ?
Her husband/writer
Osamu Suzuki
You're being a moron right now
Get outta here
You're a moron !
Get out of there
Will you guys drag her out of there ?
I don't think so
That's impossible
Tanaka, I'm volunteering you for this
I can't do this to a woman
Why don't we all help her ?
Cocorico is in charge
Ma'am, please
What do you want ?
Don't bother me
I'm not leaving
She's showing her boobs right now
Let's go
Do we have to call the cops ?
You need to be more careful
Requires 4 members after all
Yama-chan, be careful
What are you, a grand piano ?
Freakin' moron !
Let's be careful
Here we go
3, 2, 1,
Don't lose your towel
You have more issues than water in your ears
You need to get your priorities straight
I've had enough !
Damn you !
Moron !
You're a freakin' moron
Shall we go ?
Good job, guys
Please, go straight home
It's been 24 hours since the start
Having worked 24 hours straight without any sleep,
they have no remaining physical or mental strength
But this is the moment they've been waiting for
You all did a good job
Now you are all graduates of
Gasu Kurobikari Princess Hotel
Congratulations
We did it !
How was it, Endo ?
There were many hurdles
but it was overall a good experience
How about you, Tanaka ?
This was the toughest one yet,
but I feel like we did great as a team
Yamasaki ?
It's been a long time since I've stayed up all night
Hamada ?
Ah !
Thank you very much
Can't you talk normal ?
You were doing a character
Thank you
Thank you very much
Matsumoto !
He just said his
We never got into the rhythm
Shall we go ?
Finally
24 hours
This one was the most tiring
I guess it's the new year now
OK, this is where I'm saying bye
Bye
It's cold
There's nothing to worry about ~ !!
Happy New Year
Hotel Owner
Kenji Suga
I am the future owner of this hotel
I'm still in 9th grade
anyways, you all did great
You're a 9th grader ?
9th grade ?
I'll be following my father's footsteps
You gotta stop eating so much
Thank you very much
Again, I'd like to thank all of you
And especially Yamasaki-san,
I know your days as a comic are numbered this year
But the rest of you,
There's nothing to worry about ~ !
Suga-san did great job finishing this series
It gets my back more than anything
Butt-Slap Counter
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
Naoki Tanaka
Hosei Yamasaki
Shozo Endo
Incredible
On your way to the bus,
Single bed
was when you realized what was about to happen
It had been a year since the last slap
Sharan Q
And you had forgotten about the pain in your ass
Right off the bat, you got a beating from Chono
which made all of your hearts sink
And you laughed at Daichi
then laughed some more at Matsuko
Both of which led to more butt-slappings
As if using Chiaki
to get laughs wasn't enough anymore
You brought in Natsumi
which made Hamada uneasy
Heipo, in a single bed room,
can only scream by himself
No matter how stupid the gags were,
all of you still managed to laugh
The song sung by Masako
has not changed since your youth
Why did she agree to do this show,
when she could make tons of money on other shows ?
Ueshima, the chairman of "Hand-Towel" group
Who's that receptionist ?
It's her, Bibari
Nice stare-down,
Taxi driver: Devi
The Kano Sisters swing their breasts
Unlike his brother Shozo,
little brother got laughs wearing tighty whities
Despite an orthodox gag by Takeuchi
Hitoshi still loved it
Anna's mother didn't disappoint
with her shaky acting chops
What was meant to be simple filler
resulted in an unexpected expression of victory
If you could go back,
you wouldn't have laughed this much
Your life as a single man has ended
with a newborn daughter in your life
We kept the stupidity rolling
and laughed as a team
The last gag
I had no idea Tanaka fell right then
ended with Oshima's nudity
If there's no complaint calls
Yoshinobu won't be happy
Happy New Year
We wish you a year full of laughter
That's it
As is the case every year,
Matsumoto-san got the most slaps
That was a tough day
We didn't get to sleep at all
It was serious business
You know what though ?
You get so jumpy at night
Hear me out
That guy was supposed to grab each of our legs
but he got both of my legs instead
Of course, I was scared !!
I couldn't escape !
I was scared of not having control over my feet
I was trapped
I have to apologize that we ended with the sauna scene
The ending song even mentioned something about receiving complaint calls
Oshima did that to herself,
and I'm not responsible at all
That wasn't part of the deal
She went ahead and took her clothes off, right ?
Next year, we should have ARASHI take over for us
*ARASHI is a popular boy band
I see the new year has already arrived
Happy New Year
Thank you for continuing to support Gaki No Tuskai
Thank you