Translation Team:
ShibataBread
www.shibatabread.com
Alex
Alex2000@home.nl
Zurui
http://zurui.blogspot.com/
Mrs. ShibataBread
@tofupizza on twitter
Dere-kun
http://www.elgngaming.net/
Repressing Emotions Can Result In
Wild Spread of Character Deterioration
Gaki No Tsukai, Over-the-Top Series!!
"No Laughing - Spy"
Apologize, you asshole!
No!!
Assassins Target the Gaki Members
And Famous Celebrities Await Them
Nothing Is Off Limits
A Perfectly Matched Debate
How is that a fair game??
A Game of Tag
Don't get caught
The Tag Game is Back
This isn't good
Shivering In Terror
So do the shrieking cries
As the game intensifies
Give me a break!!
The Cast's Challenge Will Monopolize the Airwaves!!
6-Hour Special Edition!!
Gaki No Tsukai New Year's Eve Special Event
Downtown Presents:
Gaki No Tsukai
Ya Arahende!!
No Laughing
Spy 24 Hours
Downtown
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
We're back
Yes, once again
Hosei Yamasaki
we'll be welcoming New Year's Day
Cocorico
Naoki Tanaka
Shozo Endou
with another "No Laughing" series
I was really hoping *ARASHI would do the show this year but...
*ARASHI = 5-member Boy Band
But they chickened out on us
No, ARASHI took the gig at NHK
That's right
Well, our version of ARASHI can do the job then
We're the ARASHI of Yoshimoto Co.
We're like IGARASHI
50 times better than ARASHI
This year's theme is "Spy"
Why do we have be spies anyway?
And who says spies can't laugh?
It was a tough day as usual
And that weather...
It was wet and cold like every other year
One of us must be inviting the rain
Yeah, you need to knock it off!
Hosei-san, it's you
No, I bring sunny days!
I don't believe it
I'm guessing it's you, Hamada-san
Why me?
Right, why is it Hamada's fault that it always rains?!
Seriously, why me?
OK, hear me out then
Go ahead
Well, I saw an ad for your coffee on a vending machine
And your face with the blue background shows
you're the type who brings rain!
Horrible
I don't get it
Apologize!!
That's you
Where's your neck?
I am sorry
Matsumoto-san, why don't we start the show?
Please, set us up
Look towards camera No.4!!
That one!!
You were all over the place
Starting Day
The morning begins with rain
The morning of filming
almost as if to spite the cast
...And you ended up with the most slaps out of all of us
I don't understand anything you're saying
Despite the lousy weather, they are in their usual good spirits
I'm feeling that familiar vibe
Man, I wish Shoji-san would show up and be done with it
Shoji Murakami
He can do his "Ninja School" skit for 30 minutes
There it is again
It says "Wait here"
The initial setup hasn't changed
How cold is it right now?
I'd say it's 0 degrees
I'd say it's below 10 degrees
Bump
It is really cold
What?
Why move like that?
I can see your underwear
Look, he can't get out of it
AH!!
That's one funny looking face
You manage to make it look funnier every year
You've done it again this year
Former Downtown Manager
Hiroshi Fujiwara
Right when you came out and said,"AH!"
I heard the crow cry out
Am I right?
Yes, it did
You had no idea where I was, huh?
Could you guys line up here?
Lined up already
We're already in line
We're lined up
Of course, we are
You still don't know how to improvise
You didn't see we were already lined up?
Didn't the script say "Unless they're already lined up"??
with an asterisk *??
This year, you're going to be spies
"Being a Spy" doesn't quite ring a bell
No, it doesn't
As a newly hired spy, you will...
you will be going through some rigorous training
Kaw
Could you please string your sentences together?
Yeah, the crow's got you beat
Five Newly Hired Spies
About to take on 24-hours of training!!
And what are you supposed to be?
I'm a hot spy
Look at him laughing at himself
That's hilarious
Yamasaki!
What do spy...
What do spies and traffic rules have in common?
I'd like an answer
He would like an answer
Why don't you just look it up?
You give me an answer
Question
What do Spies and Traffic rules have in common?
What do Spice and...?
Why Spice?
Who the hell is becoming a Spice today?
OK, so what do those two things share?
Well, they're both hot
as in Spice..
We told you we're "Spies"!!
You're a Spy
That's our theme this year
Never mind then
That's it??
And your clothes--how dare you wear that when you're spies!?
I have your uniforms over there
Let's have you get changed
Prior to spy training
Change Into a Proper Uniform
Why do we have to change outside?
How's it going?
You ready to come out?
Come out when I call your name
Hamada!
Not bad
Excellent Fat-Lipped Spy
You're just like James Bond
That's nice of you to say,
thanks
Matsumoto!
Shrewd Pops Spy
007 has got nothing on you
I'm better than that guy?
Of course, I am
Endou!
You've got the "Mission:Impossible" thing going there
Handsome Divorced Spy
Thank you very much
He's got an assortment of comments this year
Right, they're all different
Tanaka!
You resemble a foreign actor--like Tom Cruise
Filthy Brainiac Spy
Yamasaki!
Talentless and Wussy Spy
Your pants seem a bit tight on you
Yes, they're a bit tight
They're short, too
They feel a little snug
Go ahead and line up over here
No Comment for Yamasaki
Here are the rules!!
First
1st Rule: You Will Be Trained as Spies for the Next 24 Hours
2nd Rule:      You Are Not to Laugh During the Next 24 Hours
3rd Rule:    If Caught Laughing, You Will Be Punished
That's all
Did you get all that?
Well...
Yes, we got it
I don't get it
And I don't wanna do it!!
There he goes again
First!
You're not to laugh under any circumstance
You need some serious help with your improv skills
You can never veer from the script, can you?
Well then...
Follow me to the bus stop
Shall we?
Here we go with the bus again
We're riding a bus again?
Let's go
Why are we going by bus?
I wanted James Bond's car
It's gonna be a long ride
Why bus?
Follow me across the street
He's like, "Follow me across the street"
Man, this is gonna be a long day
Here comes the bus!
Here it comes
Here it is
How come spies have to ride the bus?
I demand an explanation
Indeed
Couldn't you have chartered something cooler than this?
Did the bus need to be this flashy?
Come take a look, guys
Check it out
This bus goes to the Gasu Kurobikari Intelligence Agency
Or G.I.A. for short
Black Falcon
The black falcon emblem is all over the bus
Specifically Designed for Spies
I didn't know about that
It's not like we looked at the back of the bus
Hamada, pretty cool, isn't it?
This bus makes no secrets
Right, not very secretive at all
The name of the city is no secret either
Sodegaura
Pretty cool, huh?
Well, I guess it's pretty cool
It must be cool if Hamada says so
Shall we get on then?
The game starts once you board the bus
The moment has finally arrived!
We're in this for 24 hours
No-Laughing for 24 Hours as Spies
START
Are they REALLY agents or other laugh traps...
Other G.I.A. Agents Already on Board
I thought the same thing...
They've kind of got me worried...
Having to face the door is really annoying
I hate being right in front of it
Actually, I say Hamada has laughed already
Yeah, he laughed
You were smiling, right!?
The game has started
Well, because we're starting and all...
This year they're going to be cracking down
on people for things like "Smiling"
Even that's a "Smile"
This isn't a smile, is it?
And Endo is looking over here "smiling", too
Speaking of which, even I'M "smiling" now
Well, that isn't good either
That was good!
You are really dirty!!
Great way to start off
He's Here,
He's Here, He's Here,
He's Here, He's Here, He's Here!
Scary!
You set me up
4th Rule: Receive Your Spanking from the Black Army Corp.
We're screwed! That's freaking scary!
Could you cut that out?
And could you hit more gently?!
This is bad!
A bug would have died from that hit
Hehe...
You better cut that out
I don't see me laughing at this point
Comrades Suddenly Gang Up on Each Other
Would you give it a rest!?
This was epic!
This is bad!
Ooh! That must've hurt!
Seriously, enough of the silly comparisons
What I say is always serious--everyone just interprets it wrong...
Hey, my fly is open!
You laughed out hard!
This hasn't gotten us anywhere at all!
I didn't do that on purpose!
Not my fault
This guy's been laughing too!
Let's get going!
Depart, please!!
New Spies Bound for GIA Headquarters by Bus!!
What kind of day is ahead of them?
Fujiwara's face is just...
Just don't even go there...
You're free to look at him on your own time, but...
it'd be better if you didn't try to get me to laugh
Laughter Being Completely Unforgivable
Tension Builds as They Try to Suppress It
Yama-chan, you were smirking
Pu fu fu fu
Pu Ha ha ha hah...
Kintarou: Strong, Bold child from Japanese Folklore (more info at shibatabread.com)
Kintarou Crosses the Street
The timing of his appearance was horrible...
His size is what got me
Who is that?
First time seeing him!!
Who?
Really puny, isn't he!!
He's so slow
I thought it was the Grandma, but I guess I was wrong
Aforementioned Grandma
That's definitely not the Grandma I know...
I can't tell unless I see his face
We couldn't figure out who he was
It's the broa~d axe bea~ring Kintaro~u!
Who?
Really puny, isn't he!!
I can't tell unless I see his face
We couldn't figure out who he was
It's the broa~d axe bea~ring Kintaro~u!
It's Meira-san!!
Meira Yoshikazu
Kintarou
Argh~!!!!!
He's got such a great voice!
Man, I'm getting enough spankings
This is unbelievably painful
He sure can sing
His voice is top notch
Wait, the bear..
Um, the bear is moving on its own...
The bear is still going!
You better go stop the bear...
Who wouldn't laugh at that?!!
Don't look, don't look at the bear
Just that bear moving can get us OUT
Dangit, Yamasaki!
You don't need to say things like that!!
I'm a strong boy!
See for yourself!
"Kappa" Boards the Bus
Kappa: mischievous water creatures good at sumo wrestling (more info at shibatabread.com)
Get a hold of yourselves!
Yeah, let's face these pranks one at a time!
And the bear is still roaming around...
That bear is dangerous! So very dangerous!!
The bear could get hit by a car
First off, let's stop the bear
Hey!! Kappa-kun
You shouldn't come out into the human world!
Since it's come to this...
if you lose a sumo match to me
you have to return to the river!!
Kintarou vs. Kappa Showdown
Why on a bus?
Ready!Go!
Ready! Go!
Keep Going! Keep Going!...
I just saw something I didn't need to see
That's just too funny...
I was spared
You were called OUT right!?
Return home safely!
See ya!
It's the broa~d axe bea~ring Kintaro~u!
Folkloric commands used by horsemen to control horses.
Comparable to "Mush!" in English
Hai shi doudou! Hai doudou!
He's got an amazing voice!
Ah, he's over there!
Hai shi doudou! Hai doudou!
Couldn't they present the pranks one by one!?
20 Minutes from Commencement
Argh, there's more people out there
You don't need to tell me that
Stops at Bus Stop
Meikun High School Baseball Team
Boy, today's practice was tiring!
Sato Kajiro
Iwaki
Tanaka Yoji
Tonoma
Don't be like that--just focus on the good times
Even though they already laughed, please enjoy this skit without interruption
and we'll give our all together!
What's the matter, Satonaka?
I...
I was thinking about quitting the team
What are you talking about?
Satonaka, you are Meikun's
Ace pitcher!
It's more fun hanging out with my friends though...
Leave me be, I'm going!!
Hey, Hey, Hey!
Ace Pitcher Satonaka Quits Team
Satonaka!
Aren't you worried we might lose...?
You fool!
You idiot!! What--
What's gotten into him!?
What are we going to do!? He was our ace player!!
Ah!!
Yamada!!
That slope outside could easily send you flying!
Dokaben Deluxe!
Satonaka quit the team!
Did you see him!?
He's too huge!!
Ah!
Yamada!!
That slope outside could easily send you flying!!
Dokaben Deluxe!
Satonaka quit the team!
Did you see him!?
He's too huge!
Dokaben
Matsuko Deluxe
We need to find a replacement for Satonaka!
We won't be able to find one that easily though!!
We can't say for sure...
Yes?
He's here!!
I see a good replacement!!
Targets Endou ?
Could you stand up?
Stand up
You've definitely had experience with baseball, right?
You've DEFINITELY had experience with baseball, RIGHT!?
Yeah...
Let's play baseball together?
Right now that's a bit unreasonable...
And I'm asking you why?!!
I'm doing something else right now...
What exactly are you doing?!
What do you have to do!!
Not much you could have done, Endou
It's your fault, Endou
What?  My butt too?
Ah!!
It's them...
The Gang Starts Shooting
It's Satonaka!!
Satonaka
If that's him, we have to kill them!!
They're shooting us!!
Hey, where did they go?
Hurry, kill them!!
Shooting Starts
Satonaka
(Satonaka) is such a degenerate!!
Yamada, we have to do something!
OK
I'll be the decoy...
when they're distracted, take care of Satonaka!!
BANG
Tonouma Injured
I'd say that's more than an injury
He's dead
Tonma!
Come back!!
Tonma!  Come back!!
Bastard!
Satonaka runs away
He's so bad
I'm gonna do it!!
Bazooka Ready
Satonaka Blown Away
Take that!
Satonaka, you bastard!
But he used to be his teammate, right?
Let's go, Tonouma!!
Your nose fell off, Tonouma!!
This is messed up!!
This is messed up!
This is crazy
The slap to my face was painful
I'm sorry
There's no reason to apologize to me
Dokaben-san
Why is he apologizing?
I'm sorry
Dokaben-san, no need to apologize
I'm sorry!!
That was scary!
Geez, what was that all about
I'm sorry!
He's still apologizing
That was messed up
30 Minutes Into the Game
Only 30 minutes have passed
Already Receiving Punishment!!
The members have already received a lot of punishment
Arrival at the GIA main office
The Long Route to the GIA Main Office...
won't be any time soon
This is a long ride!!
To be safe, we should avoid looking ahead...
Yes, that's true
Arrival at a Bus Stop
Production Crew
Umemiya  Tatsuyo
This is the big time, everyone
-Yes
Did you practice enough?
Maybe do a dry run...
Manager
Gotou Teruki (Football hour)
I'm from an office promoting impersonators
Would it be possible to show you some of our impersonations?
It doesn't matter, go for it...
Here is..
Eddie Murphy on stage!
Here's Eddie Murphy...
Yamaguchi Takafumi (EE man)
from Beverly Hills Cop 2...
As a beautiful woman in a swimsuit passes by Eddie Murphy!
From Beverly Hills Cop 2
As a beautiful woman in a swimsuit passes by Eddie Murphy
This is great! A cute girl!
Hey, my son!  This is your chance!
Gyo Gyo Gyo!!
Don't interrupt the other comics
Let him do his act
I'm doing Megumi Yasu saying "Eh" too many times
Takada Sachiko (Ume Kobachi)
[Eh] Yasumegumi (Using "Eh" a lot)
I'm told that I resemble Obake no Kyutaro because I'm dishonest
but that's not true--I'm usually always like this
Eh!
People always misunderstand me
Please believe me!
Eh!
Eh! Eh!
EH!
Gyo Gyo Gyo!
I said be quiet!
Let her do her thing
That was good, that was good
OK, next
Kajiki Maguro-kun
Kajiki Maguro kun will now imitate a rebellious Kajiki Maguro
Rebellious Kajiki Maguro (swordfish)
Hey, old hag!
Why did you turn off the A/C?
Money, give me money
Hey, Hiroki
I stole 5000 yen from my mom
Let's go eat some food!
Vvrroomm!!
Ween ween ween ween ween!!
Let's go!
Hey, hey, that's enough
You're not consistent!!
Get it right
He's not consistent
Yes, he wasn't consistent
You didn't decide on "vvrroom" or "ween"
You can throttle differently to make various noises...
But, there is no "ween"
It wasn't a tight performance
Yeah
Here's your last chance
What? That's enough already
Kajiki Maguro stuck in traffic on the freeway
Kajiki Maguro Stuck in Traffic on the Freeway
He's not performing--he's just talking
Why so much traffic...
And no place to park either
What the hell are you doing?
Don't make those kinds of comments!
I didn't know what he was doing
Yeah, I didn't know what he was doing
Give me a break
Let's go
It's almost show time
Kajiki Maguro's not moving
Excuse us
You're coming too
Gyo Gyo!!
It's not.. you know
It wasn't funny
We couldn't take it anymore
That was very long
50 minutes into the game
It was about 20 minutes
They really tried hard
We're not there yet
We're not there yet?
Just a little bit longer
We didn't do anything "Spy" related
Hamada covers his laugh with a cough
Arrival at a Bus Stop
Two Middle School Students
What?
Wow!
What is that?
Oh, look at that!!
Excited By Magazine Pin-Up Girls
They're really something else
This is torture
They're really big, huh?
Killer
They are killer
Stops at Bus Stop
She's asking for it
I can almost see them
Unbelievable
Stripper on Board
So they brought him here
Stripper
Muga Tsukaji    (Drunk Dragon)
This is incredible
Hey there, middle schoolers
I couldn't help but notice you're having some fun
But how about seeing
The real thing...
And this is how you like it?
And you like it like this, like that, like this, and like that?
Working It for the Students
And this is how you like it?
And you like it like this, like that , like this, and like that?
And you like it like this, like that, like this, and like that?
He can't even unbutton it!?
He failed to unbutton his shirt
His hands were too cold to unbutton them
And this is how you like it?
And you like it like this, like that, like this, and like that?
And this is how you like it
And you like it like this, and like...
Sis!
Yoshio!
What the hell...?
What's up with this story?
How awkward is this...?
What are you doing here anyway, sis?
You're humiliating me!
What else can I do then?
Dad doesn't work and mom just left us
Do you think I like doing this?
I'm doing this so that you can attend college!
Tell me you're still humiliated
after you see my dance one last time!
Makes no sense
She's missing the point
Hey, you dirty old men!
Here I go again!
This is how you like it?
And this is how you like it?
And you like it like this, like that, like this, and like that?
This is how you like it?
And this is how you like it?
And you like it like this, like that, like this, and like that?
What a moron!
Lotion Service
This is the sound you like?
And this is the sound you like?
And then...and...
Lotion Causes Major Slipping
You asked for that
That wasn't planned, huh?
Of course, your hands are slippery
I think that hurt him a little bit
Yoshio!
How was my dance?
That was beautiful, sis
You're the best sister anyone could ever have!
Yoshio!
A Heart Warming Ending
I'm fixing your favorite croquette tonight
Sorry my hands are sticky
So was it his sister or his brother?
I suppose she's his sister...
At least that's what she said but...
Look, they're going home happy
Good for them
That's a good sister, or brother?
I suppose she's his sister...
After a Long Ride,
the Bus Nears the GIA!!
We're almost at the GIA
What a long trip!
Yes, that was
A long trip
How come we're riding with the public?
You're right
Here, we have arrived
A Spying and Laughing Training Facility
Where the Cast Will Face a 24 Hour Challenge!
This already doesn't look good
My heart just sunk
What do you mean?
I think I just saw something I shouldn't have
I think I did, too
What are you talking about?
OK we're here
Arrival at GIA
Why don't you follow me?
This way
This is the GIA
Pretty grand, isn't it?
It is quite magnificent
Please line up over here
Line up in front of the statue
Face the statue
Here we have
what is the symbolic statue of GIA
It's the phantom...
GIA Symbol
Gasuu Black Falcon
This is...well...
This is that.....
Seriously...
You do this every year
You never fail to do this to us
What's this thing landing on?
Buttocks
It's on a butt
This black falcon is...
You know...?
This falcon was modeled after a 3rd generation Japanese
named Micky Takano who was alleged to be the first spy ever
I didn't get any of that
And Micky Takano...
Could you not make that kind of comment, please?
Why is the sculpture in the shape of an animal then?
Please keep your comments to yourself
This is modeled after Micky Takano
Impressive, huh?
Watch out, Hamada!!
Sniper Attack
Where is he?
There he is!
Ah!
Close call
Remember, your lives are always at stake
Watch youselves
Let's go then
We should not have hung around here
Line up here
Line up right here
As you enter this building,
you will be subject to a full body scan
Security Check
Full Body Scan Required to Prevent Bio-terrorist Attacks
to make sure you're not infected with any dangerous viruses
Tanaka
You ready?
Stand on the footprints, and the machine will engage
"Should" engage?
Tanaka
Go right ahead
How about "It'll automatically engage?"
I had to point that out
"Should" engage is not OK by me
I understand but...
Let's go, Tanaka
It's a little scary
Nobody likes to be startled
I'm scared
Virus check complete
The subject is clear
Entrance granted
You're OK, Tanaka
I'm good, thank God
Hamada, you're up
Puu
Shouldn't the farting affect the outcome?
He might get a false positive
Virus scan complete
Subject is clear
Entrance granted
Endo, you're next
I don't wanna be last...
Virus has been detected
I knew it'd be Endo
Entrance Denied
Virus Disenfection Complete
Endou should be cleared of all viruses
No way!
Could you let me enter already?
Virus Check Clear
Matsumoto safely clears the virus check
But then there was Yamazaki...
Active virus found! Active virus found!
Virus Disinfectant Spray
With that over, we can have peace of mind
Fujiwara Enters Without Being Checked
Pfffh
Could I have you look at this...
It's the GIA reception desk
Reception Desk
That's just messed up
Huh,
Hmm, the receptionist doesn't seem to be here...
Argh, this again?
Huh?
Huh? The receptionist isn't here...
How many times are they going to...
Pretty cool
Receptionist
Rino Katase
This isn't alright
She just smiled at me
Ooh! That hurt!
Hello, Fujiwara-san
Good morning, ma'am
Thank you for coming
This is GIA's lovely receptionist, Rino-san
And who would these gentlemen be?
These bums are new spies in training
They're all pleased to meet your acquaintance
It's a pleasure meeting you all
Your name, my good sir?
Ah, my name is Matsumoto
And are you married?
Yes, I have a beautiful wife
Any children?
Yeah, I have one child.
You must be working hard then
Yes...
By the way,
I'm thinking about cooking dinner
for a person who's really close to my heart
What would you suggest that I cook?
Gee, what would be good?
Well...
Something like a meat and potato stew...
A nice family-orientated meal,but...
A nice family-orientated meal, but...
His taste for food
is not very sophisticated
How about a hamburger!
How does that sound?
How about a Hamburger?
What did you just say?!
You said "Hamburger"!?
Are you asking me to smack you upside the head?
The Receptionist Loses Her Marbles
My brother's 20-year jail term is up
and you recommend hamburgers
covered with demi-glaze sauce!?
The day I offer something that foul,
is the day every member of my family gets killed!!
You dumbass!!
Receptionist Has Yakuza Affiliations
What is her problem?
Oh the pain, that must've hurt!
He got you good
Hello, and your name is?
I'm Yamasaki
My friend's son is getting married and...
and I was asked to sing a song at the reception
What's the perfect wedding song?
Well, you can't go wrong with
"Tentou Mushi no Samba" (The Ladybug's Samba)
How does that go?
You and I in our dream land,
A small church in the grove was where we had our wedding...
Uh, Wh-wha-what?
Grove? Say that again
In a small church down by the grove,
was where we had our wedding party
Uh, What kind of church?
Uhm...
A small church down by the grove,
was where we had our wedding party...
What was THAT?
It's at a SMALL church!?
DUMBASS!
This party is...
so huge that 800 members from
Osaka to Himeji will attend
What is she talking about!?
And you're suggesting that
I sing a song about a reception at a "small" church?!
I would be killed, of course
Think about this
could 800 people fit into a SMALL church?
DUMBASS!
This is really exhausting
My, oh my!
What a menacing attitude we've got here.
Who are you!?
Mineko Nishikawa
Big sis, if you want to stay young
Receptionist
Even though the members have already laughed, please enjoy this skit without interruption
stop letting things get to you all the time
What was that!?
Amazing cast..
I happen to think a "small church down by the grove"
is lovely
Since when are you such a hot-shot,
showing up right now like this
Oh, I'm so scared
This doesn't change the fact that your husband
doesn't have any balls
Sounds to me like you're asking for it
You wish!
Is that so?
Then prepare for the worst!
Woah, Woah, Woah, Hey, Hey, Hey!!
Happy Boy
Okada Masuda
WoOAOoW!
That's his only line
What the heck is with him!?
I don't get him at all
Could we just chill, chill, chill, chill!
Oh and it comes out!
Oh, hang on a second
Excuse me as I go to the front
Oh my, oh my,
You're Hijese-san, no, that's not it
She's Udese-san, no I'm still off
I got it! She's Katase-san,
WoOAOoW!!
And in this corner,
Nishikawa-san!!
That was quick!
And I'm just as quick in the bedroom
WoOAOoW!
Okada OUT!
OUCH!
He sure is loud
Thank you!  Thank you so very much
Ok, Ok, Ok, Here we go
Shall we have a Sumo match?
Ready!?
Fight!
Keep Going! Keep Going! Keep Go~ing!
And I want to keep going in show business!
WoOAOoW!
Happy Bo~y!
SHUT THE HELL UP AND DIE!
I'm slowly dy....
I'm falling like a leaf!
Happy Boy Killed in the Line of Duty
You guys wanna get shot, too?
Wrong place at the wrong time
Let's go
I'm fine with being OUT
Happy Boy bit the bullet
Happy Boy was killed
Yeah, he was shot...
Pretty amazing reception though
So Happy Boy is dead
I was his fan
This way!
We're going down again!?
We're on our way to meet with the Director
Everyone, be on your best behavior!
Director's Office
Excuse us!
The order goes Matsumoto, Hamada, Endou, Tanaka, Yamasaki
Per your request, sir, I'm here with the new spies
Director
Nakamura Masatoshi
Per your request, sir, I'm here with new spies
Director
Masatoshi Nakamura
Is this for real!?
So you are the new spies
And I am...
I am Nakamura, GIA's Director
Pleased to meet you
Pleased to be working under you!
Welcome
Nice and close
Nice to meet you
Pleasure's all mine
Is Yamasaki getting ignored again?
In previous batsu games, Yamasaki gets ignored when first greeted by the boss
Will Yamasaki get ignored again?
I expected a prank here
Will Yamasaki get ignored again this year??
That's so bad, right!
That's just mean!
Yamazaki Punched in the Stomach
I didn't expect that
That's must have hurt
That was really messed up!
I thought he would just
ignore him
I wasn't expecting
that to happen
And he also got his butt slapped
He got hit twice
That's not good
A spy needs a code name,
so he can keep his secret identity
So on your behalf...
I'll assign a code name to each of you
Code Name Assignments
Let's see...
Your name?
It's Matsumoto
Your first name?
Hitoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi?
Yes
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Let me see...
"Kobonnou" (Doting parent)
Your expression says a lot
This building is very secure, so you will need a password
Matsumoto will be "883"
"Papa-san"
Pa(8)pa(8) San(3)
Ok, next...
Hamada-kun
Yes
Oops, how did I already know who you were?!!
I just said it, didn't I?
He said it himself!
I'm Hamada
What's your first name?
Masatoshi
Masatoshi?
Really?  Masatoshi is your real name?
Yes
Wow, that's a great name. Same as mine!
For such a good name... let's see...
Your code name is..."Busaiku"(Ugly)
It didn't matter
what my name was
Oh, yes, your password...
"723"
Seven hundred and twenty three
"Natsumi"
Na(7)tsu(2)mi(3) (wife's name)
We should get slapped for
sticking out our tongues
Yes, we're hiding our laughter
And your name is?
Endou Shozo
Your code name..."Dohentai" (Super perverted)
Your password is "168"
"Iroha"
I(1)ro(6)ha(8)
Endo's daughter
Next, your name?
Tanaka
Your first name is?
Naoki
Tanaka Naoki
Ok, your code name is..."Naoki"
Ok, your password...
"931"
Ku(9)sa(3)i(1) (Stink)
You'll never be anything but that
And your name is?
Yamasaki
Your first name?
Hosei
Ok, let's think of a code name...
"Makiguso-Taro" (Rolling Shit Taro)
Where did he get that?
Yeah, Makiguso-Taro
He didn't like you at all
No, he didn't
Ok, your password...
"361"
Sa(3)mu(6)i(1) (No talent)
Look at his expression
Yeah, he should've
punched him again
Before I forget
I need to hand out your IDs
This is yours, Yamasaki
And yours...
Hamada-kun
Matsumoto
and here is yours
Picture: Jiro Todoroki
This isn't me...
It kinda looked like you
This is... not me
Wrong photo
Sir...
This is not me
The photo is...
I think it's a mistake
It's not a mistake
Look,
Everyone, come and see
It's him, right?
It is, right?
It's not
It is right?
It is right!!  Look!!
Right?!
Yes, sir
Right, that's him
Yes it's him
What's wrong with you?
But this is a photo of...
It's you!
It's Jiro Todoroki
Who?
It's you
Isn't this Jiro Todoroki's picture?
It's you, right?
Ok, I'm sorry, I'll take it
I would usually end our meeting now,
but I have something private to talk about
Actually, I have to perform at a New Year's party
I want you to watch me practice and give me some feedback
Ok!  Please come in!
Actually, I have to perform at a New Year's party
I want you to watch me practice and give me some feedback
Ok! Please come in!
Itsumo Koko Kara
Kazunori Yamada
Hidenori Kikuchi
It's sad when...
when someone dies!
It's nice and loud
- Yeah
It's sad when...
when I walk down the street and someone calls me Minister instead of Prime Minister!
It's sad when I walk down the street and someone calls me Minister instead of Prime Minister!
It's sad when...
It's sad that Guzuroku looked so old on "Sanma Goten"--like a totally different person!
Is this how it's gonna be?
It's sad when...
Omeda put his heart and soul into playing a strange-looking flute on Tetsuko No Heya!
It's sad when Omeda put his heart and soul into playing a strange-looking flute on Tetsuko No Heya!
It wasn't a flute. It was a Quena
It's sad when...
My former student at Yuhigaoka High school married a foul-mouthed comedian from Kansai without much thought!
It's sad that my former student at Yuhigaoka High school married a foul-mouthed comedian from Kansai without much thought!
Natsumi Ogawa 16yrs old
(Hamada's wife)
This concludes our practice performance
You are dismissed
Thank you very much
This is so hard
Yamachan's stomach punch was really terrible
Considering his character, you would never expect that from him
More understandable if Takeuchi Riki did it (last year)
So this year they want to associate famous actors with comedians
2nd Floor Hallway
Training Room Entrance
Please let me rest a while!
Ok, This is a room for newly hired spies
For security reasons, you need authorization
Security Authentication System
Required for Entry: I.D. Card - Password - Palm Print
I need you to swipe your cards one at a time
Then enter the 3 digit code given to you by the director
The door will open only after all of you are clear
Matsumoto
This isn't me on the i.d.
Slide your card and enter your password
What's your password?
Look at Hamada getting away with laughing
Let me see...
Papa-san (883)
That's right
What happened?
How could you forget?
Pa
Papa--san
San
Press "enter" and
place your hand on the scanner
How cumbersome...
You were laughing there, too
Alright
I'd say he was laughing
Seriously, he was laughing
Like nobody's business
How could you not know to use your right hand?
I can't believe you laughed at that
Let's go, Hamada
Natsumi
Swipe your card and what's your password?
How did you remember that?
So you set it up like that...
Why didn't you answer him?
Fujiwara, you gotta get him to answer
Endou
But this isn't really me...
Don't bring that up every time
And don't show that to us
Iroha
Password?
168...
How'd you remember that?
Iroha (168) is my daughter's name
Scan your hand there
Mr. Todoroki is OK to enter now, too
Quiet
Kusai
Swipe your card and..
Use the keypad up here
9..3..1...
How'd you remember that?
Kusai (Stinky) (931)
Yamasaki, you're the last one
Samui
Password?
Rolling Shit Taro?
No, your 3-digit code
What the hell...?
ID Authenticated
Security Door Unlocked
Entrance granted
Could it turn any slower?
Why not make the door unlock quicker?
Shouldn't it unlock a little quicker?
Nice room
This will be your training room for the day
Sit in your assigned seats
You're in my seat
Huh?
Find your seats, please
I said you're in my seat
Sorry about that
It's nice and toasty in here
Nice and warm
Enjoy your break time
I would like to hit the bathroom
Are we free to go?
Shall we just go then?
I'm cold
A welcomed break after a rough start to the morning
I wouldn't call this a break
However, nobody expects a bathroom attack
Your only hot beverage choice is coffee
Well, I'm seeing some tea bags here
Man, how dare they use the left over "Suga Tea"
Ah, long time no see
Suga Tea
I can't get it out...
Bump
Bump!
What the hell...??
He's laughing, slap him now
Of course, he's OUT
You didn't even try to fight the urge to laugh
What just happened in the bathroom?
What, even the restroom isn't safe?!
So, there's no trick there
We have zero privacy here
I really need to go pee
We can't help but to think there's some tricks in the restroom
That's why we're reluctant to go
I made a cup of tea for you
You don't need to do crap like that!
Oh, he poured us tea?
What'd you think he said to you?
Tanaka Gets Hit With CO2 Gas
Tanaka~!!
You're too big of a wuss!
Who wouldn't be scared?
Cut me some slack
Close call
Wait, not close, I'm OUT
I'm sensing way more slaps than usual
What's up?
Let me pee in peace, please
Two Hours Have Passed
The Trainees Can Finally Relax in Their Room
But the Infamous "Drawer Tricks"
Await the Cast!!
We're closed for business
We just barely made it to the break room
It was just the beginning
From the bus ride all the way to the bathroom
Dokaben
How does "Dokaben" fit into this format anyway?
You've been slapped quite a bit already, Hamada-san
You think so?
I'd say you've had plenty already
Yeah, Downtown has gotten slapped a lot
But you will have the most slaps at the end for sure!!
I don't, I don't think soooo....
Sooooo??
He's been like this lately
And what's up with you punching the hell out of the urinal?
That was hard to watch
Well, that was...
I don't mean to sound gross but,
since it was cold I was wearing a lot of layers
And I had a hard time whipping out my junk
I put some muscle into yanking it out and I went "Pow!"
Well, let us continue then
Yes, let's do that
Matsumoto-san, please
Cue us in
WOW!!
It's time for the group to face an infamous prank
Do you think there's stuff in the desk drawers??
Of course there is
We're refusing to acknowledge the drawers, huh?
I say this every year...
I'm not required to open these drawers
I agree
Why do we have to open them?
Although, it's hard to ignore them
Screw it and open yours
Do I go first?
Endou Is the Lead-Off Hitter
OK then
What if it's one of those....
tricks that make you jump...
I need to be ready for that possibility
Hey, hey
What?
We caught you
Seriously, you need to tighten your lips
I'd say Tanaka's overly scared
Go ahead and open it
Tanaka, you ready?
Here I go
Let me know when you're ready
Here I go!
Endou's first drawer!
Don't worry
See?
Panel Found
You got a panel
So I get the panel...
Don't try to get out of this
You were gonna shove that in our faces
Well...
How about this?
How about...
Hold it like this
And push it up like this
Got that?
It's only fair
Ready?
Here it is
Who is that?
Is that your...
This isn't right
Who the hell is that?
This is so wrong
This isn't good
This needs to be put away
Wait a minute!
Let me see that!
No, seriously!
Mysterious Girl
Why, why, why?
How annoying!
They set me up
They've been hanging out a lot recently...
No, please listen to me
Where'd she take this?
I need to... I need to... I don't know
Who is this?
He laughing like it's nothing
I was expecting to see some old hag,
but it ended up being some random chick
I thought
"Who the hell is this?"
Who the hell is this?
So she's a...
This sucks
They couldn't have done worse really
One of the Gaki episode
involved Hamada-san pretending to be a no-show
but would sneak in on camera shots?
Aforementioned Episode
"Hamada is watching"
At that time, I was...
at that restaurant!?
Yeah, and she was working...
You were at the family restaurant
She waited my table there
And I straight up asked for her phone number...
You gotta be kidding!
She was the Waitress Endou Picked Up
You are the worst!
We've only been e-mailing each other thus far...
And never met in person
She actually stood me up twice
So why do the staff members...?
Why do they have this?
This whole thing must have been a setup by the staff members
From that while ago?
It's all clear now
I get it
My bad
but I sent her some really nasty e-mails...
No way!...
Let me hear it!
No way! There is no way I'm telling you that!
I don't see why WE need to be involved in this
and get our asses slapped
The kicker is I have this same pic saved in my cell phone...
Why were we being punished for that?
Yes, why?
The really pulled one on me there
They got me good
She looks like a chick Endou would be into
Amazing
What's crazy is
that is only our first drawer
This is horrible!
I'm getting freaked out...
about opening other drawers...
What if they're...
Well, they won't pull a same trick twice
Right, they're all different
That first drawer really got me...
What would you do if all of your drawers were like the first one?
Ka, ke, key...
What the heck?
I kept telling myself that the drawer was locked...
That was your fault!!
And NOT MINE!!!!
From now on, how about
only YOU get slapped if you can't spit out a word or two?
Nothing there
Nothing?
Candy Found
What's this?
Candy?
Just regular candy
Alright then...
Alright, after this, I'm done
There wasn't anything else
I'm done
Should we do this in order?
Any order is good with me...
This is really nerve wrecking
Should I go then?
Are you OK with sitting like that?
In case it explodes or something?
The drawer is too "narrow" to setup like that
Narrow?
What do you mean by "Narrow"?
Um, this...
You mean "Thinness?"
That was dumb... just dumb
Would you give me a break!?
What's with "Narrow" talk?
You got me in this, too
He's right, that drawer is thin
And not "Narrow"
Oh! I was spared!
Tanaka was spared just now
Ah, nothing is in there...
Nothing there
Take out the whole drawer, why don't you?!
You don't have to open it that far
Hamada Action Figure
This haunted us later
What in the hell...?
That's just straight up hilarious!
What is this?
Amazing
Hamada Action Figure
The resemblance is uncanny
This was very well crafted
It had the perfect physique
We can't stand him up though
You can just have him sit?
That is just...
He looks just like him
Don't stare at it
It's hazardous!!
Hazardous to our health
Just like him
Packed Panties
How much is in there?
It's packed
How anally retentive
Very packed
Super packed
Nothing is found at the bottom drawer
Matsumoto-san, how about it?
Someone else?
Can I go then?
Look what he's up to
That's an unfair angel
I'm going then
Yama-chan, you're up?
Nada
Nothing?
A Rock Found
What's this?
HOT!!
Rock is Burning Hot
Who would've thought?
You better not be lying!
I had no idea
Are you serious?
It's really hot?
It's really hot
Wow
How evil is this?
You would have been toast had you grabbed that any sooner
Nothing
I see something
Yes, there's something in there
Trash
Seriously, did we figure out what this was?
It was just a trash
They're screwing with you
What was that all about?
This is nothing more than a trash
So this is how they see us
I'm finished
Tanaka-san, you're ready?
I suppose it is my turn
Is this gonna make us jump?
I'm afraid of the sudden loud noise
Tanaka, you're such a wuss
Envelope Found
The staff have been onto you for a while, huh Endo?
If I can only reveal what kind of emails I have been...
I wish you'd tell us
I can't reveal that
Here we go
Mysterious DVD
Here's one
Two
and three
Why so many?
Why don't we come back to that later
First thing first
You have more?
Another Envelope Found
You're kiddin'
DVD?
We get more?
Prank Envelope
What was that?
It's a prank
Like that rattlesnake prank envelope?
Here it is
Only you would fall for that
Drawer was set up perfectly
Nothing here
Nothing here either
So you get the set of DVD's
What now?
Matsumoto-san?
I really don't wanna do this
Can I open it?
Go for it
Will you tell him to cut it out?
Nothing in here
I have a feeling something's in here
What the??
Red Ink on Drawer
Such a childish prank!
That was pointless
Yeah, it was
Really pointless
Nothing
Give him a tissue..a wet one
So irritating
What is this....
a microphone?
Wet Tissue Explosion
That was dangerous!
Give me a break
That was super scary!
That scared the hell outta me!
So scary!
They knew we would use it to wipe off the ink
Yeah, that's right!
I see
This should be OK
What was that...?
It wasn't even intended to make us laugh
Why are you laughing?
I'm not
You're doing nothing but laughing
Why is it so strict today?
Yeah, it is this year
What about Endou's candy?
Yeah, what's up with that?
Gotta be something to it
It's labeled as "Magic Candy"
Why not open it?
Let's eat it
Really?
ZAP!
Electric Shock Candy
That was so painful
Wait a...
They're not trying to make us laugh this year
The pranks are painful
and scary
It zapped you?
I felt the strong current going up my arm
This is awful..
I wonder if the DVD prank is the same as last year?
*"OUT" was hidden in the lyrics
Last Year
Yamasaki OUT angel~
Tanaka 2-Slaps Angel~
Yeah, I never expected...
Endou Still Can't Get Her Out of His Head
So, was she a customer?
No, she was a shop employee
It was a shock.. really...
I didn't notice you were doing that
Well.. it really wasn't hurting us
Now I know why she didn't respond
Because...
she said she was at the hospital...with some kind of heart disease or something...
on the day we were going to see...
That's enough, you're taking too long
How come he's laughing that much and...
I'd say I'm 100% safe
Why is that?
Looks like he was laughing at a comedy show
Yama-chan should get two hits
Look at my dusty pants
Wanna try watching a DVD?
Yeah, the DVD's
There's a total of three?
We can't just leave them there...
Why do you have that look on your face?
We still don't know if Tanaka will be out
It might be an instructional DVD for the GIA
Yes, that's true
Sorry, I had a flashback from last year
Let's watch it then!!
Yeah
I wonder what's on it
Yama-chan, it was in your desk last year, right?
Yes
Right?
That's right
Just because you find the DVD doesn't mean you'll get an "OUT"
Yes, that's true
Today's topics
Professional Baseball ZERO CATCH
Seibu Vs Softbank
9th Inning Hard Run
Orix Vs Rakuten
Nice play x 3
Liars Vs GIA
Over Thrown Cross play!?
A player runs amok in the last inning,
Nice play x 3
and the benches clear out during a brawl!?
Today's Topics
Professional Baseball ZERO CATCH
Seibu Vs Softbank
9th inning Hard run
Orix Vs Rakuten
Nice play x 3
Liars Vs GIA
Over thrown cross play?!
A player runs amok in the last inning,
Three great plays,
and the benches clear out during a brawl!?
We finally see ace Yamada after a year and five months
Liars
GIA's Yamasaki in the white uniform
What kind of spy is that?
It was a perfect pitch but the 3rd baseman overthrew the ball
Their defense made crucial errors
Next up was Matsumoto
Hamada connects again as Yamada struggles with his pitching
No outs and bases are loaded
The clean up hitter is Endou, and he's averaging .300
First pitch
Endou hits a weak slider to left center for an RBI
Endou sees his chance and tries for home plate
But gets called out
An argument erupts
What kind of call was that?
No way he tagged me
He was clearly safe
And that got Coach Tanaka going
He was safe!
Tanaka ejected!
Thai kick!!
Tanaka gets thrown out and will receive a Thai Kick
The GIA don't give up
But the catcher didn't tag him
Endou and Hamada start to complain
No, don't get involved
Next, Yamasaki starts to heat things up
Where the hell were you looking?
No, stop talking
Yamasaki ejected!
Thai kick!!
Both players from GIA will receive a Thai kick
And they also lost the game
No way!!
Thai Kick Punishment to the Named Players
This is ridiculous!
Well, the show must go on
Why?
It doesn't make sense that I have to be Thai kicked!!
Stay put or you'll get really hurt
Move forward
Move up
Why?
Hurry up
This can't be
Stay calm
No, please
THAT'S ENOUGH
That's super painful
I only smiled... slightly...
Yeah, he did
He smiled, he smiled
That must've really hurt... this DVD is scary
Take it out
Thai kicks are the worst
I wasn't expecting the Thai kick...
C'mon, can't you stop playing with the doll?
Can you stop turning the head in different directions
You're using it as a weapon
Excuse me but I have to...
That's not a natural position
Confiscate that!
Yes, we should
Take it away
Please, I'm confiscating this
Let me have it
OK, here
Why you....
Why do you do that?
This was tough not to laugh
What a pain!
You're playing dirty now!
What the hell are you doing?!
That needs to be confiscated
Confiscate that, please
I wish I had that weapon in my hand
One trick after the other,
The trickery will not stop
Listen up
Let us join the meeting out at the ground level
Participate in GIA Morning Meeting
Secret Agent ~?
You'd make us stand out in this cold?
Man, I hate the outside
They made such a big deal about the "security,"
but look at this door being wide freakin' open
Assembled Secret Agents
Here we go
Here we go again
Line up in order of
Tanaka, Endo,
Hamada, Matsumoto,
and Yamasaki at the end
Secret Agent
Toshiya Sakai
Thanks for joining us for the GIA morning meeting
Our guest is a GIA chief commander from Holland branch
Let me introduce him to you all
Lady´s and gentlemen, colleagues!!
I´m most flattered to be here with you.
Greetings in Dutch
I have come to Japan and Japan is such a beautiful country
I have enjoyed such a nice meal yesterday
I actually want to ask myself....
What do I want to say more...
ARE YOU LISTING!!!
YOU ARE SLEEPING!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE!
Did you choose the wrong job?
He's pissed at you, Tanaka
What, me?
BIIIGGG LONGGG MISTER!!
You have chosen the wrong job!
Tanaka evokes anger
I was scared for him
I didn't do anything...
WINDOW CLEANER!!
He wouldn't be that pissed off for nothing
Seriously, he had my full attention
NOT ENOUGH!! AGAIN!!!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE MISTER!?
YOU ARE TALL...
YOUR TIE IS WRONG!!!
WHAT ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO DO HERE!!!!
YOU HAVE SEARCHED FOR THE WRONG JOB!!!
TALL, TALL,... TALLER...
BRAAWWAAAAAHH
Tanaka, you really need to apologize
Say you're sorry!
Apologize to him anyway
He's really pissed off
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO!!!
THIS ISN´T GOING WELL!!!
I'm sorry
I´M GONNA GET YOU!!!
OK?!
I'm sorry about that
Chief "Vents" Kick
He's got nothing to do with this
Thank you very much
One of us has received an Excellence Citation
He's made our occupation "cool"
Limosine Arrives
One of us has received an Excellence Citation
He's made our occupation "cool"
Limosine Arrives
Too hot for a Spy
Arthur Kuroda
How are you all doing today?
Who's going to be my hostage tonight?
Too Hot for White Tighty
Don't hit the back thigh
I love you~!
With that, the meeting is adjourned
Ready?
Five hours has passed
A situation turns mysterious as Fujiwara makes a suggestion
I just caught you laughing
Let's get it right
Right, a fair game
Let's do some stretches
Why don't you stand up?
Contrived Stretching
We need to exercise
We can do this on our own
Well, let's do this together
First, pull your arms up like this
My back hurts
And move side to side
Now lean forward...
BBBBang!
BBBBBBang!!
What the....!?
Now lean forward...
BBBang!
BBBBBang!!
What the hell...?!!
I heard some noise
But that was nothing
What's wrong with you guys?
Freaky...
You scared me
Hamada, your shoulder must be stiff
Well...
I'll give it a good rub
No, you don't have to...
You've always suffered from stiff shoulders
See?
How scary is that?
What, you've seen ghost or something??
Don't be so down
I know..
You got taller all of a sudden...
That voice is none other than (Itao)
You know, your reputation has gone sour these days
Is that so?
That's right, your coworkers are sharing the same sentiment
Downtown needs to do a live concert as a unit
Won't you guys do a live performance?
as Downtown...
We'll give it some....consideration
Yeah, let's get it together
What's with you guys?
You've seen a ghost or something?
How many times is he going to say that?
I don't get what's going on here
He's freaking me out
It's amazing how scary he is!!
That was a good hit
Don't hold back
Which celebrity's underwear do you want to see?
Who wants to start?
There's gotta be someone
At least one...
The real Fujiwara isn't like this
Fujiwara-san, you're a bit creepy
There's nothing creepy about me
I'm just Fujiwara after all...
My weight is killing my back
You haven't noticed yet, have you?
This guy has been impersonating me
He's a master of disguise
Were you fooled!? Members!
Members?
Master of Disguise
Itao Itsuji
What're you saying?
He said "Members!"
So that's what you're going to call us?
Did you think I was Fujiwara?
Wouldn't it be great if ... everyone here
could become a professional like him?
Let's go
But we knew the entire time...
Yeah, we knew about it
The biggest giveaway was Itao's legs
with the stockings
He's got unique looking legs
That bow-legged stance and all...
Tanaka, hurry up and put in the next DVD
Should we take a a look?
We're gonna watch it sooner or later
It would be nice to get them all out of the way...
Yeah, that's a good point...
Maybe it won't be me this time...
I might not have a part in this either...
However it goes, it won't be good for any of us
Somehow we always get dragged into it...
Kimi no Hitomi ni Ryouomoi
(Love in Your Eyes)
Announcing the Suga HS Basketball Club's 10 year reunion
Cheers!
Even after all this time, nothing has really changed
Especially you, Ritsuko
You're still maintaining your beauty
Thanks, but keep trying
Are you saying I failed to maintain my beauty?
Not at all! You look lovely in that red dress
You're the only one who can get away with wearing that dress
You've really done it now!
Just like old times...
Yeah...
Hosaka, who are you married to?
One of my coworkers
Speaking of which, you should get married!
You're giving Captain a bad name
I'm good with being single right now...
(No, not there! Not there! Ow, ow...)
Oh, well then...
Completely unrelated to this program: You've all just been Rick Roll'ed
Cut it out, mercy!
Huh!?
What's up?
Producer
Yoshinobu Nakamura
Didn't you go to the US?
What's up?
Yoshinobu!
Didn't you go to the US?
You've got to be kidding me!?
Pretty Amazing!
Stop putting Yoshinobu in these things!!
Who's he supposed to be?
So Yoshibu-san decided to join this group this year
No kidding...
I kept wondering, "Who could it be?"
Huh!?
What's up?
Yoshinobu!!
Hang on, didn't you go to the US!?
Yeah, I was...
But I felt like seeing you guys again, that's all
And just as always, you're never on time
Captain, I don't need to hear your life lessons anymore
Long time no see!
Yeah!
Where's Ohsawa by the way?
Just like the old days, he'd rather be alone
How about you, Ritsuko?
You two are dating, right?
Sorry, but I don't really...
Let's not dwell on a guy who's a no-show
Let's hear about your US adventure instead
Yeah, weren't you in New York?
Did you see Michael Jordan walking around?
Tanaka...
Yeah?
So things with Ohsawa aren't going well?
What do you mean?
When his name came up tonight,
you sort of turned away
Which is exactly what you always used to do
So that was a dead giveaway
You caught me, Gitan
But don't worry, this is nothing new
Speaking of which, Gitan, it was only you...
What kind of name is Gitan?
I figured there'd be a better name than that
Thanks for walking me home
Gitan!
Tanaka!
I'm sorry. I lied...
I'm afraid my relationship with him is over
I can never tell what he's thinking...
And I never know what to do!
What a quick turn of an event
Gitan!
The music sounds like Omega Tribe
I think it's them
This is their song?
Amazing
Look at this cast!
It really HAS been a long time HASN'T it?
Next Week
I love you more than anybody else in this world
Marry me!
What a spoiler
That's the whole story right there
It's about time.  It's your turn, Gitan
Wait,
Now that you mention it...
If Ritsuko and Hosaka got married,
then your name your name will be
Tanaka Naoki
Cut it out
Tanaka Naoki is completely OUT
Tanaka Naoki is completely Thai Kicked
See you next week!
Tanaka's Second Thai Kick of the Day
I can't do this anymore!
This is too much
Yes, this is way too much
You can't be sitting down though
Could you wait a minute?
I hear you, but...
What're you gonna do though?
Stand up straight, otherwise, it'll hurt more
Get your hands up
No matter what, he's not going to be easy on you
How do you expect us not to laugh after seeing that reaction?!
You gotta get it together though
Tanaka, seriously, cut it out
I'm sure that hurt
And this might be your last
The real training starts right now
Can I have your attention please
Here at the GIA,
there is a special training course for newcomers
And there are no exceptions,
so please change into these uniforms
GIA Special Training
Training?
This is such a drag
Yeah, it is
These uniforms make me think this won't be easy
Gearing Up for Special Training
Prior to training, they change into training outfits
Special training...
Special Training for Spy Trainees
The Real Training Starts Now!!
What could be their special training?
The beginning of their special training
Training...
Do we really need training for our training?
Man, this feels kind of weird
Training Grounds
Looks like this is going to be difficult
It's still raining
Line up in order right here
We will now start your spy training
But before we begin, take a look over there
NO WAY!!
You're joking right?
Please don't tell me this is what I think it is
Well, doesn't this bring back memories?
Nightmares!!
Their Minds Fill With Terrible Memories...
A Nightmare From 10 Years Ago
24 Hour Endurance Tag
It's a symbol of their 24-hour game of tag from 10 yrs ago
What is Their Special Training!?
What special training is in store for them?
This was tough
This is an escape exercise!!
No way!  No way!
We shouldn't be doing something like this in the rain!
I really, really hate this!
As you know, you will receive the punishment
Escape Training
When Caught You Receive
the Punishment Written on the Tagger's Chest
written on the tagger's chest if you get caught
Escape Training
At the Start of Training, 3 Devils Will Appear
At the start of training, 3 Devils will appear
One Hour Time Limit
After 20 Minutes, Two New Devils Will Be Added Every 10 Minutes
The entire GIA compound will be used for this training
Training Area: Entire GIA compound
Don't-Get-Caught
Spy
Spy Escape Training
Matsumoto, you just had an operation, so you can't be running around right?
No, I really can't
In that case, we found a substitute for you
YES!
Seriously, I can't be running around
Why didn't they get this?
How spunky is this guy?
Matsumoto, you just had an operation, so you can't be running around right?
No, I really can't
In that case, we found a substitute for you
YES!
The Other Four Don't Understand Why
Why?
Because I really can't run
Why don't you get this?
Hey!
How spunky is this guy?
Who the hell...?
Matsumoto's Substitute
Ikki Sawamura (Actor)
We still can't laugh?
Huh?
It's raining harder now
Hey, everyone's getting wet
It doesn't matter, they'll do it anyway
It's so wet
Are you OK with this?  Do you know what you're getting into?
Yes
I only know that I will be paid well for this!!
Is that how you choose your work?
You gotta be kiddin' me!
Don't talk like that, Sawamura-san
I doubt you'll be paid that well
OK, let's start!
And what am I supposed to do??
The taggers will show up
Just keep running away
That's your only goal
OK, let's get started
COUGH
Escape Training Begins
Scary
Slipper
He's super fast
Yeah, very fast
That'll leave some mark
Three Devils Are Released
For the first 20 mins, 3 Devils will follow them
Dekopin
Not an ideal condition for running
*Five Cameramen in White Suits Follow the Cast
(Stickers are placed on their back when they get punished)
Matsumoto watches from the stage
Dekopin
Slipper
Biting
It's still early in the training and they are receiving a lot of punishment
A Flurry of Early Punishment
I don't see Hamada
I think he took off somewhere
I'm dying
I can't get away from them all
15 minutes have passed, and the 3 Devils enter the building to search for the cast
The 3 Devils search the building
The Five Members Regroup
So tiring...
Did they get you yet?
Yes...Dekopin
You can see it on our backs
Cocorico got punished a lot
It starts to pour, and Matsumoto returns alone to the spy training room
Matsumoto Returns to the Training Room
Last month I got my appendix removed
I was bored out of my mind
Really?
Appendix Operation 1 Month Ago
I hope you got my my back, Hamada-san
What? Why did you take this job?
Because I can get paid a lot...
His priority is money, no matter what
20 minutes have passed
5 More Devils Are Added
5 More Devils Added
Slipper
Dekopin
Biting
After 5 Additions, a Total of 8 Devils Are on the Field!
Slap
Back flip
Harisen
Ch$%ko
Machine
But the five men are unaware of this
The Unsuspecting Five
Sawamura-san, could you go look around outside?
Just to make sure those guys in black aren't around
And we'll look around in here
Sawamura Goes Alone to Check Outside
What?!
Oh...it's my shadow
Sawamura Surprised by His Own Shadow
What?  Is he getting punished?
No, he's just super nervous
So scary
There he is
Dekopin?
Dekopin
Distance to Target
What's happening!?
Dekopin!  Dekopin is coming!!
He's coming!!
Dekopin is here!
Dekopin
He's here!!
It's a dead end
Avoided Dekopin
Why did I take this gig...
Sawamura avoided Dekopin, but he now goes after the other 4 men
Dekopin
Distance to the 4 Targets
Who dropped that?
Oh
Yours, Tanaka?
Is that mine?
He's coming.. coming.. coming!!
This way leads to a dead end
What are you doing?
How dare you take a coffee break?!
There was nothing else to do!
Distance to Hamada
Dekopin
Hamada Escapes to a Camera-Free Zone
WHOA!!
Whoaaahhhh~!!
I'm exhausted
Hamada - Heart Break
Matsumoto - Tea Break
How dare you sigh like that
Slipper
Dekopin
Biting
Slap
Back flip
Harisen
D@#$ Machine
8 Devil Types!!
Some Devils hide and wait for their prey
Wait a minute!
Seriously?
What's this?
He was subjected to this?
What is this?
Wait, wait, wait!
It's the D#$% Machine
D@#$ Machine
Countdown
Ikki Sawamura (43 years old) writhes in pain
Please, excuse me
Sawamura shakes "it" back
[Camera Man] - You can't go in there
"You can't go in there"
My guess is they'll come this way
I'll keep an eye on upstairs
Yamasaki, Tanaka, and Endo watch for Devils in the main building
I'm looking over here
Don't forget, they're in black
I see someone
Is that Hamada-san?
Hamada-san!!
He's under the spotlight
Superstar Hamada - Always Under the Spotlight
Who do you think you are!?
It's not like I asked to be in the spotlight
What kind of Devil are you?
What?
What did it say?
It started with an "A"
A Devil Cigarette Break
"A Smoke Break?"
A Smoke Break
A "Cigarette" Break
How does this work?
I'm utterly lost over here
It's not like you can talk to him, right?
"How does this work?"
This is one of the lucky ones
Thank you very much
He got a good one
Back flip
Threatening Shadows Approach Them
Man, it's pouring now
Hamada! Behind you, behind you!!!
How dare you call me Hamada
Hamada! Behind you, behind you!!
In a Panic,
Endo disrespects his mentor, Hamada-san
I meant to say, "Hamada-san, behind you"
The Gorilla Boss Finds a Perfect Hiding Place
How creepy!
Mysterious headlights
That's dangerous
Harisen (Large Fan)
Wow, he was chased by a car?
Hamada Laughs at Another's Misfortune
They came at me with a car
That was hairy
I could've been run over
I got caught by "A Smoke Break"
Ah, I see what it means now
Yamasaki -
Traumatized By the Car Chase
30 minutes have passed
Tell me what kind of editing that was!
Trainee's Room
Main
Annex
Gym
As Tanaka and Sawamura take cover inside,
the others are in front of the gym
More Tagging Devils are summoned
Why aren't they coming after us?
You know, that Harisen group...
As long as we stay still, they can't detect us
I see...like dinosaurs
You know dinosaurs can only detect movement
Shozo, why don't you get closer then
They can also detect oxygen
Go walk past them
Once again,
Hamada enjoys other's misfortune
Fatso
Wow, I can actually outrun these guys
Did Endou get away...
Ha, ha, ha!!
What, what what??
Serious? Seriously?
Cut it out, stop, stop, stop!!
Serious, serious, you're kidding me
Punishment : Mega Slap
After watching Yamasaki get slapped,
Hamada Flees           While the Fatso's are Distracted
Hamada changes his hiding place
But...
Fatso
You're fast...
Hamada         at his Ugliest
Leave him alone
That was hellish
Definitely hell
I thought they couldn't see us if we stay put
I take it back
They can see us
What if they're behind us right now?
They        Are Terrified of the Tagging Devils
They're different than what I remembered...
They've evolved over the years
Just as they're reminded of the Devil's terrifying nature...
I know we can beat him
He didn't evolve for sure
Yeah, he actually regressed
Heipo
I'm afraid he's gonna hurt himself...
This is a great opportunity
to take out our frustrations on him
I've got a Harisen!
Go away!
I can beat that particular Devil
He hasn't changed
Not Much        Gas Left in His Tank
Another          Encounter with Fatso
I've seen enough of their battles
Mega-Running        Hamada
Seriously, I've seen enough of you and the fatso
Mega-Sleeping        Matsumoto
I wasn't asleep, moron!!
How dare you...
How're you doing?
I'm OK but...
Handsome Man Used Ugliest Man         As a Shield
What now?
Fishing
How is....how is my nose looking?
I'd say it's gotten bigger...or wider
You're kidding right?
50 minutes have passed
More Devils are summoned
15 Tagging Devils
And no place for them to hide
They have an advantage wearing all black...
This sucks!
Where did you come from?
Where the hell did you come from!!??
Here he comes, comes, comes, comes, comes
Here comes some seaweed
Seaweed
What...what do you have?
Who would've thought you'd be hiding there?!
Seaweed
One victim after the other...
With so many Devils in the area, the cast become victims one by one
Slipper
Fishing
Yamasaki        is on the verge of being traumatized again
Slipper
Seaweed
Sawamura got cornered by the Slipper and Seaweed!!
That's the worst
Could the "Fishing" Devil be coming for him too?
You're kiddin' me!!
I hate the Slap!!
Slap
Sawamura becomes victim to the Slap
Actor Ikki Sawamura
Gets a Real Slap
They should've taken him to the fishing area
Seriously, what in the hell are we doing?
What is this?
Whatever happened to  the "No Laughing" rules?
This has nothing to do with that
Who approaches Sawamura after having just been slapped..??
Fishing
There he is again
They got me already!
I just had this!
I just got fished!!
Seriously, this just happened to me!!
I was fished already!!
Cut me some slack!!!
Nobody deserves to be fished twice
He got fished again?
There's a lot of "Fishing" Devils around
There's been a lot of monsters where Tanaka's roaming around
Why're you calling them "monsters?"
Fishing
Nobody deserves this punishment twice
That hurts
You're gonna yank my nose off
That kills
Seriously, this hurts!!
You were like, "It hurts!"
You were all, "You're yanking my nose off!"
Only five minutes left
The group reunites again
Hang on a sec, OK?
What...are you friends with those monsters now?
Yeah, that was my second time getting fished
I just witnessed it
I can't shake them off anymore
By the time I see them, it's too late
Devil Sneaks His Way in
So how much longer do...
Slipper
That slipper hurt bad
That delivers a punch
Yea, that slipper hurts
How dare you ditch me like that...
Funny, this is how I try to get away from them
You should be protecting me like this
Sorry, but it's only natural that I do it
You can't control your instincts
In the meantime, Tanaka gets chased by another devil
In the meantime, Tanaka was
You were chased a lot
That's enough!
What is this, what, what, what??
Matsuri
What's that?
This isn't good
I see, it's some kind of wooden torturing device
He could get hurt with that
They got him good now
That makes me feel better about myself
That wasn't good at all
One minute left
Releasing the last devils
They're releasing more on the last minute
All are summoned on the last minute
I don't want anymore
He said they're all here
How am I supposed to...?
We can outrun them all
Here they come
Body Toss
That's a lot of devils
Training Complete
Matsumoto awakes
I'm exhausted
That was a rough hour
That was really really difficult
Like hell, it was
That wooden torture device looked kind of fun
After a hard hour of training
The cast members wind down from the madness
Applying Heating Pad
How come you're so cold?
Having the heating pad gives me energy
From good blood circulation, right?
Hamada Action Figure
You'd better quit that
The way Hamada-san flips in the air is too much...
The flip is full of grace, too
Yes, that hurt
Cut it out!!
Let's not do that anymore, please
No more Hamada-san back flipping
I used to practice this all the time with my Kamen Rider figurine
I used to play with figurines by myself
and I mastered how the human body flips through the air
Right, you do that perfectly
It's a natural motion
Will you stop doing that, please?
Let's be done with it
We're done with it
Well, nobody's gaining anything from this
I have to go pee
Ouch
Tanaka's got a sensitive ass or something
Mysterious Person Approaches
Locks Tanaka in the Stall
What was that?
What's this?
Tanaka?
Huh?
Why'd you have to call him like that?
Our butts are taking a beating, huh?
Are you really Tanaka?
Of course, it's me
What kind of question is that?
Ask him something only he would know the answer to
Which middle school did you attend in Toyonaka?
Toyonaka-3rd-Middle school
You were "4th"!!
I...like animals
I...like animals!
This isn't Tanaka
Something isn't right
Where was our first performance?
Yeah, I was there, too
Yeah, it's that place...
Um...
Nishi Shinjyuku's Pooku Doll Theater
How in the hell did you come up with that name?
I've heard of that place, but...
But you're wrong!
Not a bad hit
Was it at Akasaka?
It was at Akasaka Play Box
That's definitely NOT Tanaka
I really like animals
Tanaka, share some of your knowledge about animals
Tell us something about sharks
The real Tanaka knows this
Sharks eat monkeys!!
Sharks eat monkeys!
That's a scary thought
What do you call it when...when whales spray water
You told me before
When they blow?
Some whales spray water...
but some spray water somewhere else, is this what you're asking me?
OK, that's enough
That's enough, this is a waste of time
Yeah
That's enough, Tanaka
Huh, he's laughing
What's so funny?
You know, if you laugh, you're OUT, right?
That's enough!
None of you knew, right?
That isn't the real Tanaka!
I'm not the real Tanaka!
I tricked all of you members!!
Why "Members"?
This is a professional, amazing right?
I wonder if he's a professional
Shall we go?
How about teaching us a little about disguise?
Yeah
So, it was Tanaka who tricked us, right?
Maybe they kidnapped him or something
Right, in the restroom?
Yes
So if I went to the bathroom, they could nab me
and a fake Matsumoto would appear
That's scary!
Here comes another impersonator
So I was in the bathroom and the"fake me" took me away
I was thinking you were playing a trick on us
No, I was taking a leak...
You ARE Tanaka, right?
I'm Tanaka!
Share some shark knowledge with us
There are over 500 species of sharks and half of them live in the deep sea
Definitely Tanaka
I caught a glimpse of him
He looked just like me, didn't he?
Yeah
Fart!
I think you better go get a check up
Huh? Who are we talking about?
Me?
Why?
Stop making that face!
I told you to stop making that chimpanzee face
You can hit him harder
No, but seriously...
I started get grossed out over time...
By his farting?
If we all had same amount of farting in our life time,
he's farted to enough to clean our all of our fart savings
Like about 10 times a day?
No no no no
More than... PL's annual fireworks festival, right?
So that's about 40,000 fireworks, right?
It takes awhile to come to an end
It never ends
Wow, this time it was a good hit!
Yeah, that hurt!
Sometimes, it stinks pretty bad
and when we say, "it stinks", he gets so happy, right?
Oh, you laughed just then
Good
Hit hard
That looked painful
Yes, keep that up!
What?!
I just cleared my throat
OK, this is how you wanna play?
Wow! That looked painful!
Painful
I'd say that's the baseline for hitting
That was harsh
He's walking like Michael Jackson
Looks like the mask Itao would wear!!
He laughed too!
Hit him hard!
Go easy, go easy
It hurts, hurts!
That hurts
Seems like the hits are getting stronger and stronger!
It's been 9 hours since training started
They entertain themselves during down time
Endo, let's go smoke
They head to the smoking area
Smoking area
We couldn't see who it was from behind
Who's she?
Rie Shibata With No Make Up
That's harsh
It really is
They're not here
The Punishers Went to the Wrong Room
What are you doing?
Look what she's got on today
She didn't say a word
Can I borrow your lighter?
Zap!
OUCH!
Shock Lighter
This is too much!
It's telling you to quit smoking
That's another reason you shouldn't smoke
They're getting hit continuously
Wow, she didn't speak
She didn't say a word
Good night
She came here just for this?
Yes, I guess so
How annoying
She had ZERO makeup on!!
Was everything OK?
When we entered...
someone was smoking
An old woman was smoking
When I saw her, it was Ms. Shibata with no make up
No makeup
Yeah, that would be funny
She was wearing an apron and unfashionable clothes
There's no place to rest
No place to run
Dangerous
Mission
The spies are headed for a dangerous mission
Spy
Main Spy office
Phone calls are routed here from spies all over the world
Taking care of phone calls from around the world
Charismatic Receptionists
Charismatic Receptionists take calls
Not again...
He's in this for sure
Jennifer-san
Nancy-san
These two have agreed to assist as well as....
Here he comes
Onishi Hideko-san
Laughing Hell
Assassins Appear!!
Assassins appear one after another
A Monster Shows Up
The monster unveils itself
Dream Match Up
A dream match-up
Shivering in Terror
Shiver in Terror
So Do the Shrieking Cries~!!
As the Game Intensifies
Give me a break!!
Risky
Mission
Spies risk their lives
Spy
on a daily basis to accomplish their missions
Spy Headquarters
Headquarters never stops getting calls regarding their spies
takes unique phone handling skills
Handling calls from all over the world
The following is a recording of their typical day
Nancy-san
Jennifer-san
They have agreed to participate in this recording
And this is Hideko Ohnishi
Hello, this is Spy Headquarters
How may I help you?
I hired one of your spies
But his service has been terrible
OK! Well....I....
Well...
I'm feeling very bad and...
feeling bad about...
Well....I'm feeling...
Well, that's the feeling I'm feeling
I need a formal apology!
Yes!
Fortunately, we're blessed with such a nice day
And very lively
Why "lively?"
Hell has arrived
Fortunately, we're blessed with such a nice day
And very lively
Ah, as I ask you to refer to the...
And my whole family couldn't be happier
Don't mess with me!
I'm sorry, please don't get mad
I have....I haven't studied at the college level...
Wait
Wait a sec
You got my thigh!
Can we finish this quickly?
I used to play baseball in high school
And I would stay until sundown to play ball, day after day
So I more or less neglected studying
And ended up learning only five subjects
I've heard enough!
I see, thank you for the call
Every call is different, aren't they?
Somebody
Hello, this is Spy Headquarters
What are you inquiring about today?
I'm US Spy 002
Where are we with the "Mission:Impossible" case?
Huh?
Where do we stand on the "Mission:Impossible" case?
Passhibu~?
Misshioni~ Posshibu~??
I thought I made it through
I like it
That's good
I'm Japanese Spy 0010
0010?
Teach me how the Spy Theme song goes
Spy Theme Song?
Well...
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
Bang Bang Bang
And that's the song for the...
Where's the rest?
Ah! Chitty Chitty! Chitty Chitty!
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
Bang Bang Bang
Bang Bang
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
Bang Bang Bang
Bang Bang
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
Bang Bang Bang
Bang Bang
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
Bang Bang Bang
Bang Bang
Twinkle Twinkle
Pah Pah Pah!
Yeah
Yeah, No, stop it
Yea, Yea, Yea
Yeah
Yea, yea, yea
Yea, yea, Yea
Yeah, yea, yea
Yeah, yea, yo
Swish, swish
Swich, swish, swish
Swish, swish, swish
Swish
Swish, Peg, gah, pekkuri
Swish, swish
Swish, swish, swish
Sattan-ra
Swish, swish
Swish, swish, swish
Hi-ra-ri
And that's the end...
Alright, I made it through
My butt hurts
There's been more than 10 hours of training
The spy occupation carries certain labels such as
"scary", "hard", or "mean"
But the opposite is true...it's a fun occupation....I believe
And they're holding a show just to prove that point
And we're invited to attend it
A show??
Improve the Spy's Bad Image
Observe the Image Improvement Show
I didn't think spies had such a bad rap
I've got a bad feeling about this show
I hate walking through here
Here we are
Look at all these people
Have a seat in order
Enjoy the show, guys!
My ass hurts
The following play titled "The Return of Wanderer" was organized by the GIA theater group
This has nothing to do with spies
Enjoy the show
You know what?
Wild Bomb
Lossy
Konya Ga Yamada
That's a good Udon noodle, isn't it?
You're not kidding
That was a big lunch, but what's your favorite?
Konya Ga Yamada
And you got Beef Bowl
And the Soba noodle
Konya Ga...
How much is enough?
That's way too much
You need some help
Excuse me, more water, please?
Takayuki Kinoshita
Excuse me
I love your Udon noodles
Just looking at this place, you would never know
But now I know
Thank you so much
Anyhow, I finally saved enough money to make some renovations to the restaurant
Are you the only worker here?
I have two other siblings
Although, last I heard, my brother's been wandering around the country like a bum
But my sister does a fine job helping the restaurant
A younger sister?
Yes, she's a cutie
Did you get that?
Could you introduce her to us single guys then?
I don't know about that
Bibari Maeda
I'm home!!
Sorry about that
Welcome back, Bibari
Thank you
So she's your sister then?
What an old hag!
What did you say?
The cast gets to enjoy this part of the show without punishment
You can't treat the customers like this!
What's going on here?
Please come again!
Thank you!
Say Bibari, how come the delivery took so long?
Sorry about that, brother
Store owners wouldn't let me go
Again?
You better get married soon
Let me just invite myself inside
Yeah, he's definitely that type...
Perfect casting
He's someone who wouldn't let her go
Panzetta Girolamo
He says he likes me
Is that so?
Are you Girolamo-san from Italy?
Well, that aside,
Would you ask me what my hobby is?
Your hobby?
The act of making women orgasm!
Yes, they keep coming!
All you think about is women, right?
Yeah...
He's just like "Yeah"
Damn, here comes another guest
What's this all about?
Sorry for being late, and sorry for oh my...my bad
This is another guy who wouldn't leave me be!
Is that so?
You're only after her body though, right?
Mr. Marikku
It's not that at all
Her and I are destined to be together
Here, take a look at this as my proof
That's your famous "Hand Power"
So you are only after her body!
There is also another man who keeps bugging me...
and he's always touching his balls
A man who's always touching his balls?
There is also another man who keeps bugging me...
and he's always touching his balls
A man who's always touching his balls?
Excuse me
Note: He's pretending to be talking to somebody
"Who are you?"
I'm Tanaka Masahiro of the Rakuten Eagles
"Please Come in!"
Thank You!
Just awful
Aren't you Rakuten's pitcher?
Seriously, please marry this guy!
Tohoku Rakuten Eagles
Masahiro Tanaka
You know I'm engage to someone else!
Besides that, he does have a girlfriend!!
Really!?
Really!
Ryoko Sakaguchi
I found you!!
I found you!
Ma~chan, I found you!
I found him!
What the hell is she doing?!
Ma~ku~n!!
Ding!
How dare you treat the Japanese baseball's most coveted balls like that
Ma-kun!
Ryoko-chan!
Mah-kun is too much
Ma-Kun!
Ryoko-chan!
Ma~kun!
Haven't you had enough?!
You gotta be kiddin!
Sorry, but it smells in here!
It still reeks!
Ah~ so smelly~
Oh it's Bibari-san again
Yeah?
Me... Charlie!
What a PUNY voice!
I'm here...
Ichiro Ito
What's the problem?
There's a good chance that someone might have dine-and-dash...
I'm afraid both of your stores might be targeted as well...
we should hurry up and return to your store!
Ma-kun, learn to say NO
Didn't you say your Fiancée was going to come and greet me?
I think he should be hear any moment now!
He's late!
Yoichi Nukumizu
Another regular!
mizu-chan~~!
Mibari~~!
Mibari, who's this?
Let me introduce him!
This man is my Fiancée, Nukumizu-san!
Pleasure to meet you, older brother in law.
OLDER brother is laying it a bit thick on me there...
Let's go finish up our wedding plan!
Well I'm actually here to
ask you to forget about the wedding...
Kazuo Umezu
Kazuhiro Fujiwara
License
Takefumi Inomoto
Here comes the three Regulars!!
UAH!
God, he's way too skinny
Don't mind us
Get out if you're gonna be trouble
Ah, OK, see you...
Wait a minute!?
That man still owns us ton of money!
Well...I am...
We can settle this at our office
Wait!
This is MAN's business!
Hold up!
This one's a regular too...
Here comes the main star
I sulk at the knowledge of being a fool~
Cut it out!
This is MAN's business!!
Hold up!
Argh, this one's a regular too...
Here comes the main star
I sulk at the knowledge of being a fool~
Wait, wait, wait!
I'll have a bowl of Udon, please
Claudia Umemiya
Brother?!
Brother!
He really is your oldest brother??
I was just...
messing with you...
Glaring at script
I couldn't help eavesdropping...
How much is this amount he owes you!?
5 Million yen!
5 Million?
5 Million!?
Collectively, that's 15 million!
You probably couldn't tell but I used to play Ping-Pong in my youth
and that's not all!
I also study Karate
What about Karate!?
Inter... In, In, Intern.... Inter...
Stop screwing around already!
I ... I ... studied
I studied it on Internet Classes...
This is absolutely awful!!
Oh, let's see what you go then
Take this, Yeah take this! Who do you think you are scum!?
I won't let you off this easily next time
What in the world are you doing, Onii-chan!!!
Ah, here we are!
I found them!
Oh crap!
We're saved now!
Excuse me...
Dine and Dash Suspect - Captured!
It was you!!??
Yeah, take him in, he's been a nuisance!
I'm taking you guys in too!
Please don't fight in our restaurant!
Don't get involved in this
Please take this outside
Please stop this!
Shut the hell up!
Listen!!
I told you to stop, morons!!!!
My God...
I can no longer just let you guys do whatever the hell you want!!
Listen, Itoh!!
I don't care if you're ETC or ELT, but you're voice is like a friggen ghost!
Put some freaking life into it!!!
Speaking of life...
Nice job on building that disgusting looking house!
You're giving me the creeps, idiot!!
Hey
You, Tanaka!
Get over here, you're not safe either!
Mah-kun
What's this I hear about your special treatment?
While all your teammates report to the club at noon
You don't even have to report until 4pm??
You think you're some kind of big time celebrity?
Who do you think you are?!!
You're virtually a mute who don't even train anymore
Nukumizu who's been rehearsing since the dawn
only makes 1/10 of your salary!!
Just because you have a descent fast-ball doesn't mean shit to me!
Ah, I was so scared!
Intermission?
An intermission?
Wasn't that it?
I believe there's still more
Since there was no resolutions...
I'd say that was a good ending
Stage Assistant in Black is Standing By
Hey, did everything go OK?
I went around to pay off and apologize
That sound like a handful
You put me up to this!
But more importantly,
How did you end up with such a debt?
Her eyes are as good as dead
Well...
My friend was in financial trouble
and he made me a co-signer without my consent
Unfortunately, he's nowhere to be found
That's illegal
Well, the loan document says otherwise...
It's them again
Oh, here's the hero of the day
Let's see he can still work the wonder
Brother!
I had forgotten about him
Ah, it is him
Piccadilly Umeda
Um...don't mind me stepping in
Go home if you got nothing to do
Well, why don't I take her as collateral then?
Hold up
What the hell..??
I'm ready when you are!
It's the stinky one...
This is too much
Meow~
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Let's ditch this place, huh?
So everyone's involved?
Get'em!!
Ok, that's how it goes
How many more laps are they doing?
Amazing
Catch them!
Hey, catch them!
Hey, catch them...
I'm dyin @#$$@$%
Sounds like you really are ready to die, huh?
I have 5,000,000 yen here
Please take this and forgive us
That was to renovate our shop..
That's ok
My dream is that you stay happy
We can always make money again to renovate our shop
So this money is meant to be use now
Brother..
Brother
Brother!!
I'm not your brother!!
Give that to me
Wait
Something else again?
The voice is too soft
These guys are a fraud group that steals a lot of money
using fake IOUs
You don't have to give them money at all
That's
ALL!!
Brother!
My God
He's dead
That's fine
I'll take you guys to the police station
Brother, you don't have time to be dead
He's not dead
He is alive
Now you two can get married and our shop can be renovated
It's a win-win situation
Ahh
I'm gonna open pickles with this money
She meant to open up a pickles shop
We won't let you!
Everyone out
That's not the point
Why the hell we got OUT?
I'm fine with OUT
Ouch..
Did everyone enjoy it?
Shall we go?
Why does he ask that question?
This had nothing to do with spy
I'll go to the bathroom
I better go too
Buri Buri
Continuous farts
Taro Kida
Hey, I'm in the middle of peeing!!
Come on!
Surprised me
Can't be
Mr. Kida
Endo, you were  saved
Yes, I didn't see the moment
Give me a break
He's also the Japanese Mozart
Spy training 10 hours and 30 minutes
The assassin are even in the bathroom...
10 hours and 30 minutes since starting, the assassin are even in the bathroom...
5 men got no way out
The assassins are still coming
The assassins are continuously appearing to get the 5 men who have no way out
What the hell is waiting for us now?
That was handful, wasn't it?
We have the (Hamada) doll here
Yes
Yes, it is here
Hamada-san doll?
He will still appear in later clips but...
It's funny in any pose
Yea, it is
That's well made
Such a fashionable pose
Just some additional information,
this wasn't made in Japan
License
Kazuhiro Fujiwara
Takafumi Inomoto
It was made overseas
It was ordered from S. Korea
And it was made by someone who doesn't know Hamada-san
Amazing
And this isn't cheap, correct?
300,000 Yen (approx. $3,000 USD)
The real guy is worth about 180,000 Yen ($1,800 USD)
How cheap!?
Cheap!
You got a cheap price tag on you
Regardless, this is very well made
Shall we move on, Matsumoto-san?
NEXT!
Hey, what is this, really?
They are already past 10 hours and 30 minutes of Spy training
The 5 men have reached their limit
There are few words exchanged
Protect Japan from World Threats!!
2010 year-end special
The LDP Policy Chief ·The former Defense Minister
Shigeru Ishiba
Everyone, good evening
I am Shigeru Ishibashi, the former Defense Minister
This year, we had quite a lot of problems regarding military security
Today, we are going to discuss a theme of
"Protecting Japan from world danger"
Eh!? Seriously?
So let's invite today's guest
Great, isn't it?
Hideaki Onishi
Military commentator
Onishi Hideaki
Military commentator..
Thank you for coming today
My pleasure
Nice to meet you
Wow..
It's a pleasure to have you on board
Thank you so much
We have a lot of questions for you today
so please let us know your opinions
As we delve into the topic of national security,
we must first discuss about the weapons
whether it be an aircraft,
or military vessel
Otherwise, the discussion about national security would be a baseless one
But first, I have something for you
please take a look
Do you know what this is, Onishi-san?
Yes
Battleship Nagato
By the way, what is this ship called?
This?
This is..
Eh..
Battleship Asahi Newspaper
Ah...
is that so
Well...
Battleship Asahi newspaper
Ah...
Ok
You mean that...
What made you think so?
Because there is a Asahi Newspaper flag
Ok...
This is a flag for Imperial Japanese Navy
Oh..
Then..
I ask you what Japan should do for the world,
I'll get right to it
What do you think about PKO?
Eh..
Well...P...
Without
PKO...
games...
wont finish
Yes...
Yes
I think your answer got straight to the point, but
By the way, what does PKO stand for?
P-man (bell pepper)
Ketchup
Pi..
Pine
Jimmy's got an unfair advantage
He's totally clueless that Jimmy
Jimmy-san, this isn't fair
Let's move on to the next topic,
"Piracy in Somalia"
I would like your opinion on this issue
Well...
Gambling...
The officials are too involved in gambling to...
Well...Ah, yes...
As we're about to welcome the new year,
I'm expecting an honest and frank discussion
So please don't use this as an opportunity to joke around
No, I'm taking this seriously
Now, I hadn't heard anything about "gambling"
What is your source for this information?
Well...
I have
I heard it from the Prime Minister
By the way, who is our Prime Minister?
Kan Chokuto
I'm saying it with an accent though
Out of control
"Chokuto"?
So he read his name as "Chokuto"
You're talking about Kan Naoto, are you not?
Who?
Kan Naoto
I am...
I am aware of Mr. Kan...
Ah right! That's him!
Kan Chokuto!
So you heard it from him?
Yes, Mr. Kan Chokuto
I can only imagine
the Prime Minister has come to you to seek some advice
What were some of his inquiries?
Well, he talked about his wife...
Ah, I see...
He has his own issues like all of us
As a long time friend of Mr. Kan
How would you describe him as a person and a husband?
His marriage is loveless
You understand what you've just said?
Yes
I'm terrified to ask further questions...
Thank you very much
Protect Japan from World Threats!!
Fin
I barely made it
That was a lot of talk from him
Endou, how much "Life" you got left?
"Life"
"Life"?
Man, I'm so embarrassed
If you started with 10 hearts representing your life force,
how many hearts you got left?
I don't get your question...
Are you serious?
Serious?
You guys got that, right?
Of course
I gave you an ample explanation
"Life"?
L..Life...as in "Living?"
You know, like in those shooting games,
you get heart marks representing your vital signs, right?
And you lose a heart when you get hit
And once you lose all your hearts, you die, right?
Game over
So I was asking how much life you have if you initially had 10
Listen guys
This facility keeps notorious criminals locked up here
Like prisoners?
Right, pretty dangerous ones
No, thank you
Well, it's a learning opportunity
Spy Training
Face Dangerous Criminals
Haven't we already seen enough criminals?
I'd say I have 3 Lives left
You don't have much left then
What's "Life" mean anyway?
Is that a gamer's term?
I see they keep these guys far away
Here's the first room
What?
You mean there's more than one?
Here we have
a criminal hooked on impersonating celebrities
Let's go in
Damn...
I get it now
Yamasaki first
Yamasaki, come this way
Very eerie and terrifying
Alright then
To become an elite spy
What?
You have to act like a chameleon
It calls for more practice!
Impersonation No.1 Prisoner
Croquette
Alright then
To become an elite spy
What?
You have to act like a chameleon
It calls for more practice!
Impersonation No. 1 Prisoner
Croquette
Cinderella Honeymoon
Hiromi Iwasaki
The cast laughed but continue watching without interruption
This was harsh
We had to watch this right in front of us
Amazing
Applause
Naomi Chiaki
We had VIP seats
Yes, front-row seats
He picked up that fake mole off the toilet
This isn't fair at all
Not fair at all!
Noncommittal Venus
Jyunko Sakurada
Hold Me Tonight
Toshihiko Tahara
OK, I'm done
She Awaits
Hiroshi Itsuki
He never does that
Seriously...
Yosaku
Saburou Kitajima
What a cliffhanger!
Last Advice
Tetsuya Takeda
Can he do this normal?
I guess he can't help it
He's talented though
That should do it
I'm on my way to becoming one of the elites
But he's back by popular demand!
Dragonfly
Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi
We're gonna hear about this
He's gonna hear about this one
I think he fell asleep
Of course, we are
Yes, he needs to be locked up
Well, you're about to see the most dangerous criminal
Don't let your guard down
Line up like the last time
Who's this?
Most Dangerous Criminal
Shin Onii
Come this way
Line up like the last time
Who is this?
Most Dangerous Criminal
Shin Onii
He's notorious for faking his identity
as you just saw the other guy do
Don't take this guy lightly
Please proceed
Yes, sir
First up, Kesisuke Kuwata
Impersonation of Keisuke Kuwata
I want to travel to space
I don't get him!
What kind of intro is this?
And he goes, "The earth is gorgeous!"
Well, that's fine
Is he supposed to be Kuwata-san?
Who is he supposed to be?
Do you know who he is?
We have to get out every time?
How about just one big slap after he's done?
How does he not know who Keisuke Kuwata is?
He should know who he is!
Proceed with Keisuke Kuwata
Impersonation of Keisuke Kuwata
Since I was so hungry,
I hit the Ramen shop
And I ordered their specialty ramen
And it was very good
I asked the cook what his secret is to make such great ramen
He said it's a secret
But I really wanted to know
so I could cook it at home
It sort of reminds me of
the flavoring condiments I used to...
How creepy is he?
It's just "him" talking, right?
Go ahead and impersonate Antonio Inoki
Impersonation of Antonia Inoki
Gulp
The beer I had the other day definitely hit the spot
Isn't he freaky?
This is rough
What's up with him?
This guy's no joke
Let's see Lupin the Third, please
Impersonation of Lupin the Third
Which jewelry store should I hit today and...
have some fun?
This is an impersonation?
As much as I like jewelry
Hey, lady over there!
What jewelry do you like?
Here's some money
But now you owe me a sexual favor
Well, how's that for a story?
Incredible
What the hell is he talking about?
That was the best one
Why not check back on the first man you saw?
We already watched him
Yes, we did
He's ready to do another
Yeah, he's become someone else
Who?
Goroh Noguchi in fast-forward
Summer Night Dream (Fast forward)
Goroh Noguchi
Don't eat that!
Amazing
Exits and Flees
Get him!
Apprehend him!
Well, there he goes
That was one scary image
Oh well, he got away
You can't just let him flee
He's gone
OK, then
Well, we're definitely OUT
That almost put me over the edge
He completely owned us
He's a force to be reckoned with
For spy trainees, not even dinner is an easy task
I was amazed how he could just do anything he imagined...
Listen guys
It's about dinner time but
this is still part of training
So are you familiar with this toy?
I hate that scary game
Yeah, I've played with that
It's taxing on my heart
Watch Dog Bow Wow
Grab a bone from the dog's food bowl without waking him up
Your dinner is on the line!
Each bone has a dish's name written on it
Whatever you pick becomes your dinner
Take turns picking bones for tonight's dinner
Should he bark at you, your dinner items get confiscated and the game is over
The rest of you will be served the items written on the bones you grabbed
The loser will have zero dishes for dinner
This will train you to be more focused
Good luck
The pressure is on
I'm going to leave him here, so start whenever you're ready
Furikake (Rice condiment)
Mezashi...
Potato salad
Do we get rice?
Yes, you'll get a bowl of rice
I would love the Pork Soup
Doesn't matter, you gotta pick the ones on top
Go ahead
Order of Picking
1.Matsumoto
2.Hamada
3.Yamasaki
4.Tanaka
5.Endou
Matsumoto
I got Potato Salad
Potato Salad
That's a good one
Well, I don't think it's such a good dinner item...
Yeah, I would want that too
Hamada
Mezashi
Excuse me, but could you...?
This is too important not to focus
This makes your dinner
Yamasaki
I got Pork Soup
Pork Soup
Yamasaki
You picked a good one!
That's all I would need
Tanaka, your turn
Which one do I go for...?
Good items are buried in there
Right, the ones we want are way too deep
I got Pickled Radish
Tanaka
Pickled Radish
Well, it's only the first round
I'll go next then
Oh, I see something
I want the Yam Tempura
Endou
Yam Tempura
You picked a good one
Thank you!!
Matsumoto
Potato Salad
This Dried Seaweed looks like an easy pick
I can't do it!
What's up with "Fruit bowl"??
Must the rule apply here, too?
It appears that way
That's good
Keep that up!!
What's this?
"Pittan"
No, that's "Peetan (Century Egg)"
How do you NOT know that?!
I'd say you can hit them harder
Matsumoto
Potato Salad
Furikake
Oh man, I wish I got that!
Matsumoto
Potato Salad
I'd be happy with these two items
These could be my dinner
Stops
He almost woke up!
He stopped snoring
Well, there's nothing for me to pick
I might point out that you're laughing too
You're having too much fun
You serious?
You were like a little boy just now
You gotta be more serious
Atta Boy!!
Keep that, let's keep that form!!
Bump!
You could've woken him up with that banging
How about "Spicy condiments"?
Hamada
Mezashi
That would be good
That made me jump
Ah
I didn't mean to laugh
It's tough not to laugh
Very easy to laugh at that
Especially when it happens to someone else
What do you say, Fujiwara-san?
You'll be left hungry with what you have so far
I'm granting you one more chance
Thank you
But I'm confiscating Hamada-san's item
Of course, and we get to keep ours, right?
Hamada's "Mezashi" gets confiscated
It's Yamasaki-san's turn
He just stirred this up a little...
Right, the bones got rearranged
Yamasaki
Pork Soup
I can't see what it is, but I'm going for it
I got it
You set the next person up good
I got the "Steal"
Yamasaki
Pork Soup
Steal
You can take anybody's item
Please, don't hide yours
Endou, what do you got?
I don't have anything super
He has "Yam Tempura"!!
Yam Tempura?
I don't think this is that great
I got these two...
You got "Potato Salad" and "Furikake"
Well then,
I'm taking your Tempura
Endou
Yam Tempura
You serious?!
You got a good one
Endou
Hosei-san, you gotta be kidding!!
Tanaka
Pickled Radish
Pudding
I got the Pudding!
Endou
Hijiki
Despite the "Steal" hoopla, the cast successfully replenish their dinner items
Matsumoto
Potato Salad
Furikake
Black Beans
I'm not into this one
Not one bit!
Hamada-san, you're still at zero dinner items...
I'm going for the "Dried Seaweed" then
You'd better grab what you said you will!!
Don't worry
Hamada
Dried Seaweed
I saw zero focus in the way you picked that
What?
Were you laughing?
He sure is enjoying this game
Nice Hit!
But you can still hit harder!!
I know you can!!
It's gotten really brutal...
You can hit harder, I know you can!!
SHUT THE HELL UP!!
Too much horsing around
Let's see what you can do
Good one!
Yamasaki
Pork Soup
Yam Tempura
Miso Glazed Item
Yamasaki, Tanaka, and Endou's dinner items
Tanaka
Pickled Radish
Pudding
Pickled Shallots
You've got way too many pickled things!!
Endou
Hijiki
Fruit Bowl
I got the "Fruit Bowl"
I see "Fried Prawns"
But the "Kouya Tofu" is covering the "Fried Prawns"
Man, I haven't had tofu in awhile
Who gives a crap whether you've had tofu recently
Of course, we are
I'd say it was more Matsumoto-san...
That's scary hard
They're hitting hard
The hitting has gotten harsh at this hour
Matsumoto
Potato Salad
Furikake
Black Beans
Don't put any weight on that, or else...
I'd say you have enough items for dinner now
Kouya Tofu
I'm good at this
Wouldn't you say he's laughing now?
Got it!
"Peetan!!"
How many times did we have to point that out, huh?
Do you ever learn?
Why do you gotta laugh every time you pick one?
Good one!
But you can still hit harder!!!!
I bet we're seeing some good ones now
Yamasaki
Pork Soup
Yam Tempura
Miso Glazed Dish
What's that?
Kinpira Gobou (Burdock roots)
Kinpira Gobou
Mine's turning into a gourmet meal!!
Tanaka
Pickled Radish
Pudding
Pickled Shallots
I got Dried Sardines!
Dried Sardines
All of your items are cheap
I can see "Hamburger" now
It's still way too buried though
The dog will get you if you put any weight on it
This will be big if I can get it
Endou
Hijiki
Fruit Bowl
I wish I had longer nails for this
So, you're gonna make that move?
Damn it, how come I don't have a split finger tip?
Wow, that's a bold move
If my finger tip was split like this...
Could you please be quiet?
Serious?
Sliced Cheese
This was the only one I could get
I don't see how you got that
I got "Cheese"
Your finger tip must be split or something...
I'd say this other tofu is the easiest to pick but
Matsumoto
Potato Salad
Furikake
Black Beans
Kouya Tofu
I'm afraid I'll end up with all "Old-Fart" dishes
Nice hit!
You just hit the back of my thigh
Matsumoto
Potato Salad
Furikake
Black Beans
Kouya Tofu
He's got it
Miso Soup
Gotta be kidding me!
Seriously...
I'm going for that "tofu" piece then...
How sucky are you at this game?
No doubt
I more or less jumped...
Well, that was...
I know you can do better
"Skill Up" yourself!!
Unfortunately, Hamada, I'm confiscating yours
Dinner Consists of Their Picked Items
Upon training, each casts prepare their late dinner
Mine looks pretty healthy after all
Hamada-san, this is yours
What the hell is this?
Itadakimasu
Matsumoto
Potato Salad
Furikake
Black Beans
Kouya Tofu
Miso Soup
Delicious!
Yamasaki
Pork Soup
Yam Tempura
Kinpira Gobou
Miso Glazed Dish
Endou
Hijiki
Fruit Bowl
Sliced Cheese
Miso Soup would be perfect...
I agree
Pork Soup would be good, too
Tanaka
Pickled Radish
Pudding
Pickled Shallots
Dried Sardine
I wouldn't mind giving you a piece of black bean
You laughed, huh?
Why didn't you just give it to me?
That's a good one!
You're on the roll!
Not a bad roll!!
Time is 9:30pm
After dinner, the cast has a tea break
My butt hurts
Endou, how about something to drink?
Why don't you have some Suga Tea?
Why did you have to ask like that?
You laughed just now
Yeah, you were laughing just now
You think so?
I thought I was more or less put off by his question
I thought I did a good job responding to his question
GIA Special Elite Team is in the facility
I'm sure we can learn a thing or two from them
Spy Training
Learn from the GIA Special Elite Team
Elite....
This way
Here they are
Greetings
Damn...
GIA Special Team
Make sure you learn from these guys
They are the elite?
This was a rough spot to be in
MSB consists of members who survived the world's chaos and strife
Leader
Kendou Kobayashi
Our talent is having an unlimited amount of will to live
No method of torture can get us to talk
OK, get ready then
I heard him say "torture"
Yes, he said "torture"
Check them out
There's no youth left in those bodies
Now don't be alarmed
Once you face numerous life and death situations,
like all of us here,
you're bound to morph into a perfect physical specimen
Please don't hit the back of my thigh
By the way, people
You're here to witness the results of our training
Bring it in!!
This is just a warm up exercise
But this device
belonged to the Soviet Union in the 60's
Vacuum Cyclone Launcher!!
Vacuum Cyclone Launcher
Torture Device which Sucks in Your Nose and Mouth
Iwao!!
Are you up for this?
Football Hour
Nozomu Iwao
Are you ready?
Don't be looking at me
How was it?
No need to be looking at me
No problem, sir
Kinoshita!
Takayuki Kinoshita
This should be a cake walk for you
Ready?
Not bad
Good hits
You OK?
I'm OK
Looks like he's short on oxygen
Let's bring out the next one
Ahh...
That's an elaborate machine...
This was used up until recently in Afghanistan
Patriot Interceptor: Pitching Harisen!!
Consider yourselves lucky
because the legendary Mr. Ueshima will demonstrate it for you all
Ryuhei Ueshima
Ostrich Club
Will you demonstrate for us?
Patriot Interceptor: Pitching Harisen
Large Paper Fan Smashes Subject's Head
You know nothing's gonna get me to "talk"
Thank you, sir
Will you scoot over?
Scoot back a little, please?
Move back a little?
Scoot forward a little
Bingo!
Wait, scoot forward a little
Get it right, already!!
I don't feel justified being slapped by that
Remember the rules
Are we ready?
Fire!!
That's a shot!!
Not good
That wasn't good
I believe there's a mistake
Are you OK?
He screamed "OUCH!!"
You can do this too
I heard you scream ITAI (ouch)
No, he said AITAI (want to get together)
Who do you want to get together?
How dare you ask me a question?
Right, we need to know our roles...
Amazing hit
Yeah, it was
Newcomers like us shouldn't be allowed to talk...
Then will you ask him on our behalf?
Wait a sec
I seem to be bleeding
Bring in the next machine!!
This is a "Red Partisan Snake"
from Papua New Guinea
Its potent venom can kill a cow within 10 minutes
Red Partisan Snake
Grab the snake and put it in a wooden box
Let's see who can take on this task
Yoshinobu!!
Yoshinobu Nakamura
Producer
Try it
Show us how you can catch it with your bare hands
and place it in the wooden box
Well then...
Put him in that box
Store him
Looking good
The snake feels threatened
I'd say the snake is trembling in fear!
I heard him go, "AHHHH!!!"
Great job!
*The snake is not poisonous
That was clearly a cry for help
Shall we move on?
Bring in the next machine!
Endless Milk Tomahawk
Catch the Endless Drops of Milk in Your Mouth
Takeyama!!
Cunning Takeyama
Ready?
Drink all of it
Good job
He's spilling it
He just spilled it all over the place
I wouldn't call that a success
Just to keep you guys in awe
Bring out the next machine!
Settle down, people
As you might already recognize, it is...
Scud Cotton Missile
Place the special cotton on the subject's butt and light it
Scud Cotton Missile!!
Haranishi!
Takayuki Haranishi
What an ass!
Are you good?
You got this
His ass feels nice
What the hell's wrong with him?
What an ass
Are you good?
You got this
His ass feels nice
What the hell's wrong with him?
He didn't light the wick
Stinks!
That stinks
Good job
What's with you?
What're you talking about?
What hit you?
It's clear that you're hiding something
The leader burnt off half of his eye brows
Nonsense!!
What happened to you, leader?
My appearance hasn't changed at all
I'd say you've proved enough
Panty Hose Balloon Bomb
Sorry I'm late
Hope I'm not too late
Rigorous training has affected his hormone balance
And now he's asexual
Chris Matsumura
Are you ready to go?
Special Attire Made of Hand Towels
Sighs
Put this on
Panty Hose Balloon Bomb
Pop the balloon inside the panty hose
I'm sensing a catastrophe
Panty hose balloon bomb
Engage
Why is he ignoring us?
Oh, he just looked at us
I think he's winking at us
His cheek bones are something else
Is he OK?
Is he alright?
Kind of resembles Large Head Hairtail
He didn't hold back
He went "Ahhhh"
He was definitely scared
That was one loud scream
It somehow made his face long
Alright!
Who's next!
"Swimsuit Giant Swing"
Swimsuit Giant Swing
Subject Gets Swung around Wearing a Female Swimsuit
What the hell?
Mr. Ueshima!!
Could you?
I got this
Mr. Ueshima
Show us how it's done!
He tossed him hard
That sounded awkward
Are you alright?
It's nothing short of a miracle that your body is still in one piece
Let us see it again!
This is no joke
Well, I take that back
He clearly said it's no joke
No way, this is nothing
Look at him laughing
Watch it!
Watch it, watch it!!
Awesome, guys
That was great
He ain't one of the elites for nothing
Next up is this!!
That's a huge prop
This isn't anything new to you
"A Human Watermill"
No man can endure this for more than three minutes
This torture device has been around for 3,000 years
And only one man has refused to "talk" during this torture
It's Mr. Ueshima!!
What's this?
If you would, please!
Look at him giving the dirtiest look
I can't reach...
You can't grab onto that?
Shouldn't he have a better grip than that?
I told you he's too short to be on that wheel!
He's way too short for that
A man of this caliber can take two revolutions, right?
And that's exactly what he's doing right now!
Mr. Ueshima!
Here's two revolutions
What the hell are you doing?
He ain't an elite spy for nothing
After an exhausting experience studying the elite spies,
the cast gets some down time...
Let me introduce to you
GIA's dog mascot
Spy Dog "Bond"
Spy Dog, Bond-kun
He works as one of the elite spies
A "Super Dog"
Look what he's capable of
Showcases His Skateboarding Skill
How do you like that?
Well, he's not coming back
Let's go then
That made me feel better than anything we've done today
Was he supposed to come back?
Ah, there he is
He is here after all
Let's go then
Here's Bond-kun, he's here
That's Bond-kun?
He seems to like us
I guess we can take him back...
Look, he can walk on two
We should invite him to our room since he's so friendly
He's rather large...
I remember him being much smaller
I wish I can remember what he looked like before
Let's invite him into our room
I didn't know he could walk upright
Right, he is
He's walking like a human
He was on skateboard on all four though
Well, I saw Bond-kun try to walk on all fours and then he stood up
At least he tried to walk on four legs...
That's a good one
Nice hit!
The back of his head is completely open though
Bow!
Bow, bow!!
So he really is jumpy
I admit I got scared but...
Good
Bow!
Provoked by the Punishers
What kind of reality are we in right now?
Me too?
Matsumoto busted out laughing, too
No, I just pointed it out
He doesn't like strangers
We're OK now
Don't worry, nobody's coming back
You don't need to run away
Why don't you go with them then?
Everyone, this isn't the real Bond-kun
I'm Bond....
No, you thought I was the Spy Dog
What the hell...?
Gaki Members!!
I wish he got that right
You guys wish you....could...
could be this good
We should go
I knew it was him again
Honestly, I knew all along
Let's see the back flip again, it's been while
Serious?
From where should I have him take off?
Hamada Action Figure
Wait a sec
You were smiling, too!
No, I wasn't at all
Tanaka, you're guilty, too!
No, sir
Nice hit!
No sir
Not one bit
First of all, this is already...
Nice physique
Why was he put away in that pose?
I don't like this
I found him that way in the drawer
He looks sharp
Seriously, it was like that already
Another great hit
Good, really good
He's become a stud
Why did that crack us up so bad?
He looks cool doing that, right?
And that makes it funny
He's got that perfect body
Right, the perfect body
Why the hell do you have so many paper cups?
Well, I'm a little curious about the Suga-Tea
Since there's so many, can I go ahead and fix them for you guys?
Suga Tea
I don't want any
No, thanks
I don't want it either
Well, since they're all here...
I'm fixing them!
Why do we have to drink it against our will?
I don't know why he wants all of us involved...
I'd rather drink one as a group
Why not?
This looks sketchy
I think they're all same flavor
Matsumoto heads to the restroom
This isn't the same as last year's
It was Tonkotsu soup last year
That's right, the ramen soup
I told you I don't want it
What the hell am I smelling?
Will you try it?
When he comes back we should tell Matsumoto-san the tea tastes good
What a jerk
I see
It makes sense
It isn't bad compared to last year's
What's this?
Suga-Tea
It isn't bad at all
I think everyone agrees
I don't want it
It's good though, right?
Let me see you have a sip then?
I already had some
Have another sip then
Yama-chan, finish what you've started
I'll have some then
Suga-Tea = Super Hot Ramen Oil
Well, it's palatable
Cut the bullshit, idiot!
I admit that was funny
But I held it in
Grab a tissue
Yama-chan, find some tissues
They're hitting us harder
Well, it didn't look right in the first place
Why don't you guys enjoy some coffee?
That's random
Coffee Service
But why coffee?
Is this a trick?
No, there's no trick to this
Well, OK, I'm OUT but...
What the hell was that for?
Sorry, Matsumoto-san
Let's get you into the bath to clean up
Right away
What a pain...
Endou, you stink, you need to hit the bath too
Matsumoto and Endou Hit the Bath
The way this story unfolded was...
Just the two of us?
I'm scared...
You know it's a setup, right?
I'm sure it's...
No way, it's nothing
It was too awkward
Imagine that you're suddenly told you "stink"
Seriously, what's gonna happen to us?
Come right in here
And get changed over there
What's going on here?
There's a hot bath ready for you
We're bathing for real?
I wonder what's going on at the bath?
Something's fishy
That transition was not smooth
We can bathe here?
Please, go ahead
Man, I'm cold
Extremely cold
Wow!!
It's freezing!
Man, it scared me!
That's a big bath!
Female Guests Join
Let's get in quick
It's nice and warm!
Asian
Azusa Babazono
Harisenbon
Haruna Kendou
This feels nice
This is the perfect way to wind down from a long day, isn't it?
So the girls pretend to not see you?
Did you get a haircut?
Your hairstyle changes a lot
Well, I cut it maybe once every other week
That's a lot
Ignore the men and have "Girl Talk"
I get a hair cut maybe once a month
You must be perverted then
Cut it out!
Tomochika
I wish you guys invited me
See?
Something is going on at the bath
Somebody must be there then
There must be
Yama-chan, since the focus is on them, I bet we can laugh all we want
Tanaka, go ahead and laugh
I'll join you, too
You swear you'll laugh if I do?
Yeah
See?
We're so SAFE
They're busy with the bath
Go ahead, Zaki-san
See, I'm SAFE
Wow, laughing is no problem
You're spared, Hamada-san
How did you get away with that?
Bang!
He hit the chair
He hit the chair instead
I felt nothing
He just hit the chair
You got lucky
You know I carry Hichimi Spice in my purse
You mean Capsaicin
Excuse me
Rubbing Endou's leg
That's not fair, right?
Do you guys have a favorite place to visit?
I go back and visit my old schools
School?
They're places that remind me
who I am and how I got to be here
I see, you said "school!"
What'd you think I meant?
It's a place where I can better understand myself and...
where I can come to terms with things...
and be thankful...
What a pain in the ass
How many times do we...
What is this all about?
What is going on here?
Haruna, people must say you're looking good these days?
Ah
Can we be excused, please?
Can we go now?
Seriously, I've had enough of them
Forgive me, please
It's been 14 and a half hours since the start
Time to meet THAT guy
Hello, everyone
Agent
Seiji Chihara (Chihara Bros.)
So this is how it is
What do you you want?
Fujiwara told me to come here
And sit right in this chair
Read that
OK
(Letter from Fujiwara)
Listen, guys
I sent Seiji to liven an otherwise the boring five members
During "Seiji Time," only he is allowed to laugh
Seiji is to stay there until told otherwise
Did you get that?
But why would we want your ass in here?
What's wrong with me??
The air in here is surprisingly stuffy, huh?
I don't know what you were expecting...
I see, you're the feisty one
Yeah, very feisty
We have no idea what's happening outside this building
Is there anything big going on outside?
I heard this yesterday
in the green room
from Kawashima
Wild Bomb - Kawashima
Ku-chan?
Right Ku-chan,
he said he almost lost it at the "Sanma Goten" TV show
He didn't answer my question
That's not what we were asking
That's not news worthy
We were looking for real news
Way to go!
Nice!
Does it hurt your butt?
Yes, it really does hurt
Whose ass looks the most bruised?
Well, not everyone turns red at the same rate...
OK, that's true, but whose butt is the worst?
I'd say Tanaka
Let me see it
OK then, I was kind of curious myself...
He got Thai-Kicked twice
Get closer to Seiji
I bet it's in horrible shape
Nothing
Is that so?
See, it's perfectly fine
Really?
You got some work cut out for you
Seiji, stop laughing
I thought it'd look more bruised!
I was hoping for "the proof"
I'm sure the viewers were hoping the same
So it was such a let down to see a normal looking butt
How about you, Matsumoto-san?!
Why the hell do I have to show you my ass, moron?!
Why're you disrupting the flow? Get over here!
You didn't even try to hold in your laugh
Nice hit
Why do I gotta show my ass?
Why not? It's just an ass
I'd say my ass is pretty red
Nothing!
Not even slightly red
Why are they showing a full shot of my ass?
I'm just laughing like nobody's business
You too, Hamada!
I don't think so
No, this isn't good
That guy hits hard
Yeah, he swings really hard
That was one hell of a hit
He needs to aim better
Hamada, let me see it!
Don't be an idiot, that's never gonna happen!!
Seiji
OUT for being "too much of a half-ass"
What the hell?!
This is against the rules!!
Because you're a half-ass
Hit him with full force!
But you said I was exempt from the rules!
Yep, you laughed loud alright
You laughed so hard
As the next day approaches,
another annoying guest comes forth
Shoji Murakami
I just dropped out of a match...
But don't worry about me!
I'm also part of the GIA team!
Boy, I'm exhausted
I couldn't see his open-chops anymore
He's a wrestler
Am I bleeding?
I have Gingivitis
Not from the match?
What's your name?
How sweaty are you?
May I have your name, please?
I'd say this is as good as taking a bath
I'm Sho-chan
Don't you have a wrestling name??
I was ordered to spy on the "Wrestling Association"
And the chairman took a liking to me
I've been stuck doing this for the past 40 years
That's a long time
But anyway,
I found you!
Wrestling Assoc. Chairman
Reiji (Nakagawa Family)
Chairman!
Sho-chan!!
You can't just take off like that!
What're you doing?
Don't scare me like that!
Seriously, I heard that you just quit
Why?
Chairman, I can't do this anymore
No need to quit
Yes, I'm retiring
No, stay with it
Really, I'm done with it
Stay
Why?
We have tons of strawberries for you
Strawberries
They're super sweet, too
Well, you're not putting much effort into wrestling these days either
What do you mean?
I'm doing a lot for the company
Cut the bullcrap
That's not what I heard from the manager of the Gohanda Bar
Who?
The bar manager
Sho-chan, she's not the manager there
She's only an assistant manager
Assistant manager?
She wants to be the manager but the current manager's so stubborn
and won't give up her responsibilities
But she needs the assistant manager to deal with the younger employees there
There's a lot of confusion there,
and I said, "Why don't you become the manager?"
And she said to me,"Chairman, I don't have enough money
to become the manager."
So I told her I can cover the cost
I'm just throwing away money at this point
What's so funny?
What's he laughing about?
What's with this everyday conversation?
And he's just laughing away
What's with these two guys?
If you wanna talk about the assistant manager, then I have something to say
What do you got?
When you get inside the ring,
You have to get the crowd going, you know?
Yeah, to get the crowd on your side!!
You mean I gotta grab the microphone?
You know, like Antonio Inoki when he rambles about the poem "My Way"
Like, "Once you take this path then you gotta..."
But I'm already doing that
If you take this path here,
you'll get to Tamachi High Lane,
And hang a right there
And you'll see a convenience store on your right,
as you reach Tamachi station...
What the hell are you talking about?
Where is it?
What's that?
Well, that's what I do...
What is this all about?
So exactly where are you heading?
Talking to an audience isn't as easy as it sounds
Why don't you do my old bit?
When I was a wrestler
You wanna hear it?
So I'd enter the ring and say...
What's he trying to pull?
I thought I was SAFE
Ah, they got me!
What exactly are you doing?
What exactly are you guys up to?
Will you guys leave, please?
[Mimics Cantonese]
Ring Speech Continues
What're you doing at this hour?
We're not gettin' anything done here
Should we split?
Where to?
To that bar we've been talking about!
Chairman, I won't ever let you down
That was a lot in one sitting
They had that well rehearsed
15hrs and 30min have passed
The Rigorous Training Has Tested Their Strength!
And there's more "Laughing Assassins" on the way!
Many amazing things happened
What's up with Shin-Onii?
Shin-Onii
He was kind of scary this time
Don't be showing him to your kids
Kids will cry if they see him
You were in the bath longer than that, right?
That was a long time...
Co-Ed Bath
Listen to me...
Think about this, we were essentially being
sexually harassed by female comics
who are our juniors
What was I supposed to do?
I didn't get the point of it
This will be the last transition of the night
Why me?
What a pain!
Please set us up
WoWoW!!
That was a strong finish
The end of the training slowly approaches
No, really...
No more...
Listen guys
They're holding an event for a beautiful pop group
Let's go check it out
How does this relate to becoming a spy?
It doesn't relate at all
Well, Spy...Spy...
Well, the group consists of beautiful spies...
So they're from GIA?
That's right
Let's go check them out
Observe the Pop Group
Spy Training
Those actors from the play were also from GIA??
That's correct
Why didn't they just put the two acts together then?
We're heading back where we were before?
That's right
It's really dark out
Ladies and gentlemen
Tonight you will witness the most beautiful pop group
It's nothing short of a miracle!
They're known as
Beauty of the Times
Kazuko Kurosawa
Morisanchu
Nankai Candies
Shizu-chan
Oniyakko Tsubaki
Harisenbon
Haruka Minowa
How annoying...
Asian
Miho Sumida
How beautiful are we
A God given perfect body
We're gonna show it tonight
And I'll let you take this home
Right now, you can
Say it out loud
Anyone can
Feel free to
I hate that dance
How irritating...
She's too big to dance like that
They're the "Way Too Beautiful" Bishojo Jidai
What's this all about?
Who's more beautiful than this group representing a new era?
This is what their fans have been waiting for all day
Here's a gift for you!
It's Sexy Time!!
A lucky member of the audience will be chosen
One lucky fan will receive a sexy gift from the group!!
to receive a sexy gift from one of the girls!!
Who's up first?
Shizu-chan, will you pick the winner, please?
Go for it
And please come up on stage once you're chosen
Cut it out
Jeez, no
Hamada is the Lucky Fan
This is one ugly scene...
Let's get to the first "sexy time" gift
Presented by Shizu-chan and Oniyakko
Sexy Lipstick!!
Sexy Lipstick
Girls Apply Lipstick to the Lucky Fan
Are you ready?!
You made it?
Well, more or less...
Thank you, Shizu-chan and Oniyakko
Please go back to your seat
OK everyone, this is our last segment
Let's get together and...
Bang!!
Masahiro Chono Barges In!!
God Damn!!
A charming...
Bang!!
God Damn!!
There he is
Here he comes...
Look at you, Hosei-san!!
We haven't done anything, why is he here?
Look at your expression, Yamasaki!
I haven't done anything...
He's got nothing on us...
I'm in charge
of their production company
Some disturbing news was brought to my attention
One of you
has videotaped these girls
Pop Group was Videotaped!!
Ring a bell, anyone?
None of you, huh?
I see...
Nobody's coming clean...
Hey
Bring it in
This device
This device can detect a micro-camera
Criminal Search Begins
He's so intimidating
Something's not right
Beeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeep
Criminal Found!!
I knew it, but it was still funny
It was funny even though we knew the outcome
I think I was more relieved than anything...
There's always that "What if it's me?" feeling...
Is that so?
Hey!
Why don't you get up?
I did not videotape those girls
I don't care, stand up
I want to check you again
Now you have no excuse
Let me see it!
How do I show you when I don't know...
Where is the camera?
I don't have it...
Yama-chan, is that it?
That pen!!
What the hell is that?
Well, we all got the same pens
Not beeping though
No beep over here
No beep
Why is that beeping?
Check this pen
Don't be playing "Spy" behind my back
Yamasaki's Pen
What appears to be a normal pen
actually has
the micro-camera is installed
A Micro Video camera Installed Inside
A tool commonly used among criminals
It's widely used by criminals
I'm checking what's saved in that pen
Reveal the Pen's Contents
If you just came clean, we wouldn't have to resort to this
Is this what you do all the time?
No, sir
No way
You look like the type
who chases around young girls
No, sir, not at all
You've never come to this type of event?
Never
I never have, sir
You were never into these pop groups?
Never!!
Yamasaki Pleads His Innocence
You can't hide anything from me
If that pen is one of those high-tech micro cameras
then it will contain the footage I'm after
And it can be played back
Let's check it out
Inspection Starts
You did videotape them
Where is this?
No way...
What're you doing?
Wait, wait, wait,
Wait, wait, wait
Video Showing Girls Changing in a Locker Room
Guilty of Being a Peeping Tom
But why would you videotape them...
Hey!
What now?
I'm absolutely sure...
Yes, give me a second
OK, you just confessed
Wait
Come on up on stage
Bitch Slap Warranted for the Criminal!!!
I'm completely flabbergasted right now!
Get up here
Give me a minute, please?
Seriously, why me...??
Can you hang on a second, please?
Yama-chan, get this over with
Hosei-san, please
Get over here!
First, apologize
Apologize
Are you saying I'm off the hook if I apologize?
To them
Get up here
Say you're sorry first
Sorry
I'll never do it again
They're scared of you
And he's admitted...
Forgive me...
I'm sorry
Get over here, asshole!
This is a cruel punishment for such a late hour
Give me a second, please?
Seriously, I'm...
Ouch
Ouch!
Yama-chan!
Yama-chan, c'mon
Please just do this for us
Give us a break
Hosei-san, please
I understand your situation but...
You're not being courteous to your teammates
Give me a moment!!
Is there anyway I can get out of this?
Jeez, year after year...
But you just admitted
Accept it like a man
I confessed because you said you'd let me go
I didn't say that
Don't put words into my mouth
Give me a second, please
That tie is a little sketchy, too
You hiding something under there, too?
It's easy to grab onto you
Why're you fighting it?
Please, please, please, help me!
I don't want it
I can't do this
Get the hell up
What's wrong with your eyes?
Get up
But I'm really exhausted
You got a nice pair of shoes, huh?
You had zero strength left
Right, I had none
That's the funniest
How about a slap with his left hand...?
Well, I'm not making that decision but...
Could you use your left hand, please?
No punching though, no way!!
Get up
OK, I'm ready
Now, apologize to everyone here
Tell them you're sorry
I don't have all day
First, apologize
Say you're sorry
Apologize, asshole!!
Noooooo~, This is just terrifying
Please, I need to save my butt
I'm really hating this...
OK, time's up
Your time is up
There's no way for us to help you so...
They're right about that
Ready?
Close your eyes
I'll do it
Please, wait for my count
How dare you...asshole...?!
C'mon now
Do you realize how many times we're getting slapped?
How many times are we gonna get hit here?
Just get over here
OK, I'm ready for real
I'm not waiting for you
OK, OK, then wait...
I'll accept the punishment
But,
could you do it after i count to three, please?
Don't screw with me, asshole!
Get over to this side
Ready?
That must have hurt
Yes, it did
I'm sick and tired of you, asshole!
Get the hell out of here!
Let's go
Why did you bother videotaping THEM?
They sure despise you
After 17 hours of training,
their physical and mental strength have been long gone,
But it's time for their last mission
Attention, guys
It's finally time to prove
what you learned today
I need you to find the bomb hidden in the building
as well as find and rescue a kidnapped girl
I'm counting on you
Are we good enough?
Also, you may now laugh but don't become scared or startled
Take note of that, too
Middle of the Night Special Rule
Don't Get Scared   -   Spy
Disarm a Bomb in a 2nd Floor Office in the Annex
That's right after you got slapped
Rescue the Director's Kidnapped Daughter!!
Here's some walkie-talkies
Distribution of Walkie-Talkies
Wrist-Watch style Walkie Talkies are distributed for communication
Bomb Disarming Kit
A bomb-disarming kit is also provided
How did you set this up?
Why don't you start your mission?
You'll know what to do once you step out
You need to rescue the kidnapped girl
That's a huge mission...
Ah, here's this lighting again
Complete Lighting Change
This is already freaky
CO2 Gas Release
And it's freezing out here too
Hey, Tanaka
There he goes again
losing his cool
Why you?
This is a repeat from last year...
Man up or you're gonna fall down a lot
And be careful of the bomb kit
I know, but it's really heavy
Tanaka, get to the front
Can I please stay in back
This kit could be dangerous
It could fly out of your hands and hit Hamada-san
That would be a disaster
It would be a nightmare
We need to be on the lookout
"Secret" Trap
It's me
(God) (Monster Engine - Oobayashi)
You scared me
God, don't scare us like that!
"Secret" Trap
Why is he like, "It's me"?
Bang!
It's me
God (Monster Engine - Nishimori)
You better knock it off!
So it was you
I got you again
I'd never have guessed
We're bored out of our minds
So this is how two Gods horse around
Hey Tanaka,
You OK?
I'm OK
Say, "People of Lips"
Hold up
Who are you calling "People of Lips"?
I'm sure they're referring to Hamada-san
We used to be
the round and large
light forms
Is this some kind of code?
Round and large flashing object...?
Hold up, "People of Lips"
"People of Lips", hold up
Say it already
We used to be
the round and large
light forms
Yeah, we already got that
They're just repeating themselves
Wait up, "People of Lips"
I've just about had it already!
We got it already!
We used to be
the round and large
light forms
You've said that
We got it already
Why are they saying "People of Lips?"
And we're not questioning it either
Like we really are the "People of Lips"
This way, this way, guys
"Secret Trap"
Seriously, give me a break
I don't know how this walkie-talkie works either
3m high - Sukekiyo
That's just freaky
What the hell was that?!
That's real freaky
This isn't good
My stomach hurts
Hamada Laugh Track
I see the bomb
Where?
I see it
That was Hamada-san's high pitched laugh
I thought Hamada-san just laughed
No, it was a recording
Over there, I can see it
Bomb
That's what you have to disarm
Whistles from Wall
A suspicious person is approaching
Downtown needs to hide in the closet with the bullet-proof glass
The rest of you hide underneath the desk!!
You should be safe there
Under what?
I see under the desk!
We're supposed to hide in here?
Absolutely Safe Box
I guess in here
You gotta be kiddin' me
What a pain in the ass
Downtown-san, you're so visible
That makes all of us
Suspicious Person - Kai Atou
What're you gonna do?!! Hey!!
I'm scared, scared, scared, scared
What're you gonna do?!
How scary was that?
You're no longer in danger
Proceed to finding the girl!
Head to the ground level immediately!
"Secret Trap"
Bump!
Sadako Slithers from Under the Desk
Are we ditching the bomb then?
We don't need to disarm the bomb or what?
Tanaka Kicks the Bomb Kit and Injures his Foot
What happened?
He ran into...
Tanaka Rips the Wall
Tanaka, what's wrong with you?
Are you OK?
I'm OK
What happened to the bomb?
Off to the Ground Level to Rescue the Girl
I guess we're off the hook
"Secret Trap"
Tanaka, I fear for your safety...
Endo, could you carry this for me?
I shouldn't have this with me
Young Allosaurus
Tanaka~!!
You're awful
I had no idea you fell again
Looks pretty realistic and scary
I'm scared!
"Science-Kun"
Tanaka, he's in your TV show
Oh, man
That dinosaur was something else
Damn, it's him again
Yutaro
Hey
I've been expecting you
Here's a ticket for you guys
Come this way, please
I know that tool box is heavy
What's this?
What is this?
The "Be Scared and Sing Show"
What's that mean?
Sit here?
Not all of us
I'll just stand here then
Sorry about that
Don't worry about it
The "Be Scared and Sing Show" - Opening
Oh!
It's really her!!
Experience
Mari Hanmi
Emily Henmi's Mom
Stop, if you don't love me
Stop, don't kiss me
Stop, and let me go home
Let me hate you
Let me just go
She was the real "Mari"
She's all, "Stop~"
Countdown to Bench Collapsing
Proceed to your left
Where?
He said to our left
Bump
What's this?
That's not safe
Man, I hate being outside
It's freezing
Mysterious Character Awaits
The path is in terrible condition
Avatar
That isn't the theme song
Avatar~ Here we are~
Can't wait to tell you~
Ava-ta-tar
Feeling like a Virgin Bata
What's Bata?
OK, back to the verse
James Cameron
He's the director
Easily confused with Cameron Diaz
"Secret" Trap
What is this all about?
Seriously...
Who shot you anyway?
This is messed up
Tell me who shot him
I see a note over there
"One Member Must Enter the Phone Booth to Receive the Next Command"
Yama-chan, you go
If you would please!
Why is Yama-chan going in?
Well, because you're our "Image Character"
What do you mean by "Image Character?"
Do I have to close this?
Just leave it open
Is that OK?
He just has to wait for the call, right?
Right
"Secret Trap"
Pitfall
This scared us
Thank God...
You OK?
That scared me
I just saw your face right here
That was scary
A spectacular fall
I had to do a double-take
How scary
That's not safe
This isn't very safe
So no need to wait for directions?
There's no need to wait
Which way should we go?
I see an arrow pointing that way
Yama-chan, that was scary
I caught a glimpse of you
before you disappeared into the pit
Please stay inside the perimeter where the footing is better
"Secret Trap"
What's that coming at us!?
Here comes the "Star"
Wheel Gymnastic Pro: Akira Nishikino
That is amazing
Are you OK, Star?
I heard his knees scrape on the ground
Watch, watch out!
Be careful, please
Star, you need to be more careful
I think the Star is hurt
We're at the ground level
Man, what is this?!
Where's his daughter?
Ground Level Cemetery
She's somewhere in here?
C'mon, man...
You know what?
I can't run in this condition
Are we supposed to walk on this plastic wrap thingy?
We're going to slip all over the place
Look at the suspicious looking piles of sand...
Tanaka, you OK?
Do you wanna be in the front, Tanaka?
I don't think so
Nowhere's safe
There's another note up there
"Rescue the Girl with this Stroller"
The Girl is in the Building
So she's in here!
What? Serious?
I would say this is...
I'd say this is Tanaka's mission
I agree
I'm going?
So put her in the stroller?
She must be really little
One girl?
No idea
I'd say just one girl
A step
Don't worry, we won't leave you
How could you miss that little step?
Please don't leave me here, OK?
Kidnapped Daughter
So she needs to be in the stroller...
We all need to go in there then
I'm leaving the tool kit here then
Well, well, well, well... "Daughter?"
I'd say she's beyond the "girl" stage...
With the Girl in the Stroller, they Attempt to Escape
With Director's daughter securely inside the stroller,
they attempt an escape...
She's awake and alert
She's up
She couldn't be more conscious
"Secret Trap"
Her eyes are wide open
If you're up, why not walk on your own?
We should be good now
The mission is pretty much accomplished...
A Combination of Zombies and Explosions!
Not good
You fell again, Tanaka
This isn't cool
Matsumoto's left by himself!
That was totally uncalled for!
Wait up~!
WAIT THE HELL UP~!!
He's left on his own!
Not good
This isn't cool!
Wait guys
Tanaka, help him out with the stroller
That was seriously messed up
I was the only one pushing the stroller
The five members endured cruel and rigorous training
all day and all night to become spies
The end has finally arrived
OK, guys
Your day as spy trainees is officially over
You have all done well
Finally...
How was it, Hamada?
We made it without losing anybody
Matsumoto?
I'm the one who rescued that old hag
Don't forget the no laughing rule until you cross the front gate
It's not over yet
At last...
My butt has had it
My butt hurts...
Yours too?
No matter how many times we do this, my butt still hurts
I suppose there's no way to train for this
I'm the parent of an egg
My name is Piiyoko-chan
Pi, Pi, Piiyoko-chan
I am a duck, quack, quack, quack
Grandson of the Falcon
Kenji Suga
I am Piiyoko-chan
I get it, the egg hatched
This is the first slap of the new year
Congrats on your graduation
Naoki Tanaka, Congrats
Hosei Yamasaki, Congrats
Matsumoto Hi Shoshi Shan...
Congratulations
Hamada Masa Hi..Hyoshi-san
Congrats
Shozo Endou, Congrats
Why can't he say our names right?
Please join me in praying for our good health this coming year
Follow my lead, please
Yo~~
I am Piiyoko-chan
It hurts way more being outside
Shall we go?
Butt-Slap Counter
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
Hosei Yamasaki
Shozo Endou
Naoki Tanaka
Once again, we're competing against the "End-of-the Year Singing Contest"
Toshiyuki Tachikawa
Daiji Man Bro. Orchestra
"That's What's Important"
This year the spy trainees must not laugh
If you don't mind complaints from viewers
go ahead and show his junk
"This is how you like it?" - Muga Tsukaji
dances so his (or her?) brother can go to school
All it takes is Matsuko showing up
to terrify Endou
After numerous yelling exchanges
Nishiki and Katase never let up
Despite Happy Boy's upbeat shouting
"Wow!" never quite caught on
It's not that I'm sad that Chiaki isn't here
it's that now everyone knows my dating habit
It's sad when
Masatoshi, out of character, punches Yamasaki in the stomach
Instead of just angrily storming off,
he squeezed in a kick to Sakai
His suit got yanked off by a nice limo
And Itao kept howling, never letting go of his Bond character
Tanaka got caught by a fishing hook
while Sawamura regretted accepting this high-paying gig
Bibari is now in charge of the play
Claudia's acting is still horrible
Among the "has-been" actors,
Nakamura somehow fits in nicely
Nothing particularly terrifying came out of Hamada's desk
But it was irritating how Little Hamada looked so much like him
The Hand-Towel gang never gives up
they put their bodies on the line without running away
Koba almost loses it all
While Ryu-chan struggles
Bathing with girls you can't have
A girl makes a proposition and starts dancing
Every shot is a good shot for Chono, and that's important
One impersonator, almost too good
A lesser known impersonator, just winging it
Shibata with no make-up, smokes a cigarette
Taro Kida takes care of business in the restroom
Here comes Seiji who annoys the cast
And their tired bodies can't take any more of Murakami
Mari sings an awkwardly dirty song
Nishikino fails on his wheel
Once again, the show welcomes the new year
while we all laugh and get slapped
Nobody's getting younger, so staying healthy is the most important thing
Happy New Year
Here's to an abundance of laughs this year
It is finally over!
You guys better listen
What's going on?
Why was I the only one helping that old hag?
I'd say 99% of the zombies touched my shoulder
(Inaudible)
Seriously, give me a break
I'd say the funniest was when you fell down on stage
I was losing my footing...
I was losing it...
When Chono shoved you and you just fell on your butt,
I lost it
I thought, "That must be what's it like being a rag doll"
Did I look the part?
Are we on for next year, too?
But you gotta figure...
Arashi SHOULD be doing this,
ARASHI is a popular boy band
but they'll be singing on the other channel...
Why don't we enter the "Singing Contest" then?
Right, if we make it,
the cast from "Shouten" can take over for us
Do you think they can do this...?
They're all pretty old...
Not pretty old, really old
Thank you for your continuous support of Gaki No Tsukai