GakiFiles Subs
www.gakifiles.blogspot.com
Facebook: GakiFiles Subs
Translation:
Zurui
eChie
Spot Translation:
Vanilla
Timing:
SSSI
Chidegi
Dith
Typesetting:
SSSI
When repressed emotions resulted in mental breakdown
they found fulfilled ecstasy
Gaki no Tsukai Over-the-top series!!
"No-Laughing Airport"
That's you!!
The Famous Line Up To Issue Punishments
A String Of Celebrity Assassins Await Them
Shocking CA Training
Between That Person's Legs...
Tests Of Courage
Secrets Revealed
A Celebrity's Vicious Crime!!
The First Time In The History Of Variety Shows
A Whole Airport Will Be Used As A House Of Humor
I'm asking your name, damn you!
AHHH!!
NOOO!!
Chilling Terror
The Shouts And Screams Never End!!
Watch Until The Final Climax
It's outrageous!
Beat Kohaku!  This Is A Must Win 6 Hour Special!!
Hey wait!
Gaki no Tsukai New Year's Eve Special
No-laughing Airport 24 hours!
New Year's Eve Special
Downtown no
Gaki no
Tsukaiya Arahende!!
No-Laughing
Airport
Hours
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
The day has finally come for this year.
Yamasaki Housei
Has anyone been here before to watch this show?
It's a long show.
I see a few people.
Well, you all look healthy now.
But you'll be as good as dead in the end.
A few people were rolling their eyes.
Excuse me.
"Rolling their eyes?"
You got caught again.
Everyone was laughing,
as if rolling their eyes...
He's really not funny.
It didn't just begin now!
It didn't just..?
You guys are really being mean!
You not being funny didn't start just now.
So mean, really.
This year's stage is airport.
- Yes.
Yes.
Matsumoto-san, please start VTR.
Please.
Yes, because this is an annual event!
Yooooou!!
No-laughing Airport
It's been 3 years since the last time we saw the morning sunlight shining bright.
But the members..
Everyone's walking heavily.
Well..
No, that's not it.
Yeah.
I have a fracture on my leg.
Yes, right.
My doctor told me not to do variety shows,
not to even watch it.
Can't even watch it?
Aren't you just trying to get away?
I'd be rather happy if that was the case.
Matsumoto accidentally received a stress fracture.
The future is not as clear as this sky...
You can't even watch variety shows.
He said it's dangerous.
It says to wait here.
So far the weather looks good.
Yeah, if it was raining...
The first sunny day in the 3 years.
It's been 3 years?
Yesterday, it was raining right?
Last night, it was.
Something is coming
What's that noise?
I can't tell if it's real or just for show.
Yes, that's true. We can't tell at all.
I'm sure that is for show.
That's too strange.
Such a long intro.
That has to be Fujiwara, riding in back.
It seems so.
What is that?
I really can't see the point of this.
Me neither.
I kind of like it.
Even though it was already explained to us.
At this point, we still don't yet understand.
Why did he go there?
What?
He threw it away.
I'm popular..Good morning!
I'm so popular.
Is he a woman?
Popular..
I told him not to bring me flowers as it dies quickly.
Downtown's former manager
Fujiwara Hiroshi
But he still brings some every time I see him.
Your outfit is great again this year.
Your face is getting even more disgusting.
Year to year... now it's no better than a rice cooker.
Yamasaki...
Yes?
Why do you think I'm popular?
I guess it's because of your style. The appearance is good?
It's because I am a cabin attendant!
You can just see it from my outfit right?
I'm popular because I am a cabin attend.
Say it well.
He can't even say it.
I'm popular because I'm a cabin attendant!
CA.
This year's stage will be at the airport.
This year, everyone is going to be..
cabin attendants.  For short, it's "CA"
Excuse me,
but the sun is too bright.
The 5 members will be cabin attendants.
Newbie Cabin Attendants
will challenge 24 hour duties!!
They are going to challenge 24 hour duties, but one problem remains...
Matsumoto, I heard
about your leg...
Yes, I was strictly told by my doctor not to repeatedly stand up and sit down.
*Matsumoto received a stress fracture on his foot while
in training.   It will take 3 months to heal completely.
He said "This is not a joke." by looking at the MRI.
What was it?  What you deserve...
Stress... Stress...
Who deserves it?
This is the results of my effort!
What you deserve
Even though are stupid, you are the main character, so
we've prepared some help for you.
Come on!!
Scary.
They're scary.
Stair Servants
Matsumoto's personal SP
They're huge.
Scary.
He's snorting like "Hm hm hm hm..."
What are they doing?
When Matsumoto can't move, they will come to assist him.
Isn't it perfect?
I kind of want them to carry me at the stairs.
OK! Thank you!
"OK thank you."
By the way, I told you we will be cabin attend... What are you wearing?
You never said it correctly. Never once.
Well
we've prepared your outfits there. Can you change now?
Before starting CA duties
Changing into suitable outfits
First of all, they will change into suitable cabin attendant outfits.
Isn't it getting too cold to change?
This was a nice day though.
Why don't you respond?
Please come out in order.
Matsumoto.
Yes.
I'm glad to be first up.
First up is good.
What he deserves, Fracture CA
Normal uniform.
Everything gonna be great.
My leg is broken.
Sorry...
Yamazaki.
Yes.
You're cute, Yamasaki.
Amateur Comedian CA
Cute.
As a teddy bear.
Amateur comedian CA..
Endo.
Yes.
You're beautiful, Endo.
Handsome Super Perverted CA
No need for "Perverted"
Please try your best.
OK!
Tanaka.
Yes.
You're slender.
Tall and Dirty CA
You look like a Hollywood actress.
Shouldn't be dirty, huh?
Hamada.
Hamada! What's that?
Mini Skirt & Big boobs CA
Sexy!
You've grown very well.
I assume it's an I cup.
Yamazaki should do this.
What do you mean?
It's too sexy for prime time.
What the..
Never mind.
I'll explain the rules.
Could you stand in a row?
Come forward..
Let me begin.
One,
You will work as cabin attendants for 24 hours.
One, you are not allowed to laugh no matter what.
One, if you laugh, you will receive a punishment.
That's all.
Did you get it?
Alright!
Everyone, are you ready for flight!?
Are you ready for flight!?
Everyone... Are you ready!?
Are you ready!?
Persistent.
So, there is a bus stop over there.
No one responded!
I thought you would have another version if we didn't agree.
No, he didn't.
It's true, no one had agreed yet though
Can you stand in a line here?  The bus is coming.
Uh bus!
A bus is coming?
Shall we get on...
Are we going to?
It's coming.
Here it comes.
Sure enough, it has "Kurobikari" in the name.
Gasu Airline System.
Kurobikari.
Please look at this.
G.A.S.  Gaasuu Kurobikari Airline System.
This is the name of the airline you are going to work for.
Gaasuu kurobikari Airline System
The Gaasuu commute bus.
Suga Duck
With the Suga duck symbol on its body, this is a special bus for the GAS employees.
We are now going to the training school for cabin attendants.
Aren't you thinking like " Why not the airport"?
What is he's trying to say.
You just want us to say that.
We weren't thinking that.
For newbies like you,
Um..
it's still too soon to go directly to the airport.
Your thinking,
is bluer
than the sky
What the hell are you saying!
After reading his lines over and over, he's trying hard to remember.
What are you trying to say?
In his brain, all the pages are now messed up.
Let's go then.
As soon as you get in, the "No-laughing" rule is in effect.
Here it comes!
OK!
Talking here won't speed things up.
Yeah.
I'll go first.
This time, I am not going to laugh at all.
NOTE
That's... dangerous!
You can't laugh from here, once you step on.
Employees Already On The Bus
I saw something.
Where?
Hamada-san has something great.
What?
I'm not going to say it now.
But he has something great.
He's keeping Hamada's secret.
The bus departs for the training school.
What is in store for them?
Please check Hamada carefully.
Even now, he kind of looks like he's laughing.
Oh, yeah, he is.
Kind of.
I'm not!
It's because he said that!
Well, I really hope everything will be OK.
In the bus filled with tension, they are not allowed to laugh.
Alas, it won't be easy on them.
Arrival At A Bus Stop
So soon.
Yes, so soon.
I'm trying not to look at what is getting on.
OK! I made it.
Was this the first trap?
Banana Man
Shitara Osamu
Himura Yuuki
Ito Ichiro
Is this the first trap?
It's Matsumoto-san's fault!
Why?
You keep saying it!  "Currr"
His "Curr" is dangerous.
No no no..
It's starting now!
4th rule
Black army issues the punishments
What're you doing?
Zaki-san, was the first victim.
Hey, you know what?
Lately, I've been thinking, I like idols and actors but
don't you just love comedians?
Yes!
They are so funny and so cool now.
Comedian Groupie Trio
Comedians are becoming popular.
They're so cool.
Who do you like?
Hmm..
Kokado?
Kokado of Rocchi.
He's too plain.
That's why I like him!
What about Ichiko?
For me...
Who do you like?
Ichiko?
Takeshi-san.
Oh Takeshi-san!
He's too quiet!
Please don't do that... could you speak up?
Why say Takeshi-san..
What is it?
They are so rough!
I like him too.
Takeshi-san is cool.
But after all everyone likes Downtown.
Downtown?
I agree.
Downtown..
Too soft.
After all they are the top.
What is Downtown after all?
I thought about why they are so funny.
Did you?
- Yes.
Then I thought,
it's the Kansai dialect that they speak.
Many speak it.
He was pissing me off.
It's not that Downtown is funny.   It's their Kansai dialect.
You said it before!
Comedian groupie's opinion
Kansai dialect is making Downtown funny
We're hit in this packed bus.
Yeah, it was dangerous sitting there
By the way, I saw this on TV.
Do you know Gekidan-Hitori's Nakigei?
Yes.
- Yeah?
He can control his tears.
But that is..
I think we can do it too.
We just have to cry while saying something, huh?
Comedian groupie's opinion
Anyone can do Gekidan-hitori's Nakigei
Don't you think so, Ichiko?
Don't you think we can do it?
You just have to cry.
You should try, Ichiko!
How can I do it?
I can't remember
You can't... remember?
What?
I don't get it.
What are you saying?
Sad story?
Did someone
mention something?
To make you cry?
What do you mean you can't remember?
It's difficult.
Gekidan-hitori is awesome.
He's awesome after all.
Oh, I remember.
On batsu games that comedians do on TV,
Um.
Kuwagata Beetle.
Kuwagata Beetle?
-Kuwagata Beetle?
You often see them bitten by beetles.
- Yes.
As Degawa said somewhere...
It doesn't hurt that much.
I read it in a magazine or something.
Wanna try?
Comedian groupie's opinion
It doesn't hurt to be bitten by a beetle as seen on TV.
Yes.
Let's do it.
I have something good here.
Here.
These.
Lottery?
Good idea.
Today, I have it here.
Look.
Is it alive?
Yes, it is.
Japan Hirata Kuwagata Beetle
This.
Do you want to try?
- Yes.
They're scared.
This..
Let's do it on "Here we go."
Here we go!
Ichiko won
Ichiko.
Great.
Oh it's alive!
Yes it is.
Of course it is.
Keep still.
It has a smell.
OUCH!!
REALLY!
REALLY
HURTS!
It's stuck!
Kuwagata Beetle Doesn't Release Him
There's a hole!
It's bleeding!
Scary!
Now I'm crying... really crying...
It left a hole..
Now he's crying.
There's a hole!
This is not supposed to happen..
Wait..
He should've just cried earlier.
Ugh..There's a hole.
That's enough!
I hate it!
Wait Himuko!  Wait!
Himuko Got Scared and Ran Away
Himuko!
I did not laugh!
Why Hamada..
It's not fair that I get involved with his weird laugh...
My laugh is not weird.
You laugh as if I'm also laughing.
Like you're urging me to laugh.
I didn't do that.
It must have hurt, Ito-kun..
30 mins since the start of duty
Well, Hamada got away with a couple of laughs.
Are you sure?
No, I didn't.
I heard him making noise.
I didn't say that.
No, it was Yama-chan.
You just did it again.
You were laughing while saying "No."
He just made a funny face!
Hamada-san just made a funny face!
Let's stop trapping each other
That's dirty!
Give him the hardest hit.
Good one.
Let's not quarrel.
Between friends.
I didn't mean it.
Matsumoto-san's "Gurr."
That's bad, right?
They let it go.
What do you mean?
You were like this all the way through.
Yeah.
The one I've been doing since our debut?
That's enough already.
Quarreling.
That's one of negative spirals caused by repressed emotion.
There is a wall they have to clear.
Stopping At The Next Stop
He got off in the middle of nowhere.
Thief!!
A Property Crime Occurred!
Thief! Thief!
Where?
Underwear thief!
Thief!
Oshima Miyuki (Morisanchu)
Victim 1
Barbie (Falling Love)
Victim 2
Victims' Upskirt
Damn. That's dirty.
Miyuki
Barbie
How dirty!
Look at the butts
They're morons.
Long, too long!
These guys..
can't be helped.
Barbie-chan had lot of cellulite.
They are still at it.
They are still going.
Really?
So slow.
So full of stamina,huh.
I don't care but he laughed when I said "Full of stamina."
Yes, he did.
Yes, I think so.
I'll ban you from putting your hands around your mouth.
Damn you!
What's with your face!
Downtown's self-destruction.
They're STILL going!
Catch him already.
That is really something.
Why do they keep their distance!
Just catch him
I really thought that they were going to board the bus.
Yeah.
They're still at it.
Look.
Yeah.
They look so happy that it got stolen.
It's been 45 mins since the start of the bus ride.
The rash of punishments never stop!
After this, even stronger assassins await them!
Fujiwara-san.
Arriving At A Bus Stop
Again?
Hey wait, Shingo.
What? What's wrong with you, Yuriko-chan?
Huh?
You cheated on me again, right?
Couple Having A Fight
Yoshitaka Yuriko
Fujimori Shingo
(Oriental Radio)
Are you saying it was cheating?
No no no!
That was just a little party!
Don't make a sad face.
But..
Why?
Yuriko's Father
Umezawa Tomio
Yuriko.
Dad.
What's going on?
Huh?
Who is this man?
Oh, hi.
It's me!
Who the hell are you!
* They laughed, but please keep watching.
He stays cool.
You're crying.
I'm not crying.
What did you do? Huh?
I didn't..
What did you do to my daughter?
What? You noisy old bastard!
Playboy Being Rude To His Girlfriend's Father
What are you doing?
Shingo!
Stop it!
What? I'm telling you.
Yuriko-chan and I are getting along very well.
I can do whatever I want to do to her.
Playboy Being Rude To His Girlfriend
Ouch! It hurts..
You look just like your dad.  Let him see your face.
Stop it.
It hurts!
I said to stop it!
What! Shut up, old bastard!
Stop it.
Isn't it "Stop it, PLEASE."?
Say it.
What..
Say "Stop it, please."
What are you doing?
Watch your mouth!
Damn you!!
Hey.
What did you just do?
Huh?
Did you just kick me?
Was it in the script?
Hey.
Stop the camera.
I said to stop it!
I'm sorry, Hama-chan.
It's OK.
I'm sorry, Macchan.
Even if this is variety,
there is a line you shouldn't cross.
Yes.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Why did you kick me?
Hey.
It wasn't in the script!
Sorry.
Give me a break.
I'm sorry.
Did you make him do it?
Hey.
No..
I can't talk to you.
Call the Producer.
Call the Producer!
I can't continue this.
I'm sorry.
WOW!!
Happy Boy
Okada Keisuke (Masuda Okada)
Here I come!
Thank you very much.
Awesome.
Good to see you, but..
Hey!
Stop the quarreling, Tomio-chan!
This is all Dokkiri (prank).
My comedy is disappointing.
Stupid!!
This play is all fake.
My plays are always meaningless.
It surprised me!
It's too much of a collaboration!
I was really frightened.
Give me a break.
Wow.
I'm so sorry, Hama-can.
Let us do it again.
OK?
We will be fine this time.
Re-doing The Play
I'm sorry, Macchan.
Do it properly, OK?
Doing it again.
Huh?
It was a prank right?
Wasn't it just a prank?
Isn't it done?
Where..from..
Huh?
Hey Shingo, wait.
What's wrong with you, Yuriko-chan?
Here she says "you cheated on me."
You cheated on me again, huh?
You shouldn't call it cheating.  No no no!
Girlfriend's Father Umezawa Tomio
Dad?
What's going on?
Are we watching this again?
Who's this man?
Hey it's me!
Who the hell are you!
* They already laughed, but please keep watching.
We already saw this
I'm not crying.
What did you do!?
Huh? What did you do to my daughter!?
Yuriko and I get along well.  Do you want to see?
She is totally fine with it.
It hurts!
Playboy Being Rude To His Girlfriend
Look, old bastard!
Let your dad see your face, same face as your dad!
Ouch!
Shut up, old bastard!
Playboy Being Rude To His Girlfriend's Father
What are you doing?
Shut up, stupid.
Starting from here
Shut up, you're annoying!
Stop it.
You're noisy.
There it is.
Here it comes!
What did you just do?
No more already!
You already did it!
You just did it!
It was exactly the same.
Stop the camera.
I said to stop it!
Well, we can't react the same
I'm sorry, Hama-chan.
I'm really sorry, Macchan.
I can't talk to you.
Call the Producer!
Happy Boy
Okada Keisuke (Masuda Okada)
This is ruleless Dokkiri take 2!
Hi, Yoshitaka-chan!
You came here for a little promotion, Yoshitaka-chan.
But ended up showing your ugly faces!
I'm easing it for you!
No!!
I see! Thank you very much.
Why did he say "I see"?
Here is a question for you, Yoshitaka-chan.
What's in here?
Tada!
Here's Robo-ji!
The role she's playing this time is,
a geeky girl student who loves robot.
This is Robo-ji,
what I get during this season is.. Kireiji (bleeding piles)!
No!!
You Iboji (hemorrhoid)!
Wow!!
January 14th
Road show!
"Robo-ji"
It's an advertisement.
Here we go, come on everybody!
It's the first time for us to be used for promotion...
What the hell is this!
How dare they do a promo.
Tomio! You better cut it out.
There was a moment..
Yeah.
It was just a moment..
He didn't say he was Happy boy.
It's been an hour from the start. The hell commute still continues.
I wonder how we will get off.
This was tough.
Manager
Koyabu Kazutoyo
How's your song  about Hiyashi-chuka coming along?
It's not very good.
Oh yeah?
Fads come and go quickly.
You might have to make a new one.
Actually, I'm thinking to form a duo.
Duo?
Yes.
Sounds good.
Actually, my partner is here today.
Is your partner here?  Let me see him.
It's just.. I'm kind of worried if it will turn out OK.
Is that so..
Hey, partner!
Come here!
Partner
(Umemiya Tatsuo)
Isn't he too old?
He's got deep wrinkles next to his mouth.
Hey!
It's crazy to say that.
It's rolling into his face.
He's rude.
Never mind about his wrinkles..
Hey Koyabu..
Are you sure you'll be OK with this old man?
I'm sure. We can get along.
Be that as it may, do you have a new performance?
Yes.
OK Then.
I'm Amemiya
I'm Umemiya
Please listen to this.
"While I was attending college, I was scouted one night in Ginza"
"I became an actor at Toei.."
AMEMIYA Suddenly Laughs
What was he doing?
This is no good!
Yes.
He's not supposed to laugh.
Give me a break!
I was not counted!
This always happens.  I'm not supposed to be hit but they make me stand.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
Yes, Umemiya is OK too.
Huh?
Never mind.  Continue.
"While I was attending college, I was scouted one night in Ginza"
"I became.."
What's wrong?
AMEMIYA Did It Again
What's wrong with him?
This is wrong!
Damn you!
This isn't good.
This is not good.
This is creating a bad atmosphere.
"When I was.."
Thank you, Umemiya.
You can do it
Huh?
I can do it.
You don't need to say "Huh?"
Koyabu, cut it out.
Stop the "Huh?"
Gather yourself, Amemiya.
OK!
Finish it!
Here we go
"When I was.."
Amemiya...
Amemiya will sing.
Shall I slap you once?
It seems it would be better if I slap you once.
Pull yourself together. Think about the audience.
I'm really sorry.
As a pro...
He was fine.
He was doing fine.
He was pretty good!
It was a hard one.
I'm sorry to bother you when you are busy.
Koyabu is scary.
He's trying hard.
OK!
This is your last chance!
You have to make them laugh!
Why are YOU laughing?
That's true.
Just pull yourself together.
OK.  Again!
"While I was attending college, I was scouted one night in Ginza"
"I became an actor at Toei. Then the following year"
"I became a star, got carried away and started to regularly visit Ginza"
"I was called Emperor of night"
"The woman who brought me back down to earth"
"It was Claudia with blue eyes"
Wait.
Your voice is too soft, don't try so sing well!
Koyabu..
He didn't have to say that.
Sing loud!
On stage, you'll only have a foot mic.
Yes.
OK from, "It was Claudia with blue eyes."
Sing it loud. All of your parts. OK?
Yes.
OK, let's start!
"IT WAS CLAUDIA WITH BLUE EYES!!"
Good.
"I got bored acting so I got involved in cooking"
"I started making Tacchan Pickles"
"Matsukata goes deep-sea fishing often and got a suntan before I knew it"
"He finally caught a giant tuna"
"Anna came back home and suddenly my hair went white"
"Although I look young I became 73 years old this year"
"Stress piles up and body odor gets worse as I age"
"I started using eau de cologne"
"Every time I kiss my grandchild, she cries out"
"Why is my tear falling even if I am not sad?"
"I started breath care"
"Breath care..."
What's he doing.
No need for that!
No need for it.
The manager is so strict.
The manager is strict.
Something...
Hmm..Amemiya is fine.
Yes.
You are a bit..
Wrong. Like the tone of your voice..
It's not funny.
It's rather sad to watch you sing.
An old man is trying to sing.
You got a bad mouth!
Bad mouth.
Hey you!
Don't say that!
Such a bad mouth!
He's bad.
Yes, he is so strict.
What do you think, Amemiya. Can you get along with him?
I think we can.
What about you?
I THINK WE CAN!
Keep up the good voice!
YES!
GOT IT?
FOUL BREATH (Koushuu)!
What is traffic (Koutsuu)?
Foul breath!
Traffic!
You were just singing about it.
What the hell!
I don't want it!
Not traffic.
OK then.
I understand how hard you are trying.
Let's go back to the office and make a new song!
Shall we go then?
OK.
OK!
What's with Amemiya?
He just couldn't help but laugh, huh?
Koyabu hit them
It surprised me.
I wasn't looking
He did it to Tatsu-ni too.
Scary. Scary.
The long bus commute is almost reaching the end.
They are approaching the GAS training school.
Over the hill, is the training school for newbie cabin attendants.
The bus finally arrives.
But this is not a goal.  It's just a beginning of a battle.
We've arrived.
OK! Good!
Finally.
Looks great.
Here is the training school that you will enter.
This is the stage of No-Laughing, Gaasuukurobikari Airline System.
At this training school where customer's safety and laugher are of the upmost importance
a tremendous battle finally begins!!
Gaasuukurobikari Airline..
Matsumoto's Private SP Waiting
They are waiting.
You're right.
Arrived At GAS Training School
We've arrived, let's get off.
We've arrived.
They don't open the door.
Finally arrived.
It was a long ride.
We've arrived.
Your judgment is so accurate only for a time like this!
SP Takes Care Of Matsumoto Too Well
He laughed.
You don't need their help now..
What... why is this?
They came all of a sudden..
Something happened before you got out.
Everyone, here is the training school.
Don't you think this school looks prestigious and classy?
GAS Training School
Can you stand in a row here?
Hamada, Matsumoto..
In front of you,
you see
Gaasuu's
muscat symbol.
Muscat?
I didn't laugh!
He clearly made a mistake.
Let's do this right, Fujiwara-san.
This is the Gaasuukurobikari Airline system's
mascot symbol.
Mascot Symbol
The Legendary Suga Duck
Suga duck. The legendary Suga duck.
Shall we go then?
The entrance is this way.
Entrance lobby
Here we are.
It look awesome.
Everyone, come this way.
Actually in this room,
The top cabin attend... cabin attendant,
the legendary empress is waiting for us.
Let's go in.
Excuse me.
Chief CA room
Come on in.
* A chair is prepared for Matsumoto
Excuse me. The 5 newbie cabin attendants are here to pay their respects.
Chief CA
Matsuko Deluxe
You laughed.
No, I didn't.
It hurts!
The hardest hit today!!
Finally?
Hardest?
Yes.
Excuse me
Well... She is asking you guys to introduce yourselves and your hobbies.
Passing Messages From Deluxe CA
Starting from Matsumoto.
Names and what?
Hobbies.
Hobbies?
Q Name and Hobby
Matsumoto Hitoshi.
I wonder what..
I guess it's TV games.
Next.
Yes. Hamada Masatoshi.
Golfing... yes.
Next.
My name is Endo Shozo.
My hobby is golfing.
CUTE!
Deluxe CA Loves Endo
It's getting harder, isn't it?
I wasn't called out!
Next.
Tanaka Naoki.
Scuba diving is my hobby.
Give me a break. Bastard
She's wild.
She says to pass on the next person.
Why is she not speaking to us?
She is asking you to give your first impression of her.
Matsumoto you start.
Q First impression
I mean..
I thought you were glamorous
She says it's wonderful.
Next.
You have a presence
She says it's wonderful.
Thank you very much.
Next.
Yes
Um...
COME HERE
Deluxe CA Calling Endo
Why does she speak only during these times?
Yeah.
Me?
You were summoned, Endo
Ugh.. Scary..
Excuse me.
Excuse me
She Treats Her Love To A Marshmallow
Wider.
LICK
It was very scary.
Sure it was.
I hate it.
Q First impression
Tanaka, you're next.
Yes...
YOU'RE NOISY!
She has no interest in me.
Q First impression
Yamazaki, she said you can speak this time.
Thank you.
I thought you were big.
She says to come here.
Deluxe CA Summons Yamasaki
Me?
Yes.  Yamasaki.
Stranglehold To Her Hate!!
Poor thing!
She's scary!
Poor thing...
Yes, scary.
That was so surprising.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
It doesn't make sense.
Are you OK?
Not at the moment.
It was a killer!
It was surprising.
What do you think is so great about her?
Why is she great?
Q Why am I so great?
Matsumoto start.
As everyone may think,
I think she is great at applying makeup...
She says to come here.
Does she?
It was that scary.
This is scary, huh?
He was summoned and got OUT.
Full force!
And I had to go.
Yeah.
Sorry for you.
She Treats Her Love To A Marshmallow
Marshmallow?
What's this?
What?
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
She is saying to come closer and open your mouth wider.
It is very scary.
En... Endo!
Yes.
She says to come here.
It wasn't even his turn, right?
I guess Endo is just loved
regardless of the rules?
OK, excuse me.
Wrong. Wrong.
Come here
Here?
Lay down!
Lay down?
LAY DOWN!
Yes.
Thank you.
Deluxe CA's
Private Time
Too tough
It was really happening.
She was actually doing it.
Why was I the only one out?
It's hard to believe.
Your face changed.
Please leave, Fujiwara-san!
Thank you.
Excuse us.
I want to wipe my face
It seems like she loves you all.
I don't really think so
We're going to be OK?
Good.
Matsumoto's private SP Waiting At Stairs
f
Wow.
We are going up stairs. This way.
OK.
Thank you for your work.
This alone makes me laugh
This wasn't as comfortable
as you may think.
I'm trying not to see it
I can't stand this
I guess so.
It was so rough. That deep kiss.
I wanted to see it.
Did she do it hard?
She was seriously
3rd Floor
putting her tongue in
Sure?
Yes, she did.
Thank you.
You will be standing by in this newbie training room.
OK.
Please enter.
Newbie Training Room
Your seats are assigned by your names.  Please sit in the correct seats.
Yes.
Finally.
1 Hour 50 Minutes Since Starting
It was a long way to come.
Yes.
It was..
This place is not free of punishments.
But yet.
We could rest here a little.
Now we are going to learn about cabin atten..dants..
Here are training books.
Please read it well.
Yes.
Handing Out CA Books
Endo.
Yes.
Hamada.
This is for Matsumoto.
CA books are handed out by Fujiwara.
Of course, these are traps to make them laugh...
Hamada
Masatoshi
ID photo for just Hamada is a mountain gorilla.
Let's see what happens..
OK then, please stand by here for a while.
Can we look inside?
Yes, please read it well.
OK.
Just a regular photo..
ID Photo
You are quick.
Instant death.
What's so funny about this?
Instant death!
By what?
You stand by too easily to be hit on the butt.
What made you laugh?
The ID photo?
Yes, here is.
No thanks, I have mine here.
Just take a look at mine.
That's right.  It's true
No, I have mine here. I saw mine already. See?
ID Photo
Why are you laughing?
Shut up and look mine.
I'm not laughing.
Sure you did.
He was for quite a while.
If you are curious why I was laughing, look to see why.
Here is a big one.
What are you doing?
What?
If you ask me why I was laughing..
Endo will.
Endo, take a look.
Hamada Masatoshi
But I guess so.
It can't be helped.
I think so too.
Didn't he laugh just now?
I thought you did.
I think he did.
No no no.
Right?
See?
That isn't laughing, right?
He's laughing!
No, that's not it.  I read another page.
The more pages you read, the more traps you'll find.
* The secret story of Downtown when they debuted as "The Wright brothers" is written in tribute to the skies.
Oh I didn't know that.
It was there.
Hamada Masatoshi
What the hell is that!
This is enough.
Even such a thing is written.
It doesn't make sense!
Give me a break..
This is mine.
I think it is malicious.
It is, right?
Yes, it is.
It is a lack of a sense of equality.
Hamada Masatoshi
It is not fair.
No, it's not.
Can't help laughing.
Are they in their right mind?
This is tough.
Good job, Hamada-san!
Good pace.
Yes.
It was a critical hit. Good one.
Don't you mean technical hit?
What is a critical hit?
I didn't laugh!
I don't want to be with this stupid!
Did I laugh?
A hit that gives greater damage than usual during fighting. This term is mainly used in computer games.
This moron is killing me.
It's been 2 hours since the start.
They have been just tossed around with traps.
Furthermore the scary drawers are waiting for them!
A lot of traps even before entering the room.
Right.
I think we rode on the bus for about a couple of hours.
Endo's scene was much longer too. The Matsuko's..
Matsuko Deluxe
The kiss, right?
The kiss!
It was LONG!
She actually used her tongue like hell.
There was a prank too.
Yes, there was a prank.
Umezawa Tomio
What did you think?
I really thought wow..
But if it was true and we laughed, he would've been pissed right?
Yeah.
Just in case I had to keep a straight face.
Were you making that face?
It's been 2 hours since the start of their duty.
It is about the time to face it...
Let's open the drawers, everyone.
Shall we?
Here it comes!
Can't be helped.
Let's do it.
Usually I'm first up.  What about this time?  Will you go first, Housei-san?
Shall I?
First Up Is Yamazaki
I'm going.
Are you sure?  I don't think we have to do it...
We have to do it soon or later...
Automated Pop-out Drawer
Wow!
This is why I don't want to do it.
Did it fly out?
Did you open it?
Yes, just a little bit and it shot out.
Like a jack-in-the-box.
Yes..
You were laughing
I didn't laugh
You did.  That's why this person is here.
See?  You got hit.
Because you laughed.
It happened because you laughed.
You don't have to say it.
But I didn't notice it.
It's dangerous. This is heavy.
I'll open them all
I'm scared.
Nothing
What?
There's something
I heard air.
Suga Kenji Doll
I often see Suga-san like this at golf courses.
It's so dark, I couldn't tell.
This is Suga-san at a golf course.
I instantly got it.
This is Suga-san at a golf course in summer.
I guess this is about the right color shade.
Gasu finally became a doll.
This is..
Wow.  Suga doll.
What was it?
It just exploded
Yes.
It exploded, huh?
It was air-actuated
Yeah, it was air.
So that's it
I think it was supposed to be a bigger explosion.
It's scary!
You could've lost your front teeth.
You're right. Like this..
Did they target my front teeth?
Yes, all of them.
What is it?  I can't sit still.
Tanaka laughed too.
I want this relay to stop.
I have fracture on my leg.  They don't seem to understand it.
They don't care.
Why are you laughing anyway?  You are OUT in two ways.
You laughed at your senior having a fracture on his leg..
No, I'm not laughing.
What's with your face?
What is it?
This is not allowed either, right?
If it is allowed, I would do the same.
Let's pull ourselves together.
- Yes.
It is OK even if we get no punishment from now on.
You're right.
Please open it already.
Huh? Matsumoto-san, are you opening your drawer?
I will go with Haruo
Automated Pop-out Drawer
All of them?
Must be.
What happened just now?
As soon as I opened a little, it flew out.
Yes yes, so that's air.
It's a pump
Wait... try opening the first one.
Oh there is something.
Art student #1
Mysterious Envelopes!
Does it mean this is Art student #2?
No..
Wrong.
There are many.. Umezu-san too.
Man Gataro.
Shall we take a look inside?
Mysterious.
The 3rd one..
Let's open that drawer first.
Drawer?
- Drawer?
Very mysterious.
Baby Toys
What's this?
What is this?
Is this a play house kit?
I mean..I see these almost everyday.
(Actual toys)
Matsumoto's daughter's
She plays with these, huh?
It's a toy!
Is this really yours?
So it was meant to get you.
Nothing here
Shall we take a look at these?
Art student #1
I'm scared.
by Art student
What's this?
Oh, that's it!  I got it now!
I got it.  I got it.
Oh, that's it.
This is a Hamada-san's composite drawing by an art student.
That's what it is.
Hey you.
He must be stupid.
Don't relax so much.
That wasn't good of me.
He was really enjoying it.
Street artist.
by Street artist
This is awesome.
Hey Hamada-san!
This is no good!
As I kind of knew, I think Hamada is easy to draw.
It really looks like him!
It really does.
It does.
Are we going to look at them all at once?  I guess so huh..
We have to.
What about Umezu-san's.
He is good.
Oh, there are two.
First one.
Umezu Kazuo #1
I knew it, it is awesome.
A real pro.
What did you mean there were two.
There is 1 more.
Umezu Kazuo #2
I tried hard not to laugh!
Isn't it awesome?
It is.
This is gonna be a hard one for me.  Man Gataro.
Man Gataro
Awarded the 1st GAG KING prize on the Weekly Shonen Jump.  His outstanding works are "Chinyuki" and "Jigoku-Koshien" etc.
He's awesome too.
Gataro drew so many!
Oh is he the one with the "touch?"
Man Gataro #1
Written: Natsumi
(Hamada's wife)
I thought I could bare it!
This is great.
Yes, it is.
His power as a painter..
So many different Hamada-sans..
The 2nd one.
Man Gataro #2
Written: Natsumi..
You were alive, ware
("you" written in
Osaka dialect )
What kind of story is that!
We don't use "ware" (you) in the context.
We don't use it that way!
This is not Osaka dialect!
You were alive... ware.
Which one do you like, Hamada-san?
I like the street artist.
by Street artist
This one?
This is really awesome.
Tanaka, go!
OK, I'm going!
Nothing?
Again
Again...
Here it comes!
Mysterious DVD
It comes every time.
I wonder what it is this time?
So it's the DVD again
Let's open the rest of drawers.
Yes.
Last time, we found more than one DVD.
Nothing in the top drawer.
Nothing in the middle.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What the hell is it.
Nothing?
Don't speak in unison with me.
Tanaka laughed too!
Why are you wearing that?
Black... very obscene underwear.
Very obscene underwear.
You shouldn't say it.
I shouldn't?
Yeah, I didn't have to say it.
So let's think when to watch that (DVD)?
Leave it for now?
Please go, Matsumoto-san.
I'm scared of the air thing.
Watch out.
Nothing in there
Empty.
It can't be...
Nothing.  For the first time?
Oh my gosh, here it comes!
Mysterious Button!
Here it is.
What is it?
There might be another one in the lower drawer.
Nothing?
5 Mysterious Panels
Did you find anything?
There is.
What's this?
How can I show these?
There are 5 of them.
Just show them one by one.
Can I rotate it first?
Wrong?
I wonder how should I do this.
Should it be on the top?
Idol Collage
Hamada
Stop with everything being Hamada!
Stop bringing up only Hamada!
Wow.
This is no good.
No, maybe it's just in order?
I was on top, the rest might be you guys...
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
Might be.
After seeing the first one... the next one seemed kinda dull.
Can't be helped.
Idol collage
Tanaka
Idol Collage
Yamasaki
What are you doing?
Scary.
Who's body is it?
Yeah I wonder.
Idol collage
Matsumoto
That's malicious.
Scary! It scares me!
It scares me!
What are you doing?
This problem still remains.
Yes.
Mysterious Button
(Kanji = Dragon)
What is it?  Dragon?
Shall we leave it on the side.
Yeah, since we still have the DVD.
Endo?  That's wrong.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm putting them away.
Dragon?
"Dragon" is written on it?
Try pressing it.
Huh? Is it the character of the next year?
The year of the dragon?
Next year is the year of the dragon
Oh that must be it!
In a few hours, it will be the year of the dragon.
Why me?
He made a face like a criminal!
What the hell is it!
No, I didn't!
Hey hurry up, Matsumoto-san.
Sure?
Yes.
Here I go
I don't care what happens
OK?
I'm pressing it!
Pressing Button -> Hakuryu Appears
Oh!  That's it
That's Hakuryu.
Shhhhh
FART
Who would imagine this?  It's not like his character.
What are you making him to do!
It surprised me!
Ah!  He's going back.
Now I got it.  It means Hakuryu (White Dragon).
"Dragon" on the white button = Hakuryu
I got it.  It's Hakuryu-san.
Easing the tension.
That's right.
I was scared of what he was going to do.
In this time of the year before new years..
who would imagine to hear someone else's fart.
Someone not too familiar.
Yeah.
I wonder just how he did it.?
Was it a real fart?
I thought it was...
It was live... actually live.
Can he control it?
If so, it's awesome.
But it was quite weak.
It was.
And he left before we knew it.
CA Duties Started
2 hours 30 minutes ago
One problem follows another.
One of duties for newbie CA is visiting senior workers.
Training School 1F
Everyone, come this way.
From now on, I'll introduce you to your trainer.
Your trainer is known to be very strict.  Be careful.
Let's go in.
Excuse me.
CA Training room
Everyone, come on in.
Matsumoto, here's a chair for you.
Oh thank you.
Yamazaki, Tanaka and Endo in the order.
Excuse me!  Excuse me!
CA Trainer Appears
CA Trainer
Takahashi Keiko
Wait!
Are you serious?
No kidding!?
I'm Takahashi Keiko.
When she was 15, she won the Golden Arrow Award for new faces.
Even though she is a successful actress,
she appears on a damn variety show on new year's eve,
wearing a damn bondage outfit.
Who the hell is it?
THAT'S ME!!
I reviewed your profile information in advance.
Let's see.
You must be Endo.
Yes.
I heard you have a new girlfriend?
Are you doing well with her?
Yes, I think so... Yes!
Doing well, huh?
To a girl who was not even his girlfriend yet,
he sent a brainless text message.
"I'm going to train you well!"
Who's the super pervert?
Who the hell is it?
THAT'S YOU!!
It's funny when she says it.
"That's you!"
But it's the truth.
Yes it is.
Yamazaki.
Yes.
I heard you are married?
Are you taking good care of your wife?
Yes
Are you really?
A cheat was uncovered,
and his wife who is naturally so damn stupid
shaved off all of his pubic hair.
He's such a SEX SHOP A GO! GO! comedian.
Who the hell is it?
That was cruel.
THAT'S YOU!!
Now I remember.  I heard about it.
Shaved off?
Can't be, right?
You must be Tanaka.
Has anything exciting happened lately?
Um....I think so..
NEVER MIND!!
He sleeps then gets up.
He goes to work in his secondhand Volvo.
He receives low pay.
He eats a lunch box.
He smokes cigarettes.
He comes home and goes to sleep again.
He gets up and again goes to work in his secondhand Volvo...
WHAT A POINTLESS LIFE!!
It doesn't make sense!
It's a mess.
No need for "secondhand"...
It really hurts!
You two.
I heard it will be your 30th anniversary next year?
That you have been in show business for such a long time,
proves that everyone loves you.
You receive damn expensive fees,
complaining that dramas are tiring
or saying my knee hurts?
Who do you think you are!
Scary.
Yeah.
You sure are ugly huh.
YOU
DAMN PIG!!
Why did you start using foul language?
She said you were an ugly pig..
Like Sparta
Now I know what.
Then, I'll show you.
Expressing How To Be CA
Keep your eyes open.
Are you serious?
Um.. teacher..
INUGAMI FAMILY!!
She couldn't complete it.
Her legs never got off the ground.
Her legs never lifted up at all.
The drawers are not done yet.
One trial after another.
Shall we watch the DVD?
So there are 2 DVDs.  What's written on them?
Just DVD #1 and #2.  As always.
We should get it done.
I guess we watch #1 first.
It's so tough.
Tanaka, play the DVD #1.
Let's see what happens.
What is it...
I'm scared
Are you playing #1?
What could this be?
Yamazaki spotted her so quickly.
I didn't realize.
Me neither.
From here again.
CA Exam Site
Matsumoto Chiaki.
Huh?  Where's the exam site?
The actual character was
named Matsumoto Chiaki.
So they used Chiaki.
I wonder where I am..
Wow, cool.
Wow.
What is he doing?
What.. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Enough of them already.
This is a killer.
I see.
We really should brace ourselves for this.
You're right.
What..What are you doing?
Who are you?  I'll call for help.
You seem... to be fine.
What is he doing?
He can't say that short line?
Please say the lines correctly.
Who are you?  I'll call for help.
You seem... to be fine.
The way he walks..
Stewardess story.
Yeah.
That's a strange way to walk.
Cabin Attendant Story
Interview room
Next group please enter.
Dad, please wish me luck.
Thank you for your time.
Interview room
Don't use it that way.
He should notice her instantly!
What the hell.
It's too lame.
Let's unite together.
Yes.  Let's get through this together.
You might laugh when others laugh.
Thank you for your time.
Interview room
It's starting from here again.
Hiki Rie
I started aspiring to be a CA because my parents often took me abroad and..
Takaki Mio
I want to utilize my English skills and develop my career as a CA..
These are the original actresses.
Ito Maiko
I like to associate with people and I feel happy to assist them.
I... I like the sky...
As..as a child, I've always liked planes.
I want to become a CA as soon as possible..
and want to move out my house.
Want to move out your house?
Yes.
My mom remarried but..
I can't associate well with my new dad and siblings.
You are selfish.
What is it?
His timing was off
You are not cooperative. You can't be a cabin attendant.
Why do you think so?
Why do you say such a thing?
Because I mistook you as a pervert and scratched your face?
OK, next.
Why?
Come here.
I'm sure.
Are you going to fail me?
What's with that expression, Endo?
This was hard for me.
I'm home.
What time do you think it is?
Step father
Where were you?  Why didn't you call?
Wow..
I'm sorry.
Mother
Welcome home.  How was the interview?
Mom, it didn't go well.
I gave it up.
Hey!
Step brother
There he is.
Wasn't it your dream to become a CA?
Yeah,
Step sister
you gave it up in one day?
Good drama.
you have no guts, huh?
It's an all star cast
If you are not true to yourself, you can't be a CA anyway.
It's good that you gave up.
I won't give it up.
I'll do it.
What?
I'll try my best to become a CA!
Chiaki!
Gaasuu Airline Training Center
Service test
Here's wine for you.
It's no good.  What kind of smile is that?
A good smile comes from your heart.
I can't smile.
I want to cry.
What's this?
As a CA, you have to smile even when you want to cry.
You better quit.
Shin-Oni Instructor.
Shin-Oni Instructor, you're being too strict.
Shut up. Get away.
Get away! Get away! Get away!!
Shin-Oni, acting like a kid.
I want him to change his name.
Not Shin-Oni Instructor.
Shin-Oni Instructor, you're being too strict.
Shut up. Get away!
Get away! Get away! Get away!!
Shin-Oni Instructor!
Please don't abandon me!
To be frank, you are not suitable as a CA.
I admit I am clumsy and as slow as a turtle.
But I really want to be a CA!
Since I was child this high, it has been my dream.
Dream is dream.
If I can't become a CA, I would kill myself.
What did you say?
But Shin-Oni Instructor.
You are the one killing me.  It's YOU!
Wait!
I understand.
I don't want you to die.
Until you become a successful cabin attendant,
I'll train you hard.  Be prepared.
Shin-Oni Instructor.
What is he doing, just leave her.
You.
You are beaten by that girl.
She is so focused on her dream.  I never knew such a person still existed.
I don't get how he lost
She is just like
how you were before.
I... I decided.
I will let everyone pass the test.
Will you?
Yes!
Do you remember the name of this cheese?
I'm sorry.  I can't remember when I'm nervous.
If you can't, you just have to make a song of it.
Try singing this.
Was this scene
like the original?
I guess so.
"This cheese is known in England"
"as the most delicious cheese"
The great, Shin-Oni Instructor. He's such an idea man.
Everyone that was in the
original drama is in this.
I won't forgive you Shin-Oni!
Please transfer him somewhere far away.
Understood.
I am now going to announce the results of the exam.
Everyone passed!
From today, you all are CA!
Excuse me.
Where is Shin-Oni Instructor?
He has been transfered to Paris.
He gave all of you his best regards.
Instructor!
Shin-Oni Instructor!
I passed the CA entrance exam.
Congratulations.
Can I fall into your arms?
I don't want a crash landing.
Shin-Oni Instructor!
"I don't want a crash landing"
I'm jealous but I'm happy for you.
Embarrassing, huh?
Cheers.
I'm really glad that everyone passed.
Yes!
Instructor! Shin-Oni Instructor!
It's her.
What is it, Chiemi?
Chiemi Senior.
Instructor.
In fact, not everyone passed.
What do you mean?
Actually...
only Tanaka was OUT.
Furthermore, Tanaka will be Thai-kicked.
End
They're all looking and laughing.
Oh, yeah.
That's scary!
I don't get it.  What does it mean?
Huh?  Why?
Substitute For The CA Of The Same Name Who Failed The Exam
All of a sudden?
Tanaka... Don't move around too much.
Watch out.
It's all of a sudden.
It had nothing to do with this.
She said Tanaka OUT.
Hey wait!  Are you serious?
Tanaka, stay still.
It's gonna hurt..
It hurts..
It hurts...
Damn you!
I know how you feel.
I know it hurts.
It doesn't sound like it, but it hurts.
Aren't you laughing?
You were laughing just now, right?
Yes, you were.
He was laughing from the pain.
Too much pain?
No... I didn't laugh.
Someone's out.  What happened?
You did it, right?
I don't know.
What happened?
I really didn't know.
You're lying.
This is no good.
This is not right.
It was in the desk.
Isn't it wrong that it was in the desk?
This is no good.
I'll put it away.
Yes, thank you.
3 hours and a half hours since the start of duty.
Listen up.
We are now going to be attending the welcoming ceremony for new CA.
Since it'll be cold, I prepared coats for everyone to wear.
I don't want to go to a cold place.
Attending The Welcoming Ceremony
A coat like this won't protect me from the cold!
My bottom area is cold.
Cold..
Whoa.
Thank you, guys.
Private SP Stairs Assistance
It was really pain in the ass.
By the way, Yamazaki has been laughing for quite a while.
You too, Matsumoto-san.
OK, thank you.
They are still going.
I'm good already.
I doubt they understand what you said.
Ugh... there are a lot of people there.
GAS Training Grounds
Everyone, here.
Here is fine, thank you.
OK, thank you.
Cold!
Your seats are the front row.
OK, got it.
So, cold.
The newbie welcoming ceremony will now commence.
Before it starts, to welcome our newbies,
we invited famous musical artists from overseas.
What's that..
If you will!
I doubt it.
Famous Celebrity Artist Appears
Celebrity Artist
Watanabe Naomi
That face
She gained weight again.
- Yeah.
Another Famous Celebrity Artist
Celebrity Artist
Kurosawa Kazuko (Morisanchu)
She can't get off.
Your song is starting.
You had one more step!
Dream Collaboration
That's fine. I'm fine with OUT.
It hurts more because it's cold!
Next, we will introduce our new instructors that just transfered in today.
Please come up to the stage.
Cold.
Introduction Of New Instructors
What the hell.
Gushiken Youkou Instructor, please do a short introduction of yourself.
New Instructor
Gushiken Youkou
I'm Gushiken Youkou, just transferred from Ishigaki island.
* The members don't understand his dialect.
Speaking In The Ishigaki Dialect
I didn't understand it at all.
I caught the mobile phone part.
Yeah, me too.
He said mobile phone.
* Speaking in the Ishigaki Dialect. The members don't understand it.
He said karaoke?
He did.
It's a long intro, huh?
* Speaking in the Ishigaki Dialect. The members don't understand it.
Stand Accidentally Falls
Give me a break.
What the hell.
Why?
Thank you, Gushiken Instructor.
Up next is Takeda Instructor.
*We didn't inform Takeda Instructor that he has to do the introduction.
They didn't tell him.
Takeda Instructor if you will.
They didn't.
- No.
I want to see how he handles it.
- Yeah
New Instructor
Takeda Nobuhiro
Takeda-san, your introduction please.
Takeda Instructor's Ad-lib Introduction
Well..
Please do your best.
That's all.
Excuse me.
Takeda...
Next up is Batsugun Instructor.
New Instructor
Nishio Hidetaka
Sagane Masahiro
We are still new, so we want to
learn with you. Let's try our best.
Sagane Instructor, what nickname would you liked to be called by your students?
"Margaret-chan"
Please.
Instructors, we are counting on you from here on.
Thank you.
Excuse me? Can I have a little time?
What the hell was it?
Margaret-chan?
What's wrong?
Nishio Judging Sagane
I didn't know.
You didn't know?  You should know that's how variety is.
We were always longing to be on this No-laughing, right?
This was our big break.
You just wasted it.
We are finished.
Can I say something?
No, I'm talking.
Hey wait. Don't interrupt.
What about you?
Huh?
Sagane Rebelling
So you are perfect, then?
He's rebelling.
You often say ordinary stuff too!
What was your comment?
"Let's try out best?"
Say something funny!
Then I can add to it as Tukkomi, right?
I can't do my job unless you say something funny.
If you can't,
we are done.
Oh are you done?
Done?
It seems to be silent.
Now that I don't hear anything,
it means you are done talking, right?
I only sense your foul breath.
We visited that family for filming the other day, right?
At the time you were saying...
"Grandma is such a good cook" and
"Grandma, are you caring?"
You said that, right?
She was their Mom.
She had her children late in age.  She was the mom not Grandma.
Why only us?
It was obvious everyone laughed.
Everyone laughed.
Yamazaki has been missed.
You better watch out.
Or we are done.
I'm sorry...
You too. Don't be daydreaming.
Gushiken-san.
Spilling Over To Gushiken
Look at me.  I'm talking to you.
You don't understand where you are standing, just like Sagane.
I didn't mean it literally.
Wait. Cocorico was laughing.
Cocorico was laughing too!
Don't miss Cocorico.
We didn't laugh.
When you were on Hanamaru Market the other day, you were asked for your motto.
Yes.
You wrote it on a flip.
Isshoukenmei (Always do my best).
Yes.
You changed the word "懸(ken) "to  "拳 (ken)", which means fist, right?
It means force.
Will you bring people into submission by force forever?
I'm talking here.
Yes, I'll try my best
No, don't.
Since it's cold, it's cold... I mean it hurts.
You wrote the kanji  "拳", right?
You shouldn't be able to.
Don't even think about it.  Just now, you made people laugh by looking at the ground.
You can make everyone laugh with such accidents.
So don't try.  A moron has to be a moron.
If you don't stop it,
You're finished.
You are making a sour face, but you too.
Spilling Over To Takeda Too
What just happen to you?
You were asked to speak, and you froze.
You didn't think you would be asked.
- No.
Of course you would be asked.
Who would pay you for doing nothing?
That's who you are.
I would call Gushiken-san a useful moron.
Huh?
I'm sorry
Why did he laugh?
Do your jobs.
- OK.
Excuse me. Thank you for the time.
Next, we're going have our Gaasuu Cheer leading team perform.
This fall they earned their 8th consecutive win at the National convention.
Here they come!
Cheer Leading Team Performance
Umezu Kazuo (75) Is Also A Member
So clumsy.
What the hell are you doing!
So skinny.
Like drift wood.
What was that?
Did you see what our Cheer leadingunu.... Cheer leading team can do?
Let's return.
He really is something.
1st Floor Hallway
Next room is on the 1st floor so..
Everyone, here is a consultation room for trainees.
Excuse us.
Everyone, be quiet.
The doctor is not here yet, so let's sit here and wait.
Where's Chief?
She just left for an operation with a cancer patient.
She's not coming?
I'm sorry.
I doubt a newly transferred doctor can handle this situation.
Oh Doctor!
Training School Doctor
Mita Yoshiko
How's the patient?
The appendix seems to be ruptured.
Please take this patient to an operating room ASAP.
Will she be OK?
We came at such a critical time...
Shall we introduce ourselves?
First up is Endo.
Yes. I'm Endo Shouzou.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
You.
What's your favorite sport?
It's golfing
Golfing!
That's what Jumbo Ozaki plays right?
Yes.
There are a lot more...
Besides Jumbo-san.
I mean..
because it is a popular sport.
Yes.
Like say, Ishikawa Ryo.
Next up is Hamada.
Yes.  I'm Hamada Masatoshi.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
- Nice to meet you..
Do you have another occupation?  What do you usually do?
I am a comedian.
Oh are you?
Yes.
What role do you play?
Uh... I'm Tsukkomi
Tsu...kkomi...
It's the same as Tsusumishita, right?
Why did she think of saying Tsutsumishita?
Next up is Matsumoto.
Yes. I'm Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
She's like this.
How old are you?
Uh... I turned 48.
48...
That's HTS(Hitoshi) 48, huh?
That's funny.
What the hell..
What are you saying.
Not funny..
What the hell is HTS48?
Doctor, a critical patient!
How is it?
What's the situation?
A rib bone is stuck in an organ and it is bleeding heavily.
That is quite a severe situation.
Sudden Change in Patient Condition
Get ready for an operation now!
I'll take care of you until you are OK.
Hey there..
Hey you..
Hey you...
Hamada!
Hamada-san.
Come here and hold him.
OK? Hold him tight.
OK..
I said to hold him tight!
What are you doing!
What's your problem?
I'm sorry.
You've got what a man should have, right!?
Searching for Hamada's Balls
Hang in there. I'll be back soon!
He's dying...
He'll be OK.
He's left behind.
Yeah.
He didn't introduce himself.
Yama-chan, why don't you introduce yourself to him.
I'm Yamasaki Housei.
My hobby is playing mah-jong.
During the marathon CA duty
something like this may happen...
Don't you want to kill that fly?
Yeah.
There was a fly.
A Fly in the Room
There was a big one.
It went there.
The 3 Juniors Trying To Kill The Fly
Can you really do it?
Here it is.
They're too old to be juniors.
Oh it stopped there.
It stopped. It stopped.
It's there.
Here's your chance, Tanaka.
Make sure to get it.  Make sure.
Got it?
An Object Fell on His Back
Something fell.
You can't be more clumsy than that!
It was like an American slapstick comedy.
Where's the fly?
No..
It escaped.
Damn.
But it's not flying.
OK.
As long as it's not flying, it's good.
Last time, we found something new (in drawers) when we returned.
Yes.
Something Found in the Drawer
Wait.
That's...
It must hurt!
It hurts..
Wait a second.
What is it?
Everyone take a look.
What's this..
Matsumoto Doll
It does look like you.
It means they added new items.
New items..
This is a new item.
It really looks like him.
Matsumoto Doll
See?
This is awesome.
It's really you.
This is really you!
No, you don't have to play with it so much.
Really.
Let me do a back flip.
Yeah.
You suck
You laughed.
You did.
Try it.  Show us how it's done
Wow.
It really looks like you.
I know it does!
This is awesome.
How do I do it?
I haven't done this for a year.
Hey wait!  No one else laughed but me!
What the hell!  I responded to your request!
It's hard to do, huh?
This is really..
The face.
It definitely looks like you
Awesome.
Everyone listen up.
Now, cabin attendants from our rival companies are here
for a joint training.  Let's attend it.
You are allowed to laugh during the training.
But if you lose to the other companies,
you'll receive a Thai-kick that you all hate.
No!
I don't want it!
CA Gathered From Foreign Countries
Special Training
Shall we go then.
No way!
I can't take it more than once a day.
I got a fracture on my leg.
If I received Thai kicks several times,
it would cause a big problem for me.
Training to protect their precious butts.  What's going to happen to the 5 members?
CA Training Site
From here on,  you are allowed to laugh.
Can we?
Yes, you can.
OK, start the music!
Please go in.
Please, please go forward.
Here you are, please take your seats there.
Let's get started, let me introduce our main casts, cabin attendants from each company.
GAS Training School Assistant
Yuuki Maomi
GAS Training School Instructor
Amano Hiroyuki
"Heart is more important than looks."
KimoITALIA Airline Team!
KimoITALIA Airline Team
Fujimoto Toshifumi
Tsukaji Muga  Suzuki Taku
(Drunk Dragon)
Cunning Takeyama
Kasuga Toshiaki
(Audley)
Who's next?
"Old looking face eases people."
CHUNENTAL Airline Team!
CHUNENTAL Airline
Shofukutei Shohei
Chihara Seiji
(Warai Meshi)
Nishida Kouji
(Yasei Bakudan)
Kawajima Kunihiro
Kinoshita Takayuki
Next, "We offer thrilling borderline flights."
ONEAL FRANCE Airline Team!
ONEAL FRANCE Airline
Mittsu Mangrove
Haruna Ai
Chris Matsumura
KABA. chan
Majima Shigeki
Lastly, "Black bullets shining in the sky."
Our Gaasuukurobikari Airline System Newbie Cabin Attendant Team!
Gaasuukurobikari Airline System
Tanaka Naoki
(Cocorico)
Endo Shozo
Yamazaki Housei
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
(Downtown)
ONEAL FRANCE
CHUNENTAL
GAS
KimoITALIA
Try and Win!  King of CA!  Airline Competition
No-losing Joint Training!
The 4 airlines battle in training with their courage and pride.
They can't lose this battle for the title of "King Of CA".
Now, let us introduce the judges.
Yes.
First, Japan's most renowned international celebrities,
The Kano Sisters.
Kano Sisters
Thank you for coming!
Sisters!
Someone called them out.
Let's introduce the next guest.
His heart is as great as the sky, his passion is as great as the sunset..
Fujioka Hiroshi.
Fujioka Hiroshi
You love coffee!
Thank you very much.
Firstly.  Here's the chairman Fujioka-san.
This is a joint training for cabin attendants.
Hi, thank you for having me today. I'm Fujioka.
I'm looking forward to seeing everyone's comedian soul.
Now everyone is getting excited.
No no no!
It scares me!
Let's get started then!
What's the first game, Maomi-chan?
Yes, the first joint training is,
Let's answer in 10 seconds!
Answer in 10 seconds!
CA Joint Training #1
Let's answer in 10 seconds.
As a cabin attendant, quick thinking is a must.
CA Joint Training #1
Answer in 10 seconds!
This training requires that all 5 members think fast and answer a question in 10 seconds.
Theme: Fruits
CA Joint Training #1
Answer in 10 seconds
Rules
The rule is quite simple.  Each member answers to a question in turn.
Apple
Melon
Grape
Peach
What kind of picture is this!
Tangerine
All 5 members need to answer in 10 seconds to clear.
CA Joint Training #1
Answer in 10 seconds!
The judges choose the worst CA after observing the training
After several rounds, the judges decide which cabin attendant was the worst.
The chosen CA will receive a Thai kick as a punishment
The chosen cabin attendant will receive a tough Thai-kick as a punishment
The Thai-kick will be performed by this person.
Muay Thai Welterweight Ex Champion
Takeda Kouzou
Thank you for coming!
Kick Samurai
Takeda Kouzou
Takeda Kouzou, a.k.a Kick Samurai.
He is a rare Japanese Muay Thai champion, and also enters K-1.
He's been fighting on K-1 WORLD MAX since 2003.  His right leg known as "Superalloy" produces a killer low kick.
The low kick given by his log-like leg shook the fighting sport field.
Wait a sec.
Check out his stare.
He is staring at you.
He said he is not in the best condition today.
Why is he staring at me?
Let's see a short demonstration.
Let's see how powerful he still is.
Amazing Low Kick
Demonstration
Yes. Takeda-san, please start.
Three?
3 Bats!
Three bats!
Let's stop this.
Yes, stop this.
It's impossible.
What is that?
Incredible!
SUCCESSFUL!
Succeeded!
He broke the three bats in half!
Great.
He'll be kicking as powerful as you just witnessed.
Why does he keep peeking at us?
I wonder if he dislikes you two?
But I saw him at Hyatt, he was very polite.
So first up is...
ONEAL FRANCE Team.
1st ROUND                    ONEAL FRANCE Airline
Question.
Huh?
Please answer in 10 seconds.
Q:  Famous 2nd Generation Celebrity
A famous 2nd generation Japan celebrity.
Are you ready?
Start!
Sato Kouichi
Huh?  You chose him?
Let me think..
Yamada.
Yamada-san
Rui Yamada..
Who?  Who?
Weak
Ai-chan.  That's no good!
2nd Person Out
2nd person OUT.
Who?
Famous Japanese 2nd Generation Celebrities
Takashima Masahiro.                Takanobu                 Mifune Mika                Sekine Mari
Matsuda Shota                    IMALU                              Kanda Sayaka
Takashima Masanobu-san, Nasahiro-san. Also Mifune Mika-chan..
Before that,
Who's that Yamada whoever-san?
It's 2nd generation..
So I think she meant the renaissance guy?
The renaissance Yamada?
Yamada Rui 53rd
(Higedanshaku)
From Higedanshaku?
He is 53rd generation.
This will definitely affect the result..
This isn't good.
OK, let's move on to CHUNENTAL Team!
We'll try our best!
1st ROUND                            CHUNENTAL Airline
CHUNENTAL Team, please answer from Shohei-san.
Celebrity whose name contains Chinese characters for East, West, North or South.
Q: Celebrity names containing Chinese characters for East, West, North or South
Are you ready?  Here you go, start!
Nishida Toshiyuki
Nishida Toshiyuki.
Higashino Koji!
OK!
Higa.. Higa..
Azuma Mikihisa
Azuma Mikihisa          Higashiyama Noriyuki        Nishida Kouji(Waraimeshi)
Minamino Yoko                Minami Akina                 Kitajima Saburo                  Horikita Maki
Celebrities Whose Names Contains Chinese Characters for East, West, South or North
See?  This is impossible!
We can do it better, huh?
Yes, we can.
So stupid.
Nishi
(= West)
da Kouji
Next up is Gaasuu Team.  It starts from Tanaka-kun.
1st ROUND   Gaasuukurobikari Airline System
Question.  Answer within 10 seconds.
Q: Celebrity whose name starts with A and ends with Ko
Celebrity whose name starts with A and ends with Ko.
What is it!
It all of a sudden got harder.
Let me think... Aida Shoko!
Who? Ah... Akita Keiko.
Akita Keiko-san?
Which genre does she belong to?
Enka...
An Enka singer?
What about the back members, Yamazaki-san?
Akiyoshi Kumiko
How about Hamada-san?
We were talking about who it would be.
I think Yamazaki stole our answer.
That's so embarrassing!
That will also be judged.
During the training, they are allowed to laugh.  However, the worst CA selected by the judges will receive a Thai-kick as a punishment
Were you listening in?
Yes, he was!
No, I didn't listen in!  Teacher!  Teacher!
What do you think about this?  Fujioka-san...
It's not good.  But it can't be helped.
He forgave it.
Celebrities whose Name Starts with A and End with Ko
Asano Yuko                   Aiko                        Aota Noriko                            Asaoka Ruriko
Asano Atsuko                Akino Yoko               Akimoto Junko              Anno Moyoko
Surprisingly, it seems to be OK with him.
Oh, that's good.
Next up is KimoITALIA Team.
1st ROUND                    KimoITALIA Airline
Question. Please answer within 10 seconds.
What are titles of single songs by SMAP.
Q: Title of a SMAP Hit Single
Here you go, start!
"The Only Flower in the World"
"Dynamite Honey"
"Gambarimasho"
What?  "Dynamite Honey"?  It's "Dynamite"!
There's a song like that, huh?
There are many.  Like "Gambarimasho", "KANSHA Shite" and "Lion Heart"
SMAP's Single Songs
Ganbarimasho                          Lion Heart                           Aoi Inazuma
Yozora No Mukou                        $10                       Dangan Fighter
"Celery", "Celery"!
"Celery".  Yes, that's correct.  That's the answer.
There is really a lot.
Today's guests really suck.
You can't even reach the 3rd person.  Try harder.
Shall we move on to the 2nd round?
Let's move on.
2nd ROUND                      ONEAL FRANCE Airline
It's ONEALFRANCE Team!
Question.
Celebrity whose initial is T.Y.
Q: Celebrity whose initial is T.Y.
That's "T.Y."
Are you ready?  Here you go, start!
Tanaka Yuko
Takahashi Yoko
Tanaka Youji
There are men.
KABA-Chan!
There is Takenouchi Yutaka.
Celebrities Whose Initials Are T.Y.
Takenouchi Yutaka          Takeuchi Yuko          Tanaka Yoshitake
Toake Yukiyo          Tomita Yasuko          Takahashi Yumiko
Takeuchi Yuko as well.
Next up is CHUNENTAL Team.  Starting from Shohei-san.
2nd  ROUND                         CHUNENTAL Airline
What are titles of Japanese School Dramas?
Q: Titles of Japanese School Dramas
Are you OK?　Ready?
Like "Tobidase! Seishun"
Here you go.
"Tobidase! Seishun" is already said by Matsumoto-san, so don't use it.
Are you ready?  Here you go, start!
Taiyo...
"Taiyo Ga Kureta Kisetsu"
This is your fault, Shohei-san.
That was no good.
Giving him so much time and ending up like that.
There's a lot more, huh.
Fujioka-san, isn't it very easy to give just one drama title?
Yeah.
Well, it's hard when I'm asked all of a sudden.
He couldn't!
Nothing!?
That's what they have to do in this game.
I think Kano Sisters got something.  Any school dramas that you can remember?
What about you?  Mika-san.
"Necchu Jidai" or...
"Necchu Jidai"  Right.
Japanese School Dramas
3-nen B-gumi              Kinpachi Sensei                Kyoshi Bin Bin Monogatari          Gokusen
Rookies                                    Hana Yori Dango                                     Water Boys
You couldn't you come up with even one?
I was panicking!
When one answer comes out, nothing more comes out.
Only Shohei-san keeps acting as a woman.
Thank you for your cooperation.
So now, next up is Gaasuu Team.
2nd ROUND       Gaasuukurobikari Airline System
Shall we start from Tanaka-san?
Question.　Answer within 10 seconds.
Name the celebrities whose names contain either Spring, Summer, Winter or Fall.
Q: Celebrities whose name contains either
Spring, Summer, Winter or Fall
Any of them can be included.  Everyone ready?
Start!
Kondo Haruna
Chiaki!
Natsuki Mari
Sakamoto Fuyumi
Aki Takejyo
Aki Takejyo... The Chinese character for her Aki doesn't mean Fall. Wrong!
Thai Kick!
What's going on?  Matsumoto-san.
"Sakamoto Fuyumi" was taken from me.
I've never thought I would fight over "Sakamoto Fuyumi" with my partner.
You've got plenty of time to think.  Please prepare at least 2 people.
Celebrities Whose Names Contain Either of the Four Seasons
Matsuyama Chiharu         Miura Haruma          Natsukawa Jun               Wakatsuki Chinatsu
Akimoto Yasushi                    Akino Taisaku               Moto Fuyuki
Hey, we still haven't seen a team clear everything within 10 seconds!
Next up is KimoITALIA Team.
From Fujimoto-san.
2nd Round                       KimoITALIA Team
Question.
Q:  Name the characters from "Kyojin no Hoshi"
Characters from "Kyojin no Hoshi".  I think the answers are limited.
Start!
Hoshi Ittetsu
Samon Hosaku
Hoshi Hyuma
Hanagata Mitsuru
Hoshi Akiko
KimoITALIA Team succeeded!
This is what I wanted to see!
Difficult, difficult!
Answer in 10 seconds!
FINISHED
CA Joint Training #1
This is the end of
"Let's answer in 10 seconds" game.
We did it!  We won!
The worst CA chosen by the judges will receive a Thai kick
Fujioka-san.  Who's answer was the worst?
Who's answer was the worst?
Which answer from Shohei-san was the worst?
It must be him.  It can only be him.
For 10 seconds it was only "Uh", "Ah".
All he did was get phlegm in his throat for 10 seconds.
But it might be someone you least expect.
I think it might surprise you, like "Is it me!?"
Fujioka-san is thinking hard
We thought it would be only one person.
Fujioka-san has someone in his mind.
Fujioka-san seems to have made up his mind.
Kyoko-san, what do you think about his opinion?
Mika-san and I have a different opinion.
So, let's make it two people instead.
2 CAs will receive Thai kick
OK, Chairman.  Please make your announcement!
Well, it is kind of... I feel a bit sorry.
I feel sorry after seeing the kick.
I feel bad.
Is it Endo-kun?
It can't possibly be me?
Really.  Today, I'm really kind of...
He used his ex wife's name and still,
That's right!
he was chosen somehow.
Endo-san OUT!
No way!
Serious?
This is gonna be really dangerous if you move.
Give me a count.
What should I do?  Can I stay still like this?
He's looking for the bathroom.
He's searching for the toilet.
This is no good!
My asshole is torn.
Shohei-san, let's go.
Who did Kano sisters choose?
We think it should be...
Yamazaki-san.
Don't go against the flow!
Wait!  Wait!  No!
Viewers must think of either of you two.
It can't be helped.   It's done.
I'll participate in a different scene later.
No, I'm serious.
Just hurry and do it.
Hey, no!  Wait!  Wait!
We still have a lot more to do.
So let's just get it done.  Please.
Stand up here.
It was decided already.
Takeda-san, please!
Please start!
Move your hand out of the way!
After this a shocking training will appear!!
Why did Yamazaki-san get chosen?
"Monmari Battle"!
CA Joint Training #2
Monmari Battle
For a CA who works in the sky for a long time, endurance is essential.
CA Joint Training #2
Monmari Battle
For the CA who works in the sky over
long periods, endurance is essential.
Patience.  This is hard.
CA Joint Training #2   Monmari Battle
Rules
2 members from each team become either an Answerer or a "Monmari"
This is a famous game in Gaki.
Monmari
Answerer
Whoever gets two wrong answers receives an ass in the face punishment
If you lose, you will receive an embarrassing punishment.
Monmari: Cunning Takeyama
Answerer: Shofukutei Shohei
Monmari: Chihara Seiji
Answerer: Fujimoto Toshifumi
CA Joint Training #2
Monmari battle
1st Round
CHUNENTAL Airline
KimoITALIA Airline
Firstly...CHUNENTAL Airline VS KimoITALIA Airline.
Which team is going to win...?
You are eager to show your underwear.
Please sit with your rear end facing your opponent.
Please scoot up little bit.
I wonder what up with Seiji-kun's red underwear.
What a sight.
I don't like the line.  The middle line on the pants.
Everyone, are you ready?
His glasses might break.
Will they?
His glasses might break.  Well, let's see what happens.
Maomi-chan, let's start.
First question is...
Names of convenience stores.
Q:  Convenience Store Names
Eh, there aren't too many.
Are you ready?  Please name the convenience stores.
Start!
Lawson
Family Mart
Huh?
Let me think...Eh...
Monpari
Huh?  Monpari?
Alright!
Convenience Stores
Seven Eleven                  CircleKSunkus                       Mini Stop
Three F                    Natural Lawson                          Poplar
Now since Shouhei-san couldn't answer correctly,
"Monmari" Start!
Monmari Starts!
It looks like it just wont stop.
It's coming toward you.
I hate it somehow.
Shohei-san is staring at it.
He's staring at you, Takeyama.
Shohei-san is staring at you.
He is being embarrassed.
Are you really embarrassed?
He didn't take off his glasses.
TO EXAMINE!
Shohei Reaching The End
Next up is Shouhei-san.  Please do your best.
The theme is...
Members of Takeshi Gundan.
Q: Members of Takeshi Gundan
Takeshi Gundan's member names.  They are Shohei-san's friends.
Are you ready?  Here you go, start!
Guadalcanal Taka
Tsumami Edamame
Rusher Itamae
Dankan
Great Gidayu
Huh?
Yanagi Yurei
We won!  We won!
Shohei-san, there are more.
Let me think...
Huh?
Well...
Ahh!
Too bad!
"Monmari"
is going to Shouhei-san with glasses on.  Please start!
Ugh, gross!
Monmari is successfully completed.
Shohei-san, go get a Thai kick now.
Shohei-san, are you OK?
Go get a Thai kick now.
Shohei-san, you're not making sense, what's wrong?
He's grossed out.
Let's move on.
We will announce the next challenger.
Mommari
ONEAL FRANCE Airline
GAS
CA Joint Training #2
Monmari Battle
Round 2
Answerer
Monmari
"Monmari" member from Gasu Team is Yamasaki Housei san!
Yamasaki
And Answerer is Matsumoto-san.
Matsumoto
Now the competitor...
From ONEAL France Team, "Monmari" member is Majima-san.
Majima
And the answerer is Chris-san.
Chris
Will Majima-san's come to me?
Yes, it will come to you, Matsumoto-san.
I'm afraid I might faint.
It's like full anesthesia.
How much can he bear..
No No No!
He seems to be motivated.
That one is fine.
HEY WAIT A MINUTE!!
That underwear looks like it has been worn for four seasons.
It must have been worn for quite a long time.
Since when did you become such a person, Majima-san?
I'm embarrassed
That's our line.   We are embarrassed.
So now, are you ready?
Question.
Question is Pink Lady's songs.
Q:  Pink Lady Songs
Songs from "Pink Lady"!
Chris might be good at this.
Here you go, start!
Captain Pepper
Southpaw
Chameleon
The correct name?
Chameleon'77
Pink Lady Songs
Carmen'77                               Sinbad on the beach                                  Wanted
UFO                    Monster                                              Chameleon Army
"Carmen"...
That's right, "Carmen'77".
Now, please start!
Wow.  This is so exciting!
Yes, Matsumoto-san?
In the very middle, I see a little bulge sticking out.
I'm not joking.  See?
There's something there, right?
What is it?
Just some material.
Something is sticking out!
SOMETHING IS STICKING OUT!
That's nothing.  On to the question.
Question.
Famous celebrity Trios
Q: Famous Celebrity Trios
Celebrity Trios!
Start!
Candies
Let's Go Sanbiki.
Tokyo 03
Neptune
Eh?  Eh?  Eh?
There's a lot more you should know.
Ah!  Ah!
Eh?  Eh?  Wait...
Matsumoto-san is in a pinch!
Wait.  Trio.  I know there is a trio...
That was too bad.
Here we go.
Start!
Now.  Amano-san...
One more time!
Matsumoto-san, how about another go?
ENOUGH!
I wonder if this works.  Refill time!
Congratulations!
Matsumoto-san.
It's sad.  It smelled like soap.
It made me feel sad.
Majima-san.  How do you feel?
It feels good
Now all the trainings are finished.
CA Joint Training Scores
GAS
CHUNENTAL
ONEAL FRANCE
KimoITALIA
So the King of cabin attendants is
Kimo ITALIA Team.  Congratulations!
King Of CA
KimoITALIA Airline
Congratulations!
What about finishing this training with a Thai kick?
Did you find anyone that was just bad all around?
Since I'm impressed with their comedian souls, no punishment for this time!
No punishment!
He Ignores The Obvious!
He's kind!  He's kind!
So kind!
He is not for variety shows!
5 Hours Since The Start
Arriving back at the training room, they are having some snacks.
I'm getting tired.
What Matsumoto is holding is...
Chocolate Baumkuchen from the fridge.
Fake Baumkuchen made of hard material
In fact, it made of hard inedible material.
A fake.
Something Found In The Drawer
Downtown Dolls
It's a pair.
Matsumoto looks more realistic.
I'm sorry to ask you this now, but has anyone tried eating this?
No, I didn't
Can you get one from the fridge and try eating it?
Huh, why?
Why is it?
GakiFiles Subs
www.gakifiles.blogspot.com
Facebook: GakiFiles Subs
Translation:
Zurui
eChie
Spot Translation:
Vanilla
Timing:
SSSI
Chidegi
Dith
Typesetting:
SSSI
Try it.
This.
At the time I wasn't too sure yet.
I still didn't know what it actually was.
I see.
What is this?
What is it?
Hey wait a minute.
I can't bite it.
Isn't this fake?
This is a sponge right?
Huh?  Who would do that?
Isn't it something like...
food sample?
Yeah.
This is getting to be really
malicious.
That's what it is.
This is not "no-laughing".
Yeah.
At GAS, not only to take care of inquiries from our customers,
but also to create a good working environment for our employees, we set up a general call center.
Here it comes.
Finally.
It came.
Let's take a look at a day at the call center.
Receptionist
Sato Mina
This time we get assistance from Sato san and
Ohnishi Hideko san.
Receptionist
Ohnishi Hideko
Hello.
This is the general call center.
How may I help you?
(Foreigner) I lost my baggage.
-Huh?
(Foreigner) What should I do?
Roast?
Well..
Ro...Ro...
Oh.  Would you prefer chicken?
I'll switch to chicken.
I tried not to...
He's unbelievable.
Wait a second.
This guy is going to be killer.
As soon as this started, I...
I think so.
Endo and Yamazaki are so weak.
(Foreigner) I said I lost my baggage.  Do you understand?
Yes!  Well... I do understand.
(Foreigner) Tell me what I meant then.
Well...
Let me think....
In the baggage...
Well...
Like crispy chicken...
Potato...
And potatoes...
Well...
Pickles...
Do...
gs and something...
stabbed with food picks.
A little bit of...
pickolos...
Pickolos?
Well...
That's all in that.
It doesn't make any sense!
What the hell are pickoles?
I tried hard not to laugh...
Ouch!
I tried not to...
Pickles
or
dogs
Stuff stabbed with food picks.
What?
A little bit of
pickolos
Well...
That's all in that.
Stuff stabbed with food picks..
(Foreigner) That's enough.  You are useless!
Normally
I
I...
Ah.
Tough job, huh?
We get a lot of different things happening here.
Hello.  This is the general call center.
How may I help you?
(Newbie CA) I'm going to graduate from junior collage this year,
and start working as CA next year.
Yes
(Newbie CA) Please teach me 3 must-dos for CA.
Yes!
So
Please let me tell you now.
Thank you.
Number 1.
You have to come flying.
Doesn't make sense.  Seriously.
What the hell is he talking about?
What is he saying?
That was great!
How can you be so patient?
Number 1.
You have to come flying.
Number 2.
You shouldn't bump.
Hey wait.  What the hell is he?
What?  What?
What is he thinking?
I don't know!
He's thinking of something else?
What is he thinking of?
Please stop it!
Number 2.
You shouldn't bump.
What does he mean?
Number 3.
You shouldn't spill over.
Hey.  Wait a second!
I guess I laughed, huh!
So you...
This is tough.
Tough.
This is scary.  I hope this will end soon.
Look carefully when you hit.  Damn!
(Newbie CA)  Understood.  That's enough.
Oh..Thank you
for your politeness...
She was pissed.
We...
Well
See you again...
Ah...
A day in the call center will be continued...
To be continued.
This is not finished yet.
Huh?  What..
My butt reached has reached it's limit...
5 hours and 30 minutes since the start of the duty.
There is a serious situation for Matsumoto who has a problem with his knee.
Hey.  Can I take a leak?
Did you bring it?
*Their training room is on the 3rd floor. They must go down the stairs to the 1st floor restroom.
This is portable.
Portable Toilet Prepared By Staff
Is that it?
It's for the car.
Go outside.
Hey.  Go outside and do it.
There's another room .
Yes.
Could you go somewhere people are not around?
This room is for everyone to relax.
Yeah.
This is our relaxing room.
Yes.
No.  Let me do it in the corner here.
There's another room next to this room.
Yes, the next door.
Isn't it better if I'm here just in case something funny happens?
It's OK.
Nah, that's fine.
There wont be anything.
Matsumoto Leaves To The Smoking Room Alone
Begins To Make Traps For Matsumoto
Keep an eye out for him.
Wow.  It smells like cigarettes!
Why did you get out?
He didn't like the smell.
Oh!  Stop stop atop!
What the hell are you guys doing!
Why everyone...
Why everyone?
It was too fast to return.
The room was so stinky.
My butt is beginning to hurt.
Mine too.
Hey what are you doing?
I went to the room, but it smelled like cigarettes.
Is there..
I can't do it in such a place.  No, I can't.
But don't do it in here.
Doesn't have to be here does it?
What about hallway?
No way, man.  I thought I was more decent than that.
I've been trying hard in this field since I started at 18.
Now, before turning 50, I don't want to be forced to take a piss in the hallway.
Too long!
But it's true.
It's a different story.
No, it's not!
It can't be helped!
But...
Anywhere else but this room, please.
Yeah.
Yes.
It sounds a little bit lonely.
What.. Lonely?
I want to do it where people are around.
That's wrong.
OK then, the recessed space is fine.
Hey hey hey hey!!
What the hell are you doing?
Hey hey hey!
No no no!
Let's go outside.
Don't act like an old man making excuses.
OUCH!  OUCH!
No it doesn't hurt.
No it doesn't.
Don't play dumb.
You're trying to make traps while I'm gone!
No way!
No we won't.
You can do it there!
Can I watch here?
Yes you can.
Again Starting To Make Traps
In the drawer.
You can put in there too.
Put them all.  Put them all!
All of them!
I could see everything.  Also heard you said " Put them all!'.
I first thought you were talking about this.
Why would I tell you to put them all in there..
All...
I thought you were talking to me like casual friends.
OK then, I'll do it here.
Hey wait.
Is it possible to get only "it" outside?
Huh?  What do you mean?
From in between the door...
This is what a pervert would do.
I've had it!
Hey!
I've had enough..
Give me a break..
It hurts anyway.
No, I'm not trying to be mean or anything.
I just simply want to
take a piss.
That's rght.
What shall we do?
Your concern is the smell right?
Yes.  The smell and sound.
It's really disgusting.
The piss of a 50 year old man, right?
It's dirty.
I'm not 50 yet.  I'm still 48..
I am not a 50 year old man.
What about my idea?
Let his body stay here...
Let Matsumoto-san's body stay here and..
Here it comes.  The Pervert Plan.
We can't compromise more than this.
You know what.
I'll be here in this room, leaving my penis outside while wearing a female costume.
That's true.
Matsumoto-san.  All you have to do is just quickly go outside and do it!
He's strange.
What about inside out?
Huh?
I go outside and leave my penis inside.
It doesn't make sense!
Hey you!
It's gonna hurt as I'm not wearing my underwear.
Isn't it much better to have his body inside?
I wonder if I can take a piss like that.
Do you have to pull it all the way down?
Do you have to expose your ass?
You can pull down only the front.
I don't want you to pull it down so much.
This is an awful scene.
He's a super pervert.
This is wrong, right?
This is definitely wrong, right?
Give me a break!
Hey!
I can't.  I can't.
You can watch us from the window.
We will be just sitting here.
Yes.
We will be sitting without doing anything else. So don't worry.
He's watching
He's closing his eyes.
He wouldn't bring it back, would he?
If he does, please dump it asap.  OK, Endo?
No way!
Look!  Look!  Look!
Ugh..
No no no!
It's already solid. Try touching it.
No, I don't want.
Try touching it.
I'm serious.
It's your piss right?
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
Watch out!
Let's stop it.
No way!
Cut it out seriously!
STOP IT REALLY!
What are you doing!
What's wrong with you!
It's your piss!
No no..
This is solid, so you don't have to worry.  I'm serious.
We'll take your word for it
It's solid.  Seriously.
If you say so..
I'm sorry but this is how I have to do it.
It can't be helped.
Please dump it
Are you telling me?
Yes.
Grabs The Dirtiest Part
That's right, Endo.
That's the dirtiest part!
I'll take that
You're right!
I didn't realize it.
You can't make it seem like I'm the evil one.
No, we are not trying to make you the evil one.
At 3:00 PM, the five newbies are finally heading to that place.
Hey.
Your effort has been finally recognized,
so now you can work at the airport.
What?  All of a sudden.
We are going to the airport now.
Airport?
Finally Airport Duty Work!
Finally.
Let's go.
Everyone, please get on.
Leaving the training school, they finally start their duties at the airport.
However after this, tyrannical assassins are waiting for them!
Your doll looked just like you huh?
It really did.
It did.
That doll really looks like you!
Later on, it will cause new problems as you may expect.
Yes.
Yes!
And Jimmy-chan..
Jimmy-chan.
He's awesome.
Every time he gets me.
This year was especially awful.
Yes.
The way his tongue slipped was almost like being possessed by the supernatural.
HUH?
Picolos..
Please never mind me.
Also the baumkuchen, huh?
I had no doubt that I could bite it.
You deftly bit into it.
I thought that something was wrong with my teeth.
You thought something was wrong with your teeth.
Leaving the training school, they are heading to the airport.
Like everyone knows, it won't be an easy trip.
Everyone, it is a long way to the airport.
Are you sure?
Long way to go?
What's the distance?
It is a tough question.  I can't explain the distance.
Is it?
You are kind of laughing.
Yes he is.
Your face, Zaki-san.
Because of the sun light.
It is so bright that I can't help but making this face.
You changed expressions.
And you laughed.
It's not right!
I don't want to get out for something so stupid.
This won't be used.
I'm sorry for you too, but this won't be used.
Arrival At A Bus Stop
No kidding.
What what what?
Serious?
Is she boarding?
Rola Is Boarding The Bus While Laughing
Why is she here...
This was really terrible.
She made us laugh... with her laugh.
I didn't laugh.
Rola-chan makes me laugh.
Rola is laughing.
I can see your underwear.
Oh, the bus is leaving.
What's wrong?
Bye bye.
Moca, what's wrong?
Oh, I can't open it.
Oh, I could.
Rola's Favorite Pet Dog Moca
OK, I understand.
Are you hungry?
Do you want to eat something?
Do you want to hold her?
What is she talking about?
Nothing is going on
Nothing is going on, surely
What is she doing?
I was waiting for something to happen.
Right.
She came all of a sudden, but she is already so friendly.
What?
Are you hungry?
Tell me again?
Oh, that's right!
This happened about a year ago
Rola's Funny Story
When I kept Moca,
I still keep Moca.
I don't quite understand.
What?
What the hell.
It's not funny.
She still keeps it.
Moca, scared?  Are you scared?
Rola's Funny Story
Then, let me continue the story.
I have kept it.
Then you know what?
Oh, she is excited.
Then I was walking down on the street,
The place was called crossing,
where a lot of white lines are drawn.
When I was taking a walk with Moca for the first time,
in the middle of the street, Moca made
Poop.
I was so embarrassed
when people, like an old man without hair
was staring at me.
So I just, threw away the poop.
Finished.
An old man without hair..
What is this?
It's not funny at all.
We've had enough.
Bow!
Oh, she is mad.
Moca Is Scared Of The Black Army
She is so mad.
She is mad at them.
I'm sorry, Moca.
She got surprised.  She got surprised.
She didn't expect that old men dressed in female costumes would be a hit.
Here you go.  Go in.
Both sides are open.
Enough!
No more laughs!
What are you doing?
Rola-chan, please get off already.
OK.  Bye bye!
Are you getting off?
Yes.  Time to go.  Bye bye!
Time...
Not distance?  Time?
Bye bye.  Take care.
Oh, I'm scared!
It was terrible.
It was so terrible.
Yes.
The dog was so scared.
I wonder where you guys are looking the whole time.
I couldn't keep looking.
I basically kept looking.
All the time?
You shouldn't.
Arrival At A Bus Stop
I'm scared.
A Bad Boy Boards The Bus
Otaki Hideji (Sekine Tsutomu)
Matsumoto was laughing.
His face looked gold.
I could see the line.
In early evening.
You love women huh.
Especially small, pretty cute
girls working backstage.
* Endo has been dating Sekine's ex manager.
This is cruel.
It is.
I heard your most favorite is big boobs, correct?
Not.
No, well..
Big boobs are good, huh?  Boobs.
Hey my head is not held up yet.
What are you doing?
I was curious about the bad boy.
I heard you have a daughter.
Does she hold up her hard?
Yes
But humans can forget very easily.
So remember this.
Soon or later, she will enter the rebellious phase.
She will start resisting.
Whenever you feel angry at her,
please remember how cute she used to be, not holding up her head.
See?  Macchan.
Don't forget this.
Input this in your mind.  OK?
I understand.  I totally understand.
You've been showing a terrible attitude.
He Gives Instructions To The Bad boy
What, old man.  Got a problem?
You called me old man, didn't you?
You seem to be pretty confident but
have you ever lost in a fight?
Never once.  I am invincible.
OK then, I'll teach you that today.
Huh?
I'll teach you that today.
No room!
Otaki Wins By A Mile With An Arm Lock Cross Hold!
Otaki won in such a small space.
What the hell.
You can move.
That was so quick.
That was quick.
It was.
Yes.
After a fight, we should be friends.
So shall we have tea or something?
Wow
Yasoshima Hiroyuki
I was careless.
Right elbow left elbow, look at them alternately.  Right elbow left elbow, look at them alternately.
Right elbow left elbow, look at them alternately.
2700 Tsune Is Boarding
Look at the shoe.
Look at the ankle.
Look at the knee.
Look at the thigh.
Look at the waist.
Look at the side.
Look at the chest, look at the shoulder.
Hideji is coming.
Otaki Hideji Joins
What the hell.
* They already laughed, but please keep watching.
Awesome.
When I show the back of the card,
the card will disappear.  It's a magic.
There are no tricks.
There are really no tricks.
By any chance if anyone among you
is suspicious,  right elbow left elbow...
It got so fast.
I never expected.
2 stages.  No one expected.
It was just so funny.
They passed trials throughout the journey.  Finally the airport is just around the corner!!
Everyone, here we are.
Finally.
I can see the airport.
It's the real airport.
This is Ibaraki airport.  Please work well as GAS employees.
The stage of No-laughing is Ibaraki Airport.
At this genuine airport, new trials are waiting.
Wow, this is real.
Huh?  That's the real terminal!
Awesome.
Everyone, we arrived.  Please take your CA bags and get off.
(When Going To Work) The CA's Must Have Their Roller Bag
Everyone gets a bag?
This is mine, huh?
I'm fine with this.
OK.
This is how it usually goes.
OK.  Everyone, let's go.
Wow!
This is serious.
Yeah.
Everyone, come this way.
Wow!
Are you serious?
There are counters.
Airport Lobby
There are GAS counters.  Awesome, huh?
I can't tell what is real or fake.
This is great.
Is it really OK that we do this somewhere like this?
Awesome, huh?
Counters are there.
GAS Boarding Counter
Everyone, look.  This is an international airport.
It's bright, huh?
There is a foreign pilot.
Foreign Pilot Chats With CA
Chad Mullane
I've seen that little guy.
I know him.
It's Chad.
See, this is an international airport.
We can't laugh at this, huh?
This is so ordinary.
Let's go this way.
Wow!  Everyone, that's a Zombie!
Zombie Appears In The Airport Lobby
What the hell is it?
I don't think he's allowed to be here?
I doubt he has a passport.
I saw a Zombie.  It surprised me!
Right?
Yes.
There was a Zombie.
What's real in here?
Are we exiting already??
He laughed.
Hamada-san was laughing.
No I didn't.
You did, when Matsumoto-san spoke.
Yes that's true.
Not at all.
I don't recognize people.
I don't understand if it's real or work.
Wow, this is great!
The GAS is really standing out, Fujiwara-san!
Newbie Training Room
Wow, look.
This is the famous..
Suga Duck.
Well it is the symbol of GAS.
This time, I can really see their effort.
Yes, I think so.
This is the waiting room for newbie attendants.
Finally things are becoming more CA-like.
Really yeah.
Really yeah.  Now that we're at the airport.
But it's uplifting, huh?
Please take a break here for a while.
OK.
The 5 members are taking a little break in the waiting room.
However, one thing remains to be cleared before the start of their duties.
I wonder if there's anything in these drawers.
Cautious Of The Drawers
Yes, I've been wondering if it starts all over again.
Hey Housei-san, please check it.
Huh?  I don't want any more of...
Empty
Huh?
Something Is In The Drawer
What is it?
Matsumoto's Make-a-face Game
There was still something in there.
This is a make-a-face game.
That seems so.
Are they telling us to play with this?
I think so.
What about the other drawers?  Let me check..
Wanna check?
Matsumoto Doll
This is hot
I'm blowing it
SEE?
Don't lie.
Hey you!
This is what I set up!
I don't know why this is here.
Here they come.
I don't like when they pass here, because I have to move my chair every time.
Hey Endo, please put it away.
OK.
Continuation with Matsumoto's Drawer
Hamada Doll
This is also what I set up.
It can't be helped.
The underwear.
I don't get why it's wearing the female underwear.
Nothing there?
I doubt there's anything in my drawers.
Wow!  Again, again...
Again, Altered Photo of Yamazaki
How many times...
They want to make it seem like you love it.
I've had it.
I've had enough of it really.
Just check them all
OK.
OK, there's nothing.
I don't think there's anything new
Probably nothing in yours too.
Suga Kenji Doll
Anything new...
Nothing new.
This is the only new item.
Is this the only one that is new?
Only this make-a-face game.
Right elbow, left elbow
Look at them alternately
No no no.  You were laughing definitely.
No, I wasn't.
I was just looking at you, thinking that you were laughing.
I'm so stressed that it's such a cramped area!  I want to move everything forward.
You're so noisy!  Always complaining.
Right elbow, left elbow  Look at them alternately
Matsumoto-san,  what kind of underwear is Suga doll wearing?
Could you check?
Did both of them have on the strawberry panties?
Yeah.
Wow.  Commando.
Suga Kenji Doll Without Underwear
No underwear.
It means he gets suntan without underwear.
I don't want to see it.
Excuse me, but I didn't laugh.
Shall we do this?
Matsumoto Tries The Make-a-face Game
How does it work?
So I will...
I'll pass you the parts.
You have to be blindfolded.
Please close your eyes.
Eyebrow.
Eye.
Can I touch the eyebrow?
Yes, you can.
Eye.
Mouth.
Is this the last piece?
Yes.
- OK.
It's done.
Matsumoto's Work
I tried hard not to laugh!
The eyes are up-side-down.
Can you do it next, Hamada-san?
Hamada Tries The Make-a-face Game
We still have..
some time to kill.
Mouth.
I have no clue.
Try checking it once, since the mouth is so off.
Hamada's Work
Hey you.
The mouth is so off.
You can do that?
Tanaka, Try it.
OK.
You have to do it at least once.
Tanaka Tries The Make-a-Face Game
Yes, at least once.
It can be really good sometimes.
I want you to make it perfect.  So we can say...
Wow, that's awesome!
Just like a regular picture!
Blank Side
Not yet, not yet.
Not yet.
Which part?
The nose.  I'll start from the center.
If you can get the nose in the right postion,
it can turn out to be a real picture Matsumoto-san.
I see.
Center.
What's this?
It's the eye.
Facial spacing is really important.
Looking good
He's a natural
Yes, open your eyes.
Is it done?
Tanaka's Work
Oh, sorry.
It's the wrong side.
I thought something was wrong.
This is up-side-down.
So it doesn't stick.
What a face..
But this is fun
PM 5:00,
Duties at the airport are broad, and sometimes problems like this can occur.
Everyone, there's a trouble!
Huh?
The labor union that constructs landing fields at the airport
is striking
because of their low wages.
It has nothing to do with us.
Starting now at the neighborhood public hall,
the Labor union and our General Affairs Division are going to have a discussion.
Everyone can you please attend this meeting?
Is it necessary for us?
Laborers Strike
Discussion With Airport Employees
It's a pain in the ass.
Such a pain.
Public hall?
Wow a bus is waiting for us.
It's dark.
Cold.
Please take your seats.
We're riding a bus again.
Cold.
The bus is taking the five members to the neighborhood public hall.
Airport employees and labors.
Wonder who they are..
What is he doing?
He sometimes acts
as if he was a hooker.
Here we are.
Excuse me.
Here we go
Discussion Swiftly Reaches It's Climax
This was really really tough.
Hey!
Stop complaining.  Just sit down there!
We are not complaining...
We didn't speak at all.
What are you going to do about this!
We have been working hard!
But it was funny.
- Yes.
OK then, I'll come get you guys later.
We can't raise your pay,  considering  the quality of your work!
If you're unwilling to do it,
let's fight against each other!
OK, let's do it then!
Negotiations Failed
Battle With Their Bodies
They make decisions by doing this?
I think if would be better if you just discussed it verbally.
Airport Employees Are Ready To Fight
I'm ready to fight!
Labor Leader
Kendo Kobayashi
Bring it on!
Here it comes!
Hey!  Do you guys know what this is?
What is it?
This is Plastic Bottle Launcher!
Wow, it looks awesome!
A regular person would normally take a hit on the butt.
But our Kuro-chan, he cant take it on his chin!
Laborer
Kuro-chan
(Yasuda Dai Circus)
I'm ready!
I'll put as much air as it can take, OK?
I'm ready, fill it up!
Receive a punch to the chin from a bottle rocket powered glove
It can take more!
It's making a strange noise...
Now it's fully powered!
OK!
Are you ready, Kuro-chan?
Yes!
Go!
A Glancing Blow
You guys are not fighting at all!
Not at all.
You just got wet a little bit.
A perfect hit!
OK, that was good.
Let's move on to the next fight!
Bring it out!
What is this?
It looks like a washing machine.
This is obviously a washing machine.
Here we have some Ramen.
* Ramen = a bowl of hot Chinese noodle soup.
Can anyone eat this in the washing machine?
This is impossible.
General Affairs Division
Iwao Nozomu
(Football Hour)
I doubt someone who is only a desk jockey can do this!
He can't!
Go for it!
Let's see it!
Hurry up and get in there
Didn't you rehearse this?  If so, you should be able to get in there at least!
Yes, that's it.
Eat a bowl of hot Ramen in the special washing machine
Is this serious?
This is crazy.
Yeah.
It's hot
Be careful
It's even better for me if it's hot.
He serious?
Is he?
Just like that?
START!
That's enough!
His right nipple was centered as he rolled around!
So you Officers can only handle Ramen after all.
What are you saying?
On the other hand, our Tanaka can handle Miso Nikomi Udon!
* Miso Nikomi Udon = A hot pot with thick miso flavored soup and noodle
Show them!
Hurry up
Hurry up and get out!
This doesn't matter at all.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
Like he's being born.
Laborer
Tanaka Takushi
(Ungirls)
This is super hot Miso Nikomi Udon.
It must be hard with his height.
He has to fold his body.
Eat a "super hot" Miso Nikomi Udon in the special washing machine
That looks hot.
It's so hot.
Hold the edge.
It's steaming hot
Leave it to me!
Rolling
Start!
This looks so tough!
Very scary.
He's still eating it.  He's still eating it.
He's tough.
HE'S BORN!
You can't even call that hot!
Bring "it" here!
Stop it!
Take a look at this, this is super hot Sara Udon!
* Sara Udon = a plate of hot thick noodle porridge
Sara Udon... Isn't it the specialty of Nagasaki?
That doesn't matter now!
It doesn't matter now, does it?
Our Haranishi will eat this with hands.
General Affairs Division
Haranishi Takayuki
Using his bare hands, finish a plate of super hot Sara Udon within 1 minute
It looks so good!
OK!  Go for it!
Start!
You didn't eat anything!
* The have already laughed, but please keep watching
Quail egg
It must have been hot!
He can't do it at all.
It's hot.
He still has time.
Why did you throw it away?
I'm tired
I'M TIRED
I CAN'T BREATHE
Go for it!
Why did you throw it down!
This is no good, Haranishi.
This can't be done!
It seems like
you guys are scared.
Yoshinobu is even better.  Right?
Laborer
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producer
Do it!
Move all the snakes into the black box within 1 minute
Let's see it.
OK!
Good luck.
Ready?
Start!
They are pretty aggressive huh.
They are kind of big.
Yes, they are.
They are big and thick.
You got scared!
He screamed
There's still time left.
Put it in the box.
Pull it with your left hand!
Just pull it.
Yes, that's how!
What the hell are you doing?
What is this?
Looks like an old folk story
I don't understand what he is trying to do.
What the hell!
Good job, Yoshinobu!
Bring it here!
Here it comes
This is very hot.
Watch out!
Our General Manager, doesn't get scared.  Even if this burns his butt!
Place the special material on his butt and light the fuse. When the lit fuse reaches the material, it instantly burns and disappears.
Yeah!
General Affairs GM
Degawa Tetsurou
Light it up!
Please do so!
OK!
OK GM, are you ready?
Please light it!
The fuse is so long
It's coming.
Bring it!
The fuse is long, huh.
Here it comes!
Hot!  Hot!
Hot!
COLD!
Degawa GM Pretends To Be Strong And Says "Cold"
It's cold!
It wouldn't be cold.
We can't stay quiet seeing this.
Yeah!
Bring me the double sized cotton.
I'll handle this.
He Tries Double The Amount
OK, I'm ready!
Fire!
This is a lot
Here it goes.
Aren't you scared?
Come on!  Come on!
It's coming.
Here it comes!
Come on!  Come on!
Fuse debris
OK.
Awesome!
That was tough huh.
Crazy.
That's how you do it.
Bring it out here!
The next thing brought out is
Konpeitou Candies On Tatami Mats
Konpeito is spread out on tatami mats.
* Konpeitou = tiny & hard sugar candies
It has got to hurt.
A Judo expert,
will flip him on to the mat.
A Judo expert will flip him on to the mat.
It will be painful.
This will be painful
Our Wakki with be thrown naked like this!
General Affairs Division
Wakki
(Penalty)
Are you OK?
Yes.
As I thought he's holding his neck.
OK, I'm ready!
OK, let's start.
Landed Hard On The Back And Butt
This is tough.
Show it to them!
This is...
heated liquid wax to pour on your head.
Pour heated liquid wax on head
Can you do it!?
OK, I can do it!
OK, go!
Not Enough Wax Was Used
It's getting hot.
Do you eventually feel the heat?
What the hell.
Iwao, show them how it's done!
Iwao can handle 2 buckets.  2 Buckets!
Huh?
There are a lot.
There are 3 buckets.  Hey!
3 buckets!
OK, go for it!
Here I go!
Hot!
Monster...
He is a monster.
This is a monster.
It's a monster!
Monster.  A monster!
What's with you!
Sit down.
Iwao!
Iwao!  Iwao!  Iwao!
Can this be aired?
Good.
Good job!
It's all over the floor.
This is a final round.
Yeah!
It will be, arm wrestling!
But regular arm wresting is boring so...
before we start, we'll insert air into each player's butt.
Then whoever makes a fart first will lose. How that?
What did he just say?
What is it?  Seriously.
What kind of rule is that.
Watch out.  Don't say it in a funny way.
OK!
Whoever makes a fart first will lose!
Fart doesn't matter.
I should just have to win in arm wrestling, right?
Ueshima-san.  Can I get your help?
OK!
Boss
Ueshima Ryuhei
(Dacho Club)
I said I'm going.
To begin with, can you take air in your butt?
Of course I can!  Moron.
You said that.
I'll do it.
I will.
Can you do that?
GM, can I get your help?
OK, I will!
OK, let me go!
Hard to believe that he can
just standby like that.
He is very boyish.
No way.
Am I OK?
Can you take Nozomu-chan backstage?
We are friends
I will be watching.
You will be right?
Yes, I will be.
Will you so?
Can you stick out your butt little more?
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
Are you OK?  Does it hurt?
What are you doing?
What are you guys doing?
Come on!
I don't want to watch this preparation...
Try to find a better position.
Does it hurt?  Are you OK?
No it doesn't.
What are you doing?
Not yet!  I haven't done it!
OK.  Try now.
Does it hurt?
No.
Hosshan Completes The Air Insertion
OK.
OK!
OK, wait.  Can you do mine, Ueshima-san?
Wait.. Mine is kind of dirty..
Hurry up!
It doesn't matter as he hasn't stood on the stage!
That's right!
Useshima hurry up!
Ueshima, hurry up and do it!
You do it first then
Can you do it again?
OK.  Like this?
Ueshima-san.
You've got so many warts.
That doesn't matter right now!
Damn!
We don't need to know that!
Hey, I will go!
Boss Ueshima's Butt Is Sensitive
We've had enough of this!
Be more patient!
They should be adding air at the same time, huh?
Yes, do it together.
That's enough
Are you OK?
It's full
Full?
OK, let's start!
OK, please add it now.
Hurry up!
What the hell!
I'm impressed.  You guys can really do well.
Isn't it fine to just finish the job you have right now?
Each other.
They Came To An Understanding
Do your best!
Now please go on.
Ryu-chan did it come out?
Huh?
Yeah, it feels like it's going to come out.
Ah, should I add some air?
He is amazing, it comes out soon.
Huh?  What is this?
Air going in.
Fart
Try harder!
It came out already!?
You better try harder!
Why did he let it out!
7 pm
They have returned to the airport, from now they will start their work in earnest.
Everyone it's over here.
Their first assignment is
to welcome Passengers at the check-in counter as the image of the airport.
Shall we line up here?
Boarding Counter
Wow this is cool.
Hamada, Matsumoto, Yamazaki...
It's starting
Yes.
Many Passengers will be coming so handle th... um, invite them.
I don't know how to do this, can you teach me.
Oh, you won't teach us?
If you just watch me, you will be fine
Welcome, we will keep this for you.
Yes.
Passengers Are Checking In
Here, you need to proceed to the 2nd boarding gate.
Please enjoy the comf... comfortable journey in the sky.
Yes.
You guys say it too.
We're not suppose to screw up like that though.
You guys say it correctly too. Start from the next customer.
Next Passenger Is Checking In
Here.
Please proceed to the 2nd boarding gate.
Yes.
Please enjoy the comfor...table journey in the sky.
Hey you guys say it.
Please enjoy the comfortable journey in the sky.
Endo, be sure to say it correctly to the next customer.
Yes.
Next Passenger Is Checking In
Isn't it written?
Somehow They React To The Passengers
It's his family.
Family?  No way.
The Endo Family Is Checking In
This is the Endo family.
They are his mother, father, and younger brother.
Oh hey Shozo.
How are you?
Long time no see.
Yes.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Toshihide-san (Father)
I am the father of Cocorico Endo.  Thank you for taking care of him.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you
Wait a second.
Nice to meet you?
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
He wasn't really trying to make us get hurt.
What kind of person is he?
Hamada-san, it's been a year.  Long time no see.
Yes.
It's been a year..
Thank you very much.
Tanaka-kun, long time no see.
Thank you always for being my son's friend.  Thank you very much.
Thank you, I'm glad to.
My hair has become so thin like this.
Look at this
What are you saying?
Heh Heh heh
The Endo Family's True Colors
What the hell.
Weird atmosphere.
Please proceed to the 2nd gate.
Is this ad-lib?
OK, now please proceed to the 2nd gate.
I'm sorry the 2nd gate please.
Nice to meet you.
Hamada-san, nice to meet you.  I am his younger brother.
You should all do it together.
Matsumoto-san, thank you for everything.
I am Endo's younger brother, um ..... Junji.
He Totally Forgot His Name
That is not good.
Wait a second.
It's surprising that he forgot his own name.
Ah sorry brother.
There is a letter from mom.
A letter from his mother Kimiyo to Shozo
Try reading it.
Can I read it?
Dear Shozo,
Four years have passed since you broke up with Chiaki-chan,
how are you with your new girlfriend, Masami-san?
Don't say her name
And I read in a magazine that,
Masami-san is in her late 20's and used to be a beautiful manager.
Right now, you guys live together?
If so, please remarry as soon as you can and attain new happiness.
I have never told you this until now but
when you were in junior high school, I went into your room
and I found a fetish adult magazine.
I felt gloomy after the discovery.
Please don't do weird things to your girlfriend.
What kind of..
Um, what are you saying?
What are you talking about, mother.
Don't do weird things.
That wasn't something new to hear.
- No.
OK now we'll be going.
Now we are going to our vacation.
Oh, thank you very much.
Bye bi
They didn't laugh
Well your mother was amazing, she has guts.
Yes that's true.
She is like the bravest one.
Yes yes.
I'm sorry everyone.
Sorry about that
Not at all, it's been awhile.
Next Passenger Is Checking In
Excuse me
May I have your name?
Kuu?
It's KOO.
Koo.
Koo-san.
What is he wearing?
I'm looking for an ATM...
Well..
Walk straight then at the far end
turn right.
Right?
There will be two machines.
Thank you.
Here it comes.
Next Passenger Is Checking In
32-D means..
it's an isle seat, doesn't it?
Pizza Cap
Nishio Kazuo (Tomochika)
When I called, I said I wanted a front window seat.
Then when I came here and received my ticket from the machine,
it said 32-D.  So I was like "What the hell is going on!"
I asked the staff, and they kept telling me to check with the other sections.
I was given the runaround, so I asked them if this was the City hall!
Claim On Passenger Service
It's a complainer.
Yeah, it seems so.
I have relatives in Kyushu, and I run a pizza shop here.
There will be a lot of people there, so I told them I would bring an L-sized pizza.
So I asked if I could carry it on the plane,
and they said they were afraid of the smell.
They said it will be too smelly to bring it in the plane.
And that it will be disgusting because it is all seafood!
It's not disgusting.
It's OK.
You can just get hot pizza in Kyuushu.
Awful customer
Thinking about everyone,
I told them to just deliver it on the plane then.
I won't carry in on with me!
Everyone will get sick because of the seafood, saying it's disgusting.
I feel sick!
Gross!
Bunch of idiots!
Feel sick?
It hurts!
Keep it nice, OK?
Yes.
Do it right, idiots!
He's a claimer.
The Zombies Reappear
Zombie Itao Appears
This must have taken time.
It's Itao-san, right.
Serious?
Ouch!  It's getting tougher.
So what's the meaning of this?
If you get bitten by a Zombie,
you become one too.
Then he got bitten!
It's so scary.
Don't you think you should call the police?
9:00 pm.
Without any break, they head to their next assignment.
Exercise Control Over Dangerous Articles
Security Check Duty
They are going to the security check point
where carry-on bags are checked.
Your names are written.  Hamada is front.
Security Check
Since you guys can't, the security officers will check the baggage.
Can you sit here and watch?
I think us watching won't accomplish anything.
Hickson Gracie
(Yamaguchi Tomomitsu)
I'm going to check my baggage-son
Hickson
I'm passing the gate-son
Why?  Why Hickson?
Hickson
This is Hickson
Long time no see-son.
Can I check your baggage?
Hickson VS Guitar
Why Hickson?
It's dangerous.
Yes.
It's your own guitar, right?
Hickson VS Guitar Continues
Hickson retired..
Dangerous person.
That was very high.
No good.
He shouldn't do it.
Yeah he shouldn't.
What is he doing?
It's a regular guitar.
Hickson Gracie Hickson Gracie
Anytime Anywhere Hickson Gracie
My name is Hickson Gracie
He's so cheerful.
He's having fun.
Hurry up and board the plane.
He was playing quietly during this time.
He was waiting.
Hickson Gracie
Anytime, it's Hickson Gracie
Happy and fun Hickson Gracie
Isn't he making a mistake of the meaning of Hickson?
What the hell.
A White Wig From His Baggage
Even if you say so..
Mimicking
Kuwana Masahiro
I have never sang anywhere like here.
Stop it.
I don't mind
to go on singing, carrying my guitar.
It's embarrassing to sing in a place like this.
"Light of the moon"
Security Check Becomes A Live Concert!
He tried too hard.
* They have already laughed, but please keep watching.
~　♪
That's too much!
Nothing like him!
Over exaggeration.
It hurts.
Hickson
Some people are strange.
Security Check
Looks bad, huh.
Foreigner Trying To Pass Unchecked
Security Officer
Egashira 2:50
Officer Pissed At Passenger's Attitude
Punished Him With A Slap
* They have already laughed, but please keep watching.
Why.. does he act so crazy.
Watch out.
Officer's Madness Is Getting Out Of Control
What a mess.
I think he will be reprimanded.
He should be OUT.
What a mess.
Some people are really crazy.
Really yes.
It was an officer, right?
Japanese officers are still reliable, huh.
What made you think so?
11:00 pm, it's been 14 hours since the start of the duty.
Going up?
Attending The Debriefing
The 5 members are attending a meeting
to discuss how to create a better airport.
However, there..
2F Meeting Room
Come on in.
Here they are.
Can you sit down there?
Please learn from them.
Now we are going to start
the airport black list debriefing meeting.
Yes.
We are going to list problematic celebrities and put them on a black list.
Blacklist Meeting
To avoid future problems, create a black list of problematic Passengers (celebrities)
So please report if you have anyone in mind.
OK.
Does anyone know of a suspicious celebrity?
Please make a report.
I have one.
OK.
Well...
In this world, there are a lot of scary things.
Right?  As it says "Earthquake, Thunder, Fire and Father."
Yes.
What scares comedians the most is,
if after your gag, there is total silence.
Yes.
The other day, the broadcast writer Takasu's wedding reception was held.
Katsumata-san was there at the reception sitting in his seat,
Yamasaki-san came and sat next to him.
Yamasaki Housei-san.
Yamasaki's Secret
#1 At Wedding Reception
Then he..
when everyone else was wearing formal suits,
it was about this size,
he was wearing a costume of "Eyeball Old Man".
Eyeball Old Man
In full costume?
Yes.
He was asked to give a speech in front of everyone.
But it was supposed to be planned for the latter half of the reception.
So from the beginning, the costume was lame.
Actually, not even one person reacted.
It's so lame.  He failed.
Then the reception started, and we were served our meal.
It seemed like the big eyeball costume was bothering him.
He took it off and..
started having his meal.
Once he took it off,
from the neck down,
he was wearing a gray shirt and gray long underwear.
So his attire looked so rude.
Unbelievable huh.
I was there
I was there, too.
Really?
Then he completely slipped up his speech.
Yamasaki's Secret
#2 At Wedding Reception
We stayed in the waiting room before the 2nd part of the reception started,
Yamasaki's Secret
#2 At Wedding Reception
there were Cocorico-san, Kimura-san, Matsumoto-san and Yamasaki-san.
In the small room, we were drinking some water.
Was it so bad?  Was it so bad?
He kept asking over and over.
Of course it was.
Cocorico-san said so too.
Yeah, even though they were juniors.
Then Matsumoto-san said some kind words to him, saying
If asked who they wanted to become in their future, you or me,
some people would say "Yamasaki".
Then Yamasaki asked,
What about you, Endo?
I want to be Matsumoto-san.
What about you, Tanaka?
Don't make is sound like that, stupid.
It's the reality.
It can't be helped.
That's only natural.
It's the reality.
Yamasaki-san,
before he gave a speech,
Yamasaki's Secret
#3 At Wedding Reception
Everyone got excited when musicians like Tortoise-san, Suga-san or Okuda-san sang.
Tortoise
Matsumoto
Sugashi Kao
Okuda Tamio
Then the celebrities and comedians at the tables
started talking and it made everyone laugh.
We were having a French dinner course,
but he ordered hot sake from the waiter.
We have a report from someone who couldn't make it today as well.
It's from Iwahashi, Plus Minus.
Provided by
Iwahashi Yoshimasa
(Plus Minus)
I'm reporting about a person called Hamada.
At his son's birthday, he bought
Hamada's Secret
At Son's Birthday...
Red Wing boots as a gift.
But the size was totally wrong and now he himself wears them.
What is it?
He's so stupid.
So stupid.
Can it happen?
When buying shoes, the size is most important.
Someone called Matsumoto-san..
This is reported from his wife's friend.
Provided by
Matusmoto's Wife's Friend
I heard..
his wife and daughter are
learning English at home lately.
His daughter keeps saying
Matsumoto's Secret
Wife & Daughter learn English...
Giraffe!  Giraffe!
So Matsumoto asked what's Giraffe,
because he didn't know what it was.
It's Kirin (in Japanese).  His wife told him.
Kirin (Giraffe)
Is Kirin called Giraffe in English?
I don't get it at all.  What is it?
What is it?
I don't get it at all.
He kept repeating it over and over.
What kind of report is that?
What kind of..
So he didn't get it at all.
It's called giraffe.  It can't be helped.
It doesn't matter if you get it or not.  Giraffe is Kirin.
He has to accept it.
Speaking of his child,
I heard this from Ameagari's Miyasako, but..
Matsumoto's Secret
Daughter's Story...
The genius comedian, Matsumoto Hitoshi
never tells a story without having a twist ending.
He surely does so on TV shows and
also during his private time.
One day, he was talking about his child,
When I run after her, screaming "Wahh!"
she screams and runs away.
And when I was reading a book for awhile, she started watching me...
So I  say "Wahh!" then she again screams and runs away.
It continues forever.
Then in the end he said,
I'm no match for her.
Can it be?
No twist ending.  Nothing funny.
It can happen, huh?
It seems so.
Anything else?
Well...
Let me talk about Hamada-san from Downtown.
I heard this from his family, so this is from a reliable source.
Provided by
Hamada's family
I heard, every New years, the Hamada family
Hamada's Secret
On New Yeah's Family Trip...
along with the High-heel Momoko-san family
goes on a trip.
High Heel Momoko
One year, they went to Australia.
Australia is famous for koala bears.
So Hamada-san was happy to hold a koala bear.
His wife and sons were next to him.
When they were about to shoot a commemorative photo,
travelers from Japan found him.
And it became a big crowd.
And they started taking pictures using their cellphones or digital cameras.  Pictures of his family.
Then of course Hamada-san
tried to protect his family,
and screamed to the crowd.  Then in that exact moment their commemorative photo was shot.
When the guide gave them the photo,
and they saw how it came out,
of course his wife and sons were embarrassed
and looking down.
But Hamada-san
was so mad at the moment,
but he was fully smiling to the camera.
But the koala bear he was holding thought that he was an enemy,
and was biting his arm.
That's how the photo came out.
That koala bear?
Yes.
Enough about Hamada.
Add him to the list.
Speaking of family,
sorry for continuing family talk but
Well..
Endo-kun got married and divorced.
Endo's Secret
Main Factor Of Divorce...
And
according to Katsumata, he asked Chiaki
Provided by
Chiaki
what's the main factor of their divorce.
It's basically because of their relationship,
but one of the main factors is
that Endo-kun
can't recite the alphabets.
Can it be?
So I asked him to say it.  He was good in the beginning.
A B C D.. then
When he hit around L M,
L M M
From O P Q, it got strange.
And he quickly came to Z.
We can't let him fly in our plane.
It's surprising.
Excuse me, so Endo-san.
This is a story that I still don't know the answer.
Endo's Secret
Story With No Answer...
In the middle of the night, around 2am.
I got an text message and it said,
I feel a bit horny
so why don't you come over?
It was sent to me by mistake.
You're lame.
It's crazy.
What are you doing?
Horny..
We don't know the truth.
No.
What kind of relationship is it?
That's crazy.
It's about Endo-san.
In his cell phone,
Endo's Secret
Cell phone...
he keeps a lot of weird adult movies.
Why do we have to hit for something like this!
Delete it!
Hey you.
If you didn't have adult movies in your cell phone..
We didn't have to get hit.
He is a super masochist.
That's mean.
He is a self-claimed super masochist that everyone admits.
Oh is he?
He often goes to the Sugamo area.
Endo's Secret
At Adult Shop In Sugamo...
He usually calls the woman's name with the honorific -san.
During their play, they used
some kind of toy.
And when the battery ran down, he thought it was still part of the play
and felt pleasure that she made him change the battery.
What the hell is that?
It's killing me!
This is killer!
It's hard.
Everything was awful.
He should be ranked S in the black list.
He's ranked an S.
I have a story about Yamasaki-san.
Well.. some years ago
he got a disease that only one out of millions will get, called Peyronie's disease.
Once you get it, your penis gets harder.
Yamasaki's Secret
Peyronie's disease...
When I went out for dinner with him,
he was quite drunk and
he started saying that he didn't need his penis any more
since he already had a kid.
He said he would cut it off and become like ***-san
So I told him that he wouldn't be able to become like ***-san even if he cut it off.
Then he said he would get something like spiritual power if he cut it off.
His words were pretty disrespectful to ***-san.
That's not how it is.
It hurts..
This is enough!
I have a story about Matsumoto Hitoshi.
At the dinner party,
Mimata Matazo asked Matsumoto for serious advice about a business.
Matsumoto's Secret
During The Party...
Mimata was running a shop in Roppongi for about 2 years, and closed it.
He told Matsumoto that he wanted to run a shop in Roppongi again if he had money.
Then..
Matsumoto Hitoshi said
he should try and do something different from Bar Matazo.
Then Mimata asked Matsumoto what would be good.
Then Matsumoto told him to run a sex delivery shop.
If you open a sex delivery shop, I'll pay for everything.
This is not good.
Mimata didn't know how to reject the offer.
At the time, Ameagari's Miyasako was there too.
Matsumoto's Secret
During The Party...
And he was listening to their talk.
They were actually talking about that.
In the end, looking at the sky, Matsumoto said
Let me decide the play menu.
Hey!
That's enough!
Scary.
A lot of people have been reported.
Can I report mine?
Well..
Mimata Matazo..
Yeah, Matazo.
Mimata's Secret
With Beautiful Junior Comedian...
Well, I heard that he had some trouble with *** from ***.
I heard they were quite drunk.
Let me explain what happened.
Mimata Matazo is a quite dangerous man.
He used to own a bar in Roppongi.
And when I, my girlfriend, and two junior comedians, four of us went there,
Yes.
He was there by himself.  Mimata Matazo-san.
He welcomed us.
And invited us to drink together.
So we were about to drink.
Then...
The beautiful ***M arrived.
Compared to Takahashi, she was still a newbie.
Mimata Matazo's Secret
With Beautiful Junior Comedian...
"Are you drinking?"
"Let me join!"
She was so friendly since she was drunk.
Under normal circumstances,
I think Mimata, the master of the bar, should have scolded her.
Because Takahashi is her senior and she should show him respect.
Yeah.
"Never mind that, ***."
"Just sit next to me, and be quiet."
That's strange.
"Let's go to *** like the last time."
Are you serious?
Hey!
Mimata Matazo's Secret
With Beautiful Newbie Comedian...
I didn't want to be bothered, so I said " I'm leaving." Then when I was going to pay for the bill,
I only had a glass.
"Oh, Takahashi. Please come again."
"Your bill comes to 18,000 yen."
He was trying to show off to ***.
In fact, this story still continues.
That's dangerous.
Mimata Matazo's Secret
With Beautiful Newbie Comedian...
I got a call from ***, and she said
on that night that she got drunk,
Mimata said that he would take her home.
She said he didn't have to do it, but
he said nothing was going to happen
between us because we are comedians. So, he took her home.
From that point on, she doesn't remember anything, but
when she got up in the morning,
her skirt was removed.
It's not a laughing matter!
Mimata Matazo's Secret
With Beautiful Newbie Comedian...
It was just off,
he said he didn't do anything, he just took it off because she looked sick.
Even though he says nothing happened,
since that day, he calls her "***."
Help me!
Something like that could get him arrested right?
No wonder the shop closed.
There are no rules here?
What is this?
Continue please!
Please go ahead.
Something easy.
I heard this from Kojima, UN-JASH.
Provided by
Kojima Kazuya
(UN-JASH)
About his partner, Watabe.
Watabe Ken's Secret
At Drink Party...
This is something easy, lately every time he drinks,
he complains.
His complaint is,
that *** salary is so low.
That's easy. We need more of these.
He won't be on the black list.
Did you learn a lot?  We're going now.
Did we learn...?  We heard terrible stories.
It was something.
Yeah, it was.
Now I remember I heard it (Mimata's story) before.
It was too lame to remember.
Meeting is finished.
Looks like more have been bitten.
Zombie Itao
Zombie Chad
One Zombie After Another
Looks like more zombies.
What the hell are they doing?
My dad has been bitten too!
Zombie Dad Appears
What is he doing?
My dad became a Zombie.
Chad also?
My dad got bitten.
Your dad is a good actor.
What should I feel as his son...
It's been 15 hours since the start.
It's a new day.
These men have been through hard duties.
No words,
they are just staring into space.
All we can see on their faces is tiredness.
You often do that, huh.  Quit it really.
Nobody gains.
Alright?
Next, the First Year Anniversary ceremony for this airport will be held.
All employees are required to attend. Let's go.
Congratulations On Opening Of The Airport
Attend The First Year Anniversary Ceremony
1 year?
1 year anniversary?
It's being held.
Everyone Is Already Seated
It's really being held.
Everyone, sit in order.
From now on,
the first year anniversary confere...
ceremony for this airport is going to be held.
How can he make a mistake?
Easy lines.
Yeah.
1 Year Anniversary Ceremony Of The Opening Of The Airport
First of all, the big-shot politician.
The former Prime Minister, Kan Naoto came to address everyone.
Kan Naoto (Teru)
The Former Prime Minister
Too realistic.
Awesome.
He looks too realistic.
He looks exactly like him.
I'm Kan Naoto.
I was the Prime Minister until recently.
Now, I am just an old man that likes to go on a pilgrimage.
Haha.
Now that saving power is really important,
Battery
so I carry something like this with me.
This is a real Kan Denchi (=Battery).  Who am I kidding?
Sudden Gunfire
Freeze!
Terrorists Are Surrounding The Area
What?
Hey! You guys.
You guys, be quiet. Hey!
This airport is being taken over!
Don't make any sudden movements!
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
Our demand is,
to release our comrades in 1 hour!
Do you understand?
Terrorist
Nakagawa-ke Reiji
We still have time.
Shall we have you guys do something to kill time?
Hey there, you and you.
Come up here!
Hurry up!
Airport Employee
Nakagawa-ke Tsuyoshi
Instructor
Shin Oni
Hey!
You, do something!
I'll do dog.
Do it.
Dog Imitation
That's it. Get out.
You.
I'll have you do something too!
Yes.
I'll say the greeting of a Cabin Attendant.
Huh?
CA's Greeting
"Welcome a bonboard, Ladies Gentleman."
Ladie La...Ladies and Gentleman,
thank you very much for coming.
Hey!
Do it as Hamasaki Ayumi.
Hamasaki Ayumi Imitation
Fli...
This
This Fli
go
goes to
Hawaii
and Honolulu.
Never mind about that one.
Next, Shibata Kyohei.
Shibata Kyohei Imitation
Hey
I wish
I could be
just a little bit
more kind.
What the...
What is that?
No idea.
That's crazy.
Hey, next is QUEEN.
Queen?
I am
the wife of a King, a Queen.
He should know that's wrong.
Oh ouch!
I've had enough of you!
Now, I'm going to kill you.
Please wait!
Who are you?
Hori Chiemi
I think it was very funny.
Thanks to you,
I could become a successful CA.
Thank you
Ko..
Instructor
The same to you!
It's because you tried hard!
When can he talk normally?
This is supposed to be a serious moment.
Instructor, I'll keep trying.
Good luck.
What the hell are you guys talking about?
I'm going to kill you!
Watch out!
Chiemi
Why did this happen?
Are you OK?
Chiemi!
Why did this happen?
How many are there?
Chiemi.  Are you OK, Chiemi?
CA Died In Place of Instructor
Chiemi, are you OK?
Why did this happen?
Suddenly The Terrorist Gets Shot
Huh?
Here!?
That's SAT.
SAT Appears
We're safe now.
Good.
GOD
DAMN!
Chono Masahiro Barges In
Here he comes
What's going on?
This is terrible!
Captain Chono Finds Something
What?
No wonder you made that face.
- Yeah.
This is a dying message.
Transport her.
Be careful!
Yes sir.
The person who leaked information to the terrorists is
YA
MA
ZA
It's a message that the CA left right before she died,
even though it is not completed.
A terrorist sympathizer's name is written.
Hey!
Is there anyone here named YAMAZA?
Be honest and get up here!
I see.
Are you trying to hide?
It's gotta be one of you.
You can't hide.  It's written on your face.
It's Yamaza!
Does anyone have any idea?
I'll ask one by one.
Searching For The Person With The Name, "Yamaza"
OK?
What's your name?
Tajima Isamu.
Wrong.
What's your name?
Matsunaga Takuya.
Wrong.
What's your name?
Kamata Chiharu.
Wrong.
What's your name?
Fujiwara Hiroshi.
Wrong.
What's your name?
Tanaka Naoki.
Aren't you lying?
No.
What's your name?
Endo Shozo.
Wrong.
What's your name?
Hamada Masatoshi.
Wrong.
What's your name?
Matsumoto Hitoshi.
Wrong.
What's your name?
I'm asking for your name damn you!
Imasaki Hosei.
The worst.
You're the worst.
You probably shouldn't lie.
I can't stand it.
Just say it.
That's interesting.
Can you tell me your name again?
Imasaki.
I'm Imasaki Jose.
Your given name doesn't matter!
Give me a break!
What's the hell is "Jose"
Come on, please.
It can't be helped.
Say your name properly to your friends.
Stand up, face them and say it properly.
Say your name properly.
Say it. What's your name?
Imasaki Jose.
A long way to go!
You guys know him, don't you?
His name is Yamazaki Housei.
Are you Yamazaki?
But it's actually Yamasaki.
You're suspicious.  Come here.
Sanction Slap for the Terrorist's Sympathizer
Don't you feel anything?
This happened because you gave information to terrorists!
I didn't do it.
I couldn't stand the silence.
There is no way to get away. Come closer.
Wait
wait
So why was your name written?
I have no idea, really.
Confess!
Confess what?
Try rolling this on your neck.
You'll understand the feeling.
Understood?
Understand the feeling of what?
Stand up!
Understand what...
This time he is getting a neck punishment.
Stand up!
Understood?
I'll give you a chance!
Give me a chance!
No, I lied.
Wait huh!
Nooo!
Noooo!
Give me a chance, please.
Do something then.
Something that you like.
What I like?
Something you are good at.
A loud voice!
Do it then.
What is that.
What's with this guy.
What.
Come on, this again!
What did you say first?
Your name? Say it again!
What's your name?
Well.. how.. nothing can save me now right?
Nothing can save me now right?
Chono-san, do you want to
SLAP?
You want to                    , right?
SLAP
Maybe you shouldn't call him "Chono-san" now?
You want to                    , right?                           .
SLAP
It doesn't have to be me?
That's all I want to know.
Cant it be him?
Him
HIM
HIM!
Hey! Endo
YOU!
What you!  Why are you trying to get away!
Tanaka please take my place.
I'll do whatever you ask from now on.
Tell me who can take your place!
Ask them then.
Please.
I'm sorry but I can't.
I can't.
Tanaka take him back.
It can't be helped.
Please wait.  Yes I will.
Hurry up and make your last appeal!
Tanaka.
I really hate this.
If you can take my place,
I will definitely be your good friend!
Come on.
Done?
Yama-chan, please.
Come here.  Hurry up.
The hits are getting stronger.
No need for formalities.
We already know each other.
What's the matter?
Do you want to get closer to me?
You were laughing.
Hey stand up!
I'm falling, falling.
That's enough.  That's enough.
Every year,
Step
Please don't step on my foot!
Ouch!
Hurry and stand up!
OK, stand up.
Here we go!
Stand up, stay still!
Be strong.
Let me hear your name again, OK?
Then say "I'm sorry."
What is it! Say it properly.
Yama...
Yamazaki
Housei!
God Damn.
Hey let's go!
It was a mess.
Let's go.
I'm done.
Shall we go?
1:00 am, after completing their duties at the airport, they are heading back to the school.
Return To The Training School
So cold.
Then after this, something unsuspected happens.
My butt hurts.
Are we entering?
Inside?
Zombies!
A Hoard of Zombies Attacks
Let's get out!
Everyone, let's get out!
I have a fracture!
I said I have a fracture!
Close the door!
Zombie Itao
Wow, it scares me!
Zombie Dad
It's your dad.
What are you doing there?
All of a sudden a crowd of Zombies attacked the members.
They could get out of the airport safely. However...
It was dangerous.
I said I have a fracture!
Yes, you did.
They made him run.
They made him run pretty hard.
Bus Driver Is Also Zombie
We didn't know about this.
- Yeah.
2:00 am,
they arrive at the training school.
The five members were just released from their hard duties in the airport.
However, more trials are waiting for them.
It's an emergency!
One of our instructors has been kidnapped by a group of hoodlums.
They should still be around here.
Yamazaki and Endo, can you go find them?
What is it?
Where?
I forgot to tell you.
From now on, it's not "No-laughing" but "No-getting scared"
Middle of the night special rule
No Getting Scared Airport.
So what's with you guys, Slightly Sweet.
You know what, we are great. We've been increasing popularity.
Well, I can see you trying hard.
Doing great when some people prefer black or cafe au latte.
Even though we belong to different groups, our goal is the same.
Here you go.
Not that. This is mine.
What? You don't make sense. Do you understand which group you are in?
Of course I do.  I notice it every time I see my outfit.
That's not good.
Some vending machines don't have mine.
It really surprised me.
Of course it's sold out.
Anyway...
Cheers!
This is good.
I am really into slightly sweet.
I really like Ememan.
Let's go then.
Shall we go then?
Yes.
Don't miss the opening of 2012!!
Middle of the night special rule,
No Getting Scared Airport.
Firstly, Yamazaki and Endo are
heading to the changing room on the 2nd floor,
where the kidnapped instructor was seen for the last time.
Isn't it No Laughing?
We're leaving.
Supposedly he was seen in the changing room on the 2nd floor.
It's the pattern of 2 pairs...
Lighting Changed
Wait a second, this is...
Let's go slowly.
CO2 Gas
In           Seconds
We have to follow the arrow, right?
From here, Getting Scared Word Link Game starts...?
Getting Scared Word Link Game Starts
Ringo (apple)
It's No Getting Scared Word Link Game!
What?
Rin"Go"
Ringo.
Gorira
Rin"Go"
Gorii"Ra"
Secret Trap Starts
In              Seconds
Rin"Go"
Gori"Ra"
Rap "Pa"
Pa pa pa...
Panaki!
Savanna Yagi 's "Panaki"
What is it!
Panaki!
Getting Scared Word Link Game Ends
At the same time in the training room...
Shall I give you a ride?
Oops. Dangerous.
When was it?
They were doing this?
You must've had no idea what to do.
I really didn't know.
What are you doing?
For argument's sake, I am OK.
But I feel sorry for Tanaka.
Tanaka has no idea what to do.
Nakata Kausu・Botan
If Kausu・Botan-san started doing this, I wouldn't know what to do.
Meanwhile, Yamazaki and Endo...
Mysterious Masked Group
were attacked by a mysterious masked group.
2F Storage Room
I'm scared!
Ouch!  Ouch!  Ouch!
Handcuffed And Confined In The Storage Room
What the hell?
What's going on?
Getting Scared Theater Opens
Getting Scared Theater!
Getting Scared Theater...
Hissatsu Shigotonin
Did you watch this?
-Yes.
Hissatsu Shigotonin
The 2 guest will be at risk!
I'm scared!  I'm scared!
Secret Trap Starts
In             Seconds
Weird atmosphere
-Super scary.
Hi, this is Kyomoto Masaki, Hissatsu Shigotonin.
Kyomoto Masaki's Incomplete Imitation (Razah Ramon RG)
Let me sing the Historical Play Aruaru in the melody of Nonstop Romantic by C-C-B.
Historical Play Aruaru
Nonstop Romantic (C-C-B)
Things that happen in historical plays
I want to tell you things that happen in historical plays
I want to tell you
High heel, high heel, high heel, high heel
Historical play, many things, I want to say it
Hurry up and finish it
Just finish it already
I want to say it I want to say it, it becomes painful it becomes painful
Historical play, I have a lot to say, as soon as possible
Historical play, a lot, the end roll is
Prank in
All vertical writing
CO2 Gas Shoots Out
What is that?
Eventually it ended like this.
Hey!
What are you doing, hey!
Bomb
We really can't get out of this thing you know!
Stop!
Stop it!  What is this?!
The RG Lights The Fuse
I'm scared!
Hey, what's gonna happen!?
Explosion in
Flowers From The Bomb
I feel so drained
Huh?
Their Mouths Are Gagged
This is bad!
Yamazaki and Endo got kidnap... I mean got attacked.
By the Oyaji hunter gang.
It looks like they will be in the 2nd floor locker room or in the warehouse.
Matsumoto will remain here...
because he has an injury.
So Hamada and Tanaka can you go?
Leaving Matsumoto behind,
Hamada and Tanaka will search for the missing duo.
I'm counting on you because I'm really scared.
I know, I got it.
I hate this.
They're going to get me hurt
Matsumoto Is Happy About His Partner's Misfortune
Wow, it's so dark.
For me, this was hard too.
Having to wait?
-Yeah.
Like desk work.
This is scary
Hey
It's so dark!
No, it's you Hamada-san
3rd FL -> 2nd FL
It stinks!  It really stinks!
You guys are disgusting
just how old are you?
What is this smell?
A Foul Odor Is Being Sprayed
It stinks!
Ranking Game Noise in
Stinks!
Did it stink?
-Yeah.
What is that?
AH!
You guys are panicking
What's wrong with you?
What is it?
What is it?  What is it?
The Game Result Is Failure
Tanaka!
What are you doing, seriously!
I had no clue what would happen
Prank in
You exaggerate too much
Are you for real?
Hama-chan, sorry about this morning
Umezu Kazuo & Umezawa Tomio
They were still here
Yamazaki & Endo Confined
Hamada & Tanaka Passes By
They Passed The Room Without Noticing
Why do I have to be in front?
That hurts!
Shohei's Glasses in
Scary!  Scary!
I said
to
stop falling down!
This is
Shofukutei Shohei
These are Shohei's glasses
It's going to be like this!  Definitely!
The Public Phone Starts Ringing
Wow, it says to answer the phone!
Hello?
Hello,
I have a question for you.
What do you call the person who comes in last during a race?
Biri!
How do you say it twice?
Biri Biri!
Biri
What the..?
Shocking Phone
What is this!
Are you alright?
What the hell is this!
Stop pushing me!
They were always there!
They Arrive At The Locker Room
It's so creepy
After The Door Appears Another Door
There's another door!
What is this? Easy life.
Wandering Around In The Room
It's fine, don't worry.  There's nothing there.
Shocking Door in
That's true, it should be fine.
It's not like when you open it, someone will pop out.
Interested in "How The World Walks"
Wow, they even filmed all of this
Shocking Door in
Can you see inside?
What are you doing?
Electronic Hand Gripper
Shocking Door in
I'm going.
Take a look inside.
Biri
BIRI
Shocking Hand Gripper
At the same time!
Something feels weird
Locker room
Seriously, what is this?
Yeah.
Moving Doll in
This way?
Don't fall down, it's scary
Examining The Area
What? What was that?
Toy Tank Fires in
A stray bullet?
Matsumoto Receives The Same
Yeah
Why is this here?
Tsuyoshi Takashiro
Portrait
Maybe this way.
What are these things?
Tsuyoshi Takashiro in
Kannazuki Doesn't Look Like Takashiro At All
Thank you for your hard work!
Erika you're late!
Erika!
Who is Erika?
Erika you're late.
You scared me.
Hey Erika don't go!
ERIKA!  I SAID DON'T GO!
Where are you going Erika.
Erika!
Erika you can't go!
Someone!
Help us!
E.. E...
Endo and
Zaki-san's voice!
Prank in
Chidegika On A Segway
Oh, it's here!
Store Room
Take it off?
Is it Ok?
They Have Been Saved
We got captured by some weird guys dressed in black.
I guess you saved them.  Someone reported that an Instructor has been captured
It seems like he is in the ground level warehouse.
Get over there right away.
At the ground level warehouse?
An instructor?
Instructor in the ground level warehouse.
Huh?
What are you surprised at?
Someone is there, there's someone there!
It's the old lady.
The Hip Shaking Granny Is Calling Them
No, we have to help someone now.
Huh, what, what is it?
No way!
Farting Cushion in
How old fashioned
Tanaka, you exaggerate too much.
You...
Surprise Comedy Routine
What does this mean?
The Healthy Boys
The Surprise Comedy Routine Starts
We are the Healthy Boys!
The Healthy Boys
Nakayama Kinnikun            Savanna Yagi
Healthy!
This guy looks like he is training hard everyday, but he knows nothing about muscles.
No, these are real muscles, but you have no knowledge about muscles.
How about a quiz about muscles to see who knows the most?
Ok, let's do it!
What is known as the king of exercises
that is great for the lower body?
Squat!
Correct!
So then, what is good for training
the back muscles...
Lat pull down!
Correct!
What type of pants do bodybuilders like
that has a lot of room down below?
Baggy Pants!
Correct!
The opposite of...
Tights!
Correct!
What is the sports gym, 3 mins away from Namba Grand Kagetsu?
Dipness Namba!
Correct!
Who, when Dipness Namba first opened
forgot their ID at the front desk and caused a scene?
Hanshin Shisho!
Correct!
Who is a famous personal trainer at Dipness Namba?
Hirao-san!
Correct!
What do the customers think of Hirao-san?
He's the best!
Correct!
What good thing happened to Hirao-san recently?
He had an international marriage!
Correct!
Special Effects in
Hirao-san congratulations on your marriage!
Healthy!
Congratulation Confetti
Yagi didn't screw up this time.
Shampoo Hat Koizumi
What is this?
Tonight, I would like everyone to listen about how I love my wife.
How I Love My Wife
Shampoo Hat Koizumi
While my wife is sleeping
I lick her lips.
Also the arm pits... I lick.
What the hell is he saying?
I also lick inside her belly button.
Also the hip bone... I lick.
Her crotch... I lick.
The left butt cheek, I lick.
Only the left side
Left, left left.
Left, left, left, left, left.
Left, left, left.
What is she doing?
Left, left, left, left.
The left side... I lick.
Prank in
Matsumoto Feels It Too
Hey stop it!
He Got Assassinated
We are supposed to be CA right?
S..s..cary
Bombs, Dinosaur, and Missiles, 3 pranks at once.
What will happen?
Hallway
Was that a singer?
I don't know who that was.
That weirdo.  Everything was "Left" song.
HOT!
It's dangerous!
What? Huh?
Dinosaur Gomora
That's scary
It's huge!
Missiles
This is crazy!
It's so huge. That dinosaur.
Field
Ah I think that's it, the shelter.
They say that we need to go through this thing right?
It looks slippery.
I'm so scared.
It's so scary this time.
The instructor, got attacked by the Oyaji hunter gang.
And the gang is still there.
The Oyaji hunter gang has nothing to do with this.
Field Storage Room
What do we have to do?
I'm opening it
Open the door, open it.
Heipo-san!
Ah, Heipo-san.
What are you doing?  It's just Heipo.
The Instructor captured by the Oyaji Hunter gang
Heipo
I'm cold!
Temperature
It's so cold!
It's too cold!
Cough
Lets take him on this thing.
Rescue With The Baby Stroller
Ouch!  Ouch!  Ouch!
They have successfully rescued the instructor.
They try to get out as soon as possible.
We have to hurry, before the gang comes.
Scary, scary, ouch ouch ouch!
Prank in
This is your hat right?
Oyaji Garigari-kun Gang
**Garigarikun won't do something like this
This is awesome
Wait!
It's over.
Trying to get back here was terrible.
The trip back was crazy.
Over here, I had to endure many small pranks that were pretty evil.
Like unsuspecting bombs.
It exploded.
Even you had pranks!
18 hours have passed
Whew, my butt is so hot!
All of you guys did a great job today.
You have now all graduated. Congratulations!
Yes!
Finally!
For love       Okuda Tamio
In the seat in front of us, there is a gross lady
A stag horn beetle pinches, and everyone laughs
Girls on bike pedaling, showing their panties
Koyabu face slapping Umemiya and Amemiya
Umezawa you got mad but
It was a really really stupid prank
In SM costume, not losing to their salary
It makes you become a good role model
Matsuko attacks the throat
Kurosawa and Watanabe shakes hips
Umezo takes off all of his clothes
Around here the cold Nishio
scolds Gushiken
For my wife, for my daughter, let's endure everything
Ah she got a good grab, like a young kid
World Shin-Oni World
Farts in front of scared Matsumoto
Butt hitting. 5th place Endo Shozo 224 times.
4th place Yamazaki Hosei 227 times.
3rd place Tanaka Naoki 231 times.
2nd place Hamada Masatoshi 288 times.
1st place Matsumoto Hitoshi
An old man dancing to "Look at my right elbow."
It is true that Rola is hard to understand
Tomochika holding a pizza and complaining
A creepy Itao wanders around
Oh Ueshima & Degawa used their bodies
Let's continue to show our butts even after 10 years
You should get bitten by a snake yay
Around here, Ameagari will
reveal big secrets
Copying Kuwana, copying Hickson it's Gu-san's show
Ah altogether
Endo of Endo
Stretching briefs and takes him away
This year again, Yamazaki
gets slapped by Goddamn Chono
For failure, for laughter, let's get surprised
Ah everyone is getting old
The world of only laughter, the world of Gaki
Run old men and cheer up
Wishing you all the best for the New Years.  By Zombie
2011's Eneman battle will have a prize for end battle.
Also in 2012 a big event!
Hi everyone!
Downtown has arrived!
Happy new years!
We will do our best this year too!
Well this year, let's see who's the strongest Ememan!
Hey can you get that please.
Ready set go, Happy End of the Year!
What is this?
We will start this year with a little sugar!
What did you say?!
This is our slightly sweetened winner!
I will fight with you of course!
Let's do this!
Do your best.
Yes! We will do it with this!  With this!
We're going to do our best!
We will do it this year again!
Have a happy 2012 everyone!
2012 which is it?
I said I had a fractured leg.
You stayed in the room the whole time but earned the most hits!
How about next year?
What do you mean? What are you talking about?
This year's episode has already finished.
You mean the end of this year?
This year...
I don't know anything about it!
You decided already?!  We just finished!
This year I want to create a hit song and enter Kohaku.
Please tell us more about that!
Yeah, but Chono-san may come to Kohaku.
God damn! God damn!  That would be pretty scary.
He would find me, really.
Thank you for everything!
Thank you everyone for watching until the end!  Please continue to support us!