An abyss of emotional suppression
TEAM Gaki presents:
Timing/Typesetting:
Hinnerk
Kazuma
Inugami
Sacro
AIDOL Keicchi
Kevin
Rich
Translation:
Michael
Half-San
Lei
Oolong
typesoshee
Final checker:
James
Team Leader:
Alex (Slayeer)
At such a time,
A roar of admiration will rise
a roar of admiration will rise
The best Gaki no Tsukai
No Laughing Great Prison Escape
Gaki no Tsukai best series!!
This year's No Laughing Batsu Game is
The Great Prison Escape!
You're kidding!
Assassins of Laughter on the Attack
Ultra Extravagant Lineup!
For this year's assassins of laughter
we have of course
an ultra extravagant lineup!!
You won't believe it, it's
KATOU~!!
You're joking, right?!
White
Hot
Game Battle!!
A special force of celebrities gather for the game battle!!
That man's crotch is...
This is the worst
The terror returns
We're bringing it back again this year
Onigokko
Tag War
Onigokko Tag War!
Fly under the oni's radar!
Howl and scream inducing, Onigokko Tag War!!
Whatever you do, just run away!
The terror returns!
WAHHH~!!
Peril
Danger
Scaled at MAXIMUM
The scale of the danger is at maximum!
You CAN'T do that!!
The Oni will
Prey on...
That big star's sudden participation
Big Star
As the oni's prey
That's the first time I saw that!!
Escape
Prison
Escaping out of the prison
Influential Figure
This is a disaster!!
Willpower of Men
The willpower of men whose bodies are put to the test
Ouch!!
Oi!!
HERE I GO!!
I DON'T WANT THIS!
NO WAY!!
Only Laughter! 6 Hour Special Challenge!!
This year again, 6 hours with no interruptions
Absolutely
New Year's Eve Special
No Laughing
Absolutely
Great Prison Escape
Absolutely No Laughing Great Prison Escape 24 Hours
24 Hours
Gaki
Downtown
New Year's Eve Special
no Tsukai ya Arahende!
Let's do this!
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Alright!
Thank you
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
This year, this day comes around again
We're really gonna do this, right?
Tsukitei Housei
Yeah!
Yes, yes we will
This is NTV's 9th consecutive
"Gaki no Tsukai"  welcoming of the new year
Before we know it, we will have crossed into the new year
That is right
Well
This year is a good turning point
so I think I’d like to end this series on this one
Turning point?
WHY DON'T YOU TRY?!
I dare you to try!!
You try and steer this ship!!
Nagabuchi-san
Notes: Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi is a Japanese rock singer with a distinct coarse voice.
Okay
Well then really...
How was watching it?
Watching?
We haven't seen anything yet
Talk as if you've seen it
As if I've seen it?
If we can film the ending
we can just go home!!
The poor audience... they came all the way here to watch!
That's okay. They can stay and watch.
Without further ado,
Let's start then
let's start
Matsumoto, your VTR cue
if you would, please
Hurray!
Go already
go
Notes: Matsumoto is imitating Nippon Electric Rengou, a Japanese female comedian duo who says, "Dame yo, dame dame"
What a rip off
No Laughing Great Prison Escape
It's started!
Morning glow
As the morning glow dyes the sky red
A gentle welcome
The forest trees give the guys a gentle welcome
Seriously, they should increase the number of people here
Oh, so not just 5 of us
Not just the 5 of us
They should make it around 60 people
I really think Hamada alone is good enough
What the hell
Oh, but
What the hell...
that's a good idea
No "buts"
What should we do?
No "buts", just no
You know, just by judging that reaction,
he's not that against it
That's true!
You're right
It does seem that way
There's no way
He'll say to his wife with a smile,
"I did it by myself"
It says "Wait here!!"
What's this?
I hate seeing that changing box
Wait here!!
It's cold
It's so cold in there!
It only just started getting cold from today
It always gets so cold for this occasion
I want to go home
You've been complaining the entire time
Matsumoto, you're pretty good
Well, you know, I did a complaining performance
It wasn't really much of a big deal though
You're complaining as part of your comedy?
Cheerleaders arrive
Hamada Matsumoto
What is this?
Endo Tanaka
He can't concentrate
Hamada Matsumoto
Looks like they're doing something
Endo Tanaka
Cheering for the stars of the show
They don't say my name, huh
Well, you know
Downtown! Cocorico!
They don't say my name at all
It's just going to end like this
It just ended with the "Woo hoo!"
I wonder if they care at all
Hey!
Fujiwara Hiroshi
Downtown's Former Manager
Just for you guys
the local cheerleaders came to support you
fart
You guys must...
must be feeling pumped up now
Please say something
He farted just now
That's right
Matsumoto
In what way are you pumped up?
Well, you know, it's definitely how
they said "Fight! Fight!" over and over, but
then lead to Hamada's fart...
The support from the cheerleaders,
due to Hamada's farp
due to Hamada's farp...
He can't speak at all
Your anxiety is ruining it
Farp...
How funny!!
It's funny, right?
How annoying
Matsumoto, isn't your boke super dope?
What the hell
This is getting ridiculous
Every year the quality deteriorates
Yes, you tell him
Enough about that
We're doing it again this year
This year's theme is a prison
A prison?
Prison staff?
Are we the jailers?
For the next 24 hours you guys will be
leading the life of a prisoner
What the hell
Why the hell
I thought we'd be the jailers
This ain't right
For 24 Hours they will live as prisoners
All 5 will be imprisoned
This time, all 5 will be imprisoned
And for 24 hours they will live as fictitious prisoners
Why does it have to be like this?  Be prisoners...
No, really?
I'm saying prison, but
what's with your outfits?
From now
He just keeps going
I'm going to have you guys go get changed
He won't listen to us
Just continues with the lines from his script
It's like what the AIBO says when you get home
Notes: AIBO stands for Artificial Intelligence Robot and was a series of iconic robotic pets.
There's no response
None at all
And he still doesn't say anything
It's all prepared for you
Please get changed
Before becoming a prisoner
they change into appropriate attire
My back hurts
That being the case
They change into prisoner appropriate attire
Are you guys ready?
Then I'll have Matsumoto come out first
Macho Man Prisoner
You're so muscular, you must be strong
I don't understand why we're being arrested
We shouldn't be able to carry our shackles
Even though I'm told to take this
You're like the Incredible Hulk
Knew he was going to say that
Don't just continue with your lines
Next, Hosei
Babyface Prisoner
You're so small
Really, you're
Note: Jizo bodhisattva are Buddhist deities that protects children. A rice grain bodhisattva is a rice grain that has their likeness drawn onto it as a souvenir or charm.
like a rice grain bodhisattva
Next, Endo
Divorced Handsome Prisoner
You're handsome, as always
Thank you
Anyway
Ryotaro Sugi  is who you look like
Notes: Ryotaro Sugi is a Japanese actor and singer, most famous for period dramas
Thank you!
You're not mad?
Next, Tanaka
Lanky Pointy Chin Prisoner
You're lanky, as always
Like Hattifatteners
Notes: Hattifatteners are skinny mushroom-like characters from a Finnish comic called Moomin. In the Japanese version of Moomin, they're called Nyoro Nyoro.
Hattifatteners
From Moomin
Next, Hamada
Wasn't very clear
Only Hamada is a Sexy Female Prisoner
That is no good
Give me a break
Could you please stop that?
Just reject them please!!
It's not that, I mean
It's always me!
As soon as I enter, I immediately see this wig
Could you resist them a bit?
Is that really a wig?
Why do you wear this?
This is a wig
My head didn't look like this before
You sure you didn't just quickly do your hair?
Quickly do your hair
Just like that
Quickly styling it
I don't think this is a wig
Just comb your hair like this,
it'd look like that
There's no way that's a wig
What kind of person is that?
No Laughing Rules
For 24 hours, live as new prisoners
The rules this time are simple
While imprisoned, absolutely no laughing
If you laugh, there is a severe punishment
During the 24 hours while living as prisoners,
no matter what happens, absolutely no laughing
If you laugh, a severe punishment is waiting for you
That is all
A bus bound for the prison is on its way
to get us and take us there!!
I don't get why we've been arrested
I agree
That's right
At the very least
Aren't these shackles heavy?
Really though
Oh, only mine is heavy
You're kidding, right?
Huh?
It is kinda heavy
Only Hosei's shackle weighs 10kg (about 22lb)
Are you serious?
I'm serious
It's true!!
This is just plain mean
It actually is heavy?
About 5 times heavier
Right right
Time to start
At last
it is time to start
Rising Tension
The tension rises naturally
Well now
This is so annoying
In this case, a police van is what we need
Why a bus?!
Here it is
The bus is here like no big deal
As if it's no big deal.
It must have not been a major crime, so can we just not do this whole thing?
There’s no need for chains, right?
Kurobikari Central...
Here it is.
Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison
This is the name of the prison you'll all be going to.
The bus is painted in yellow and black
to signify danger.
The destination is the central prison.
The No Laughing starts once you board the bus.
So once we board, it starts.
I gotta first get used to how Hamada looks.
That's true.
You can’t get used to that.
Okay, Hamada, please board first.
Please, thank you.  It’s gonna start.
It's cold out.
Close the doors.
He's laughing already.
He's already on board.
What?  I'm not on board yet.
You just laughed.
I'm not at the top!
This is the worst.
Hit him on the butt.
The Black Army Gang Smacks Your Butt
You can go stronger.
Practice, go practice.
Should we go then?
Here I go.
They should have seriously closed the doors and left us.
Okay.
Regular passengers are already on board
It’s warmer than necessary in here.
The bus finally departs for the central prison.
What lies in wait for them?
Laughing is not allowed.
Laughing is no longer allowed.
The mood in the bus is uneasy.
However,
the assassins of laughter will not go easy. Their assaults will be merciless!!
Please be careful about that.
The bus arrives at a stop
Isn’t this really fast?
That was fast.
Matsuko, are you going to be all right?
Tarento
Matsuko Deluxe
This is fast.
What's the matter?
This is definitely fast.
Director
Hakata Daikichi
This, you see,
is a new show by our company, Saitama Hatsuratsu TV
which has staked its future on this show.
In the middle of an on-location shoot for a new show
This is the first on-location shoot.
Whatever. Didn’t I do everything fine?
Another person will be coming, but I'll say this again.  Please do this right.
Another person?
Not that way.  This way, this bus!!
Composer
Niigaki Takashi*
*Note: In February 2014, Niigaki Takashi revealed himself to be the ghostwriter for Samuragochi Mamoru.  The latter had claimed to be a deaf and physically disabled composer.  The revelation by Niigaki that Samuragochi had faked the authenticity of his compositions and physical disabilities was a huge news story in Japan in 2014.
You're kidding.
Let’s not use the casting.
Let’s not make us laugh because of casting.
It's a phenomenon, so it can't be helped, but...
The casting...
As if this was some normal thing.
Mr. Niigaki,
Matsuko and Niigaki's Local Bus Journey.
This is a show where this year's most famous gay person and composer
take a journey using only the local bus.
A segment that resembles a popular TV show*
*Note: This is referring to a real TV show where two TV personalities (Tagawa Yosuke and Ebisu Yoshikazu) go on a local bus journey, "ローカル路線バス乗り継ぎの旅 (Local Bus Transit Journey)".
Isn’t this a rip-off of that one on TV Tokyo by Tagawa and Ebisu?
This is bad, right, Mr. Niigaki?
Yes.
I think it is bad to use someone else's work.
What is that, seriously?
What is that?
The setup is just too solid.
It's fine.  But this is TV
so we want to capture a certain amount of incidents.
He wants to capture incidents during the journey
How are we suppose to cause incidents?
I was thinking, perhaps, you two could create them.
Deliberately create an incident
We've prepared a number of things,
so could we just rehearse them?
Okay.
First off, how about this?
What is that?
It's an electric muscle stimulator.
Incident Item 1
Electric Muscle Stimulator
We’ll have you put this on your face and introduce the scene.
With this electric stimulation, our ratings will also rise electrically.
There's no way it’ll go that easily.
What do you think, sir?
I think it will go well.
Okay, Matsuko.
Mr. Niigaki will operate the electric muscle stimulator.
Voltage Meter
This time we have come to Tochigi Prefecture, where places like Nikko Tosho-gu, Mt. Nikko, and Rinno-ji are located.
One can enjoy the historic environment and be in the presence of numerous historic sites.
It’s too high.
It's set on 9.
That’s a bit strong.
Was that okay?
Voltage Meter
With sites like Kegon Waterfall, which has a height of 97 meters,
the region is full of tourist attractions.
It's on 9 again.
Sir, could you please lower it?
Can't we just get one smack for all of this?
Alright, already.
Can we be done with this part?  Was that fine?
That was a pretty nice incident.
Then, are we about done?
We still have more, though.
More?
More incidents are desired
Here we go.
What is that?
A giant balloon kit.
Incident Item 2
Giant Balloon Kit
We’ll put this inside your clothes and expand the balloon
while you read the tourism information from before.
Have Mr. Niigaki do it as well.
Instead of using the tarento, they go for something more novel
Not just me.
Can you, sir?
I'll do it.
We would be grateful if you could do this for us.
Put it on like this?
Put it inside the clothes.
Thank you.  Is that ok?
Okay, let’s rehearse it.
This time we have come to
Balloon Expanding
Tochigi Prefecture
where places like Nikko Tosho-gu, Mt. Nikko,
and Rinno-ji are located.
The sites within Mt. Nikko
are listed as
a UNESCO World Heritage Site
and one can enjoy
the historic environment
and be in the presence of numerous historic sites.
And currently
Sir, please raise your voice.
Is this really safe!?
It should be safe!!
It's supposed to get this big!?
It's crazy when you're right next to it.
Absolutely nothing.
He gave absolutely no reaction.
That was a novel sight.
He was so startled he didn’t even give a reaction.
Sir, that was good.
Sir, that was wonderful.
Really.
Assistant!  Bring that over.  Bring that in.
Going with the flow, another thing is added
What is that?
That's the Chinko Machine.
Incident Item 3
Chinko Machine
I just stand here?
You just need to stand there.
Is the cue card fine?
Yes, it's fine.
What exactly is the situation with Matsuko there?
It’s the first time to see Matsuko like that, right?
She looks so weird.
Pisses me off.
Just wear that from the beginning, then.
That hit Matsuko.
Chinko Machine
The machine fires at some point during the take
Okay, Matsuko.
She's sort of like Oba-Q, right?*
*Note: "Oba-Q" or "Obake No Q-taro" is a manga featuring a character that is a large, round ghost.
You're right, that's like Oba-Q.
It's sort of like Oba-Q.
This time we have come to
Tochigi Prefecture, where places like Nikko Tosho-gu, Mt. Nikko, and Rinno-ji are located.
The Yamaage Festival is a well-known tourist attraction
as well as local cuisine like shimotsukare, and surely you know about
No!!
She went “No!”
What is this?
That was great, Matsuko.
What was great about that?  Seriously?
I think the viewers will love it.
Now that it has come to this, sir,
you can't take a backseat to this, right?
We have one more thing.
Let's try this one.
Incident item 4
Hirata Stag Beetle
Incident Item 4
You use this stag beetle and clip it on your nose.
Sensei...
We’ll have your nose get pinched by the stag beetle.
Let's do this.
The place that we've arrived today is a secret location that is rarely known...
Sensei is giving no reaction while enduring severe pain
This will hurt.
That was amazing.
Sensei, can you do it again?
Do it again?
Sensei, you don't have to.
Sensei, that's enough!
It's alright, you don't have to do it.
That hurts!
It hurts that much, huh?
It's alright, don't do it.
There is no reaction from him at all.
Should we go?
Let's get out.
Ah, so you're doing it.
Ah, there it is.
That hurts really bad...
It's been 20 minutes since we started.
The storms of punishment are not stopping.
So we only started for 20 minutes?
There will be even more stronger assassins waiting for them.
We stopped at a strange place.
Arrived at a bus stop
Double Cheesecake
Tsuchiya Anna
Himura Yuki
Double Cheesecake
Uwah, that was bad.
We didn't pass.
No, we didn't.
This time was no good, huh?
I wonder why
An unsuccessful comedian duo
It must be that judge.
I wonder why. I guess they don't have any sense.
That's right! It must be that.
I know right? That must be it!
Should we show them our joke?
To someone here.
Okay ♥
Should we show them?
Yeah~
Ah!?
Ah!
We met last year, right?
Do you remember us?
That's right!
We want to show someone our joke...
Well, I...
I want to show our joke...
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING!?!
She's just doing as she likes.
You shouldn't laugh this soon.
Reason for being unsuccessful (1)
Tsuchiya is acting too freely
That's scary.
She's being too free.
I won't laugh.
That's right. Don't laugh.
Just hold it together.
We want to show you our sketch after a year.
Do you want to watch our growth the past year?
That's fine.
Really? Yay!
Thank you so much!
Alright!
Double Cheesecake presents a short sketch.
New Year's Day!!
Sketch "New Year's Day"
Alright, here you go.
Okay.
Are you ready? Let's go.
Have fun.
I'm ready.
Let's go!
Okay.
Oh yeah...
Before this...
There was a man who wanted to look cool so he put on color contacts.
WHAAAAATTT!????
SO HE REALLY DID, HUH!?
A man is in silence!
The naked eye.
That's another person's joke!!
We're not rare.
We're not baked.
That's right, we're double cheesecake.
It feels like we did it.
No way...
They copy other people's jokes
Reason for being unsuccessful (2)
You didn't do it at all...
What do you think?
We really leveled up, right?
Right?
Hi there, double cheesecake!
Ah, what is that?
Well, we...
You can't laugh, earlier I started laughing as well.
This is an amazing world.
That hurts!
Kechaa!!
We just got back from an audition too.
Really? How was it?
Comedian
Wakabayashi Masayasu
Rola
Comedian
Well, it was a bit..
Another unsuccessful comedian duo
It didn't go well?
Yeah...
Why don't you show them your joke?
Eh?
These are our friends...
They're really funny!
We are.
Just show them. Go!
Shall we?
Good luck!
A short sketch.
"A funny story".
Sketch "A funny story"
Today, I have a really funny story to tell!
What kind of story?
I was walking down the street the other day...
And um...
You were walking down the street...
Um...
Are you okay?
What was it again...
Rola-chan, can it be that you forgot your story?
Ah! Oh no! I forgot!
Heetakoitaa!!
Heetakoitaa?
She doesn't even know the original joke!
I forgot it~!
But that doesn't matter!
Rola-chan, that's another person's joke.
Ehehehehe
We have a hole.
But we're not chikuwa.
We're The Baumkuchen.
That wasn't good at all.
Reason for being unsuccessful (3)
Obviously copying other people's joke
That hurts!
I'm glad we showed them our joke.
That was great, right?
Your joke quality is higher.
Excuse me...
Can you see some joke from one of us?
It's something that's not a sketch, can you watch that?
Yeah, go ahead.
Really, then show them.
Well, our Rola is really good at making sentences with syllables.
The Baumkuchen's strength:
Good with compositions
She can really sum up the sentences quite well.
Can we show it to you?
Why don't we start with the word Ha.Ma.Da.Ma.Sa.To.Shi?
Topic
Hamada Masatoshi
Is it alright?
Yes.
Let's start with the first syllable from Hamada Masatoshi.
Ha
Violent retorts
Ma
In a flash
Da
Without fail, the important stuff
Ma
Earnestly
Sa
As expected
To
He puts in the effort
Shi
Unbelievably has a Gorilla's face
You didn't even connect the sentence.
That was not related at all.
No continuation at all.
Rola is harsh
No matter what we said, you already know what you'll be saying!
That must be it!
You already decided earlier to say it.
Shall we show them another one?
Our Rola has a lot of secret stories about celebrities.
The Baumkuchen's strength:
She can expose a lot of stories of any celebrities
She has lots of them. If you say a celeb's name, she can expose something about them.
Shall we do it? Who wants to start?
Go ahead.
Antonio Inoki-san.
Ah, Inoki!
I know him.
"You bastard!!" That person right?
That person used to exist in the past.
What was that?
Is that so? That's amazing!
You can't even call that an exposure.
You really know a lot, Rola-chan.
Double cheesecake's strength:
Performing an amazing skill with the help of an item
Let's go and show them.
Yes!
With her butt...
Gimme a sec.
She'll break a chopstick with her butt.
Double cheesecake's strength:
She's break a chopstick in half using the power of her butt
Okay, I'm ready. Put it seriously lower.
Lower.
What is she saying "Put it seriously lower"?
Lower, lower.
Around here?
Lower.
Around here is okay?
Yeah!
Okay, now let's do this!
Will it break? 3, 2, 1...
Yeah, it broke!!
What the hell was that.
I broke it.
That was awesome!
So cool!!
That wasn't cool at all...
Look, look.
Well, that was great, right?
It was great!
I gained confidence.
Thank you so much; sorry for taking up your time.
Thank you so much.
Really, thank you.
We gained confidence as girls as well.
We really did it properly, right?
Goodbye!
Do your best!
It actually broke.
Yeah, it did.
There's only a little bit more on the bus trip.
The central prison is approaching closer.
We are about to arrive, guys.
That was really far.
Finally, the bus with the five prisoners are about to arrive to the central prison.
But that is not the goal! It is a new battlefield.
Look, everyone. That...
That is the Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison.
We've arrived.
We're here! We're here!
We've finally arrived.
The stage for our No-Laughter:
Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison.
The first prison for rules and laughter.
The fierce battle with assassins is about to start.
It's a  prison?
There aren't even any fences
Huh?
The bus comes right in front of the prison. That seems dangerous!
That's amazing
The bus arrives at Central Prison
Alright let's go everyone
Let's go
This is Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison, guys
Guys we've arrived let's go
Muhoho... *cough*
Excuse me
Shall we go?
He's pantomiming
This isn't right
Wait
Man, I lost too
Of course we'd lose
It's not really like losing
They're here they're here
This is an endurance test
Sure let's get off
It's cold
It's this way
Right, of course
It's cold
Look, it's a pretty fancy building
Yeah, it is
It's amazing
Prison entrance
It's this way
This is the entrance
No one is here
Really
Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison...
Prison 2nd Floor
Listen guys
At this end is this prison's
director's office
Prison director?
Don't be rude
Do prisoners go to greet the director?
Yes, because we're prisoners
Prison director's office
Excuse us
Nobody is even in here
Oh, nobody is in here
Just line up and wait here
It's cold
Oh, what happened?
Prison director
Mizobata Junpei
This is what happened
We wanted to greet the director
Oh, what happened?
Prison director
Mizobata Junpei
This is what happened
We wanted to greet the director
so we came here
Is that right?
Sorry, the director is not here right now
Oh?
Are you an actor or something?
No
Oh is that so?
excuse me
You looked so cool so...
At this moment Junpei thought
What is with this out of fashion handsome face
Even though he's an extra
he's like a poorly paid actor selling himself
Maybe his real job
is a cheap job
that's like Gravure Idols
that's what he thought
How unfair
They're doing that now?
I don't think it's like that
Mystery of Director's Office
You can hear his heart's voice
I can believe it
That's what you think about me?
You think weirdly
Oh?
You have trash on your chin
At this moment Junpei thought
What's up with this guy's chin?
Does he put something in it?
What?
Does this feel like
a hamburg?
T/L note: Hamburg is a popular Salisbury steak dish in Japan
Did he put a half-eaten hamburg in his chin?
This is what he thought
It's a hamburg
That's amazing
This is...
Why is it hamburg?
It's not like that
He's stupid
Mizubata-kun is thinking
He's thinking weird things
Everything is revealed
What the hell
Oh... sorry I'm late Junpei-kun
Prison Director
Nishikawa Helen
Oh... sorry I'm late Junpei-kun
I thought the director was a man
Ahhh whaaat?
I definitely thought it was a man
We all thought it would be a man
So that means
we need guts
These 5 new prisoners want to greet the director
Oh is that so?
You, what's your name?
It's Endo Shouzou
Is that right?
Nice to meet you
At this moment Helen thought
Hm?
This guy
shaves his eyebrows?
This 40 something year old man
is conscious about his sex appeal so he shaves his brows
but... this eyebrow shape
I've seen it before
Ah!
It's Oguri Shun!
This guy
is conscious about a younger actor
Oguri Shun's eyebrows!
This is what she thought
What the hell
Oguri Shun?
Mystery of the Director's Room
You can hear her heart's voice
She's really thinking some weird things
She really thinks weird things about me
Yeah
You, what's your name?
It's Matsumoto Hitoshi
You are in very good shape
At this moment Helen thought
What?
Why is there a porn star here?
Among comedians,
why is there a porn star?
No, that's wrong!
This guy is a pro wrestler!
He came to announce his next pro match!
There's no doubt about it!
It's too long!
This is what she thought
My buttcheeks hurt
It's really hot in here
This room is blazing hot
It is hot
Maybe the heater is too high
Hot...
It's too hot!!
It's hot!!
At this moment Hamada thought
You're gonna wear it?!
This is what he thought
That's what I thought
I thought that too
But I thought that!!
You
You've had a sullen look on your face
No...
Do you have something
you wish to say to me?
Not really...
Say it
At this moment Housei thought
This old hag!
She wants to fight with me?
Even though I was being quiet
she has the nerve!
Even though she's just a gold digger
who wants more money!
Otherwise
She wouldn't have married someone like Medama!
This is what he thought
That's a messy thought
You...
That's what you were thinking!?
Scary
Don't make me look stupid
At this moment Helen thought
Oh!
Oh no!
How unlike me
to yell at a comedian who
only sold 40 tickets
in a room with a max occupancy of 140 people
only 3 days before
his solo performance!
I raised my voice at a poorly paid comedian!
This is what she thought
That's alright
I've been part of this world for 50 years!!
If you humiliate me I will not tolerate it!!
Quickly get out of my office!
Let's go
We're going
She got really pissed
Yes you're right
She's staring at us
She just made herself angry
Yeah you're right
prisoner life has just begun but
the path looks like a lot of laughter traps
Their long prisoner lifestyle has just begun
the path for the 5 guys
has many laughter traps in store
This is the newcomers' room
Ahhhh!
This is our base
It's cold
Okay get in
Newcomers' room
It's nice
It really is
It's a tatami room?!
Oh it is
Isn't it nice? The prison has prepared you a nice room
Oh it's a tatami room
Huh
Wow...
Of course there'd be drawers
Alright everyone, just be on standby in this room
2 hours since the start
From now on
it's time for Hell on Earth
Coming right up, it's time for the drawer pranks!
10:30 AM, it's time for the drawers from hell
Time living as a prisoner: 2 hours
Shall we?
Drawer Pranks START
Let's go
Are we going to open them?
Like who to start with
Oh right, there is that
Usually I start and go down in order
Right, that's true
But this year, is that how we want to do it?
So...
He's always getting scared,
so should we start with Tanaka?
This year's top batter is Tanaka
Let's do this
Okay
It's probably a DVD
In the past, there were a lot of DVDs
DVDs 5 years in a row
Thai Kicks
Hotel
Spy
Airport
Enthusiastic Teachers
Defense Force
We'll watch it later
Yes, alright, time to open the drawers
Don't like this...
The first drawer has nothing in it
Nothing?
Yes
This year there are tatami mats, so we need to be careful
It's slippery
The second one has nothing
It could be that all of them are empty
How about this long one?
Oh, well, there's still a fourth drawer at the bottom
The fourth one also has nothing
Whoa, nothing
Ah!!
A DVD
Mysterious DVD x 1
Leave that for later
Yeah, let's deal with this later
Here I go
From the long one
What!?
There it is
What's that?
(Secret) Prison Escape Notebook
Prison Escape Notebook??
Prison Escape Notebook...
So that means we can't look at it
Like it's only for Hosei
Right, it's not ours to look at
Yeah, otherwise it'd be left out in the open
Nothing
Then, Matsumoto
Huh, me?
Well...
Should we do it this way?
It's fine
In this order, then
Yes, I agree
The blast...
Smoke blast from drawer
Right, it's always Matsumoto
In the past, yeah
I'm seriously still traumatized from those blasts
Just opening my drawers at home
sometimes makes my heart race
And again,
there's something here!!
It's a key
Key?
Mysterious key (no.14)
Key number 14
Well, let's just check the last one
Ah yes
Number 14...
Inside the room, there are lockers numbered 1 to 20
The lockers...
They're all numbered, one by one
Yes
Ah, number 14 is right here
Not right now
Oh right, let's do it later
Do it later?
Alright, I guess it's my turn
Whoa!?
Ehh!?
It's the same, the same!
A key
Key?
What?
Number 3
Mysterious Key (no. 3)
What's the number?
Number 3
Nothing
Just the key
Then it's only this
A series of keys huh?
Give me a break
What the hell, there's 2 of them...
Is it okay if I go?
Yep!! Again, something new...
How scary
It's escalated
A letter
Something's written on here, what is this?
Mysterious Envelope
Why don't you check it out
Take a look
Should be okay to take a look
Ehh, this sequence is way too scary
Don't know what's in there
In the past, there were a lot of different things
that's in this room
Open the silver briefcase
Instructions
"Open the silver briefcase that's in this room"
I was curious about that
That?
Oh, it's this
Briefcase
I was curious about it
It's that one
Should I take care of it now?
It'd be better to get it over with
It'd be better to just open it
It's pretty big, Endo
Oh god, so scary
Is it okay to look?
Oh god, so scary!!
That is pretty scary
Briefcase
My heart is pounding right now
You don't think that Chiaki is in there, right?
I doubt that
Ehh!?
How should I do this?
Can I take it over there?
Well, that's fine, but...
Sure, over there
Sorry, pardon me
Man, this is so scary
Is it heavy?
No, it's not that heavy
Here??
Is that okay?
Is this going to be okay?
But maybe it's better over there?
It says, "Do not turn this upside down"
Just like that
Here I go
Stop doing that
Oh, sorry
Huh?
This...
There's one for everyone
Inside are Gas Masks
A gas mask for Matsumoto...
Announcement
State of emergency! State of emergency!
At this time, a strong odorous gas is leaking within the prison
So scary
For those who are indoors,
put on a protective mask immediately!
Hold on, hold on
It's on
Announcement
At this time, the source is being secured and disposed
Those who are indoors, please remove your protective masks
What the hell, that was unexpected!!
That surprised me
Hosei in a strange predicament...
It's okay to remove it now
I could've died
Adhesive in Hosei's Mask
Proper safety measures were taken
This is no good!
I was wondering what the hell you were doing
That's what it was
Scary
That surprised me
I seriously thought, "What is he doing?"
So very scary
Why was that in Endo's drawer...
You really might've died
Could've killed me
I suddenly couldn't breathe, seriously
That's dangerous
Stop that please
Really though, that's dangerous
That's really scary
What is this?
What is that?
It might not have been harmful, but...
How about the others?
There's nothing else
Matsumoto, that...
Damnit
Geez, way too scary
Mysterious Key (no. 14)
Number 14
This was the first one
Yes
It's this one here
Locker number 14
It's small
I don't want to do this...
Even if you say it's small...
It's still very scary
Yeah, it's still scary
What is that?
What!?
A pumpkin...
Mysterious Pumpkin
That's pretty big...
What?
How scary
That is scary
Pft heehee fufu...
Halloween?
It's a pumpkin monster
A Halloween pumpkin?
But the timing is...
It's already over
It's New Year's Eve already
You can't do that!!
That's amazing!
Pisses me off!!
Artwork of Hamada's Face
You can't not laugh at that!
That's amazing
This is incredible
This is very high quality
It turned out so well
Who makes this kind of stuff?
That's really good
This is...
The wig he's wearing today...
That's right
They matched it for today
Can't do this
Right now
This crosses the space-time continuum
They predicted this and did it
That was the case
I'm going to put this away
Amazing
What kind of expression is that?
Geez...
Hosei's sticky stuff is
stuck all over the place
Isn't it?
on your own
Look at the prison escape notebook
Oh, that's right
But really, it's kinda scary
Alright, gonna look!!
Oh, you're going to look?
Are you going to look?
I will
Well, for now, Yamasaki will look
Yes
(Secret) Prison Escape Notebook
Why does only Yamasaki get the Prison Escape Notebook?
Yeah
To whoever finds this notebook,
Prison Escape Notebook
It took me 10 years to finish,
but these are my notes on how to get out of the prison
through a secret escape route.
Those who find this,
promptly use the escape route
to break out of the prison.
From the Prison Escape King
Wait, really?
Is it telling all of us to do that?
From the Prison Escape King
to break out of the prison
Prison Escape Notebook
It says "to whoever finds this"
"Whoever finds this"...
"To whoever finds this notebook, promptly..."
What!?
There's a sketch
If you remove this door
there lies the escape route
In the Prison Escape Notebook, the escape route is drawn on a map
Is there a map?
There is a map
In this room?
Prison Escape Notebook
there lies the escape route
If you remove this door,
Sketch of the Room
What door?
There isn't one, but maybe it's a disguised door
Door?
Is it here?
How is it situated?
It's like this and like that
This
It's the locker!!
If we move it...
Ah!!
It's a fake locker
Isn't it impossible if you don't move it out of the way?
And you're laughing.
You’re all laughing as if everything's fine.
As if you're all at peace and in harmony.
I thought I could go through the locker...
Your reaction there was also...
He was laughing there.
Let me help.
There
Wow!!
That’s it.
Huh!?
Where does this go?
You can escape.
Open that.
Just open and go through, right?
Whoa!!
What is this?
A secret escape route
That's amazing.
You're kidding.
You can escape.
Yes, you can make it.
Why just Hosei?
I’m gonna go check it out.*
*Note: Hosei did not use honorifics in his speech here, which is an inappropriate way for him to speak to his seniors, Downtown.  Matsumoto reacts to that.
Who the hell do you think you’re talking to?
Like “I’m gonna go.”
I will check it out.
If I’m able to escape, um...
I'll come again.
Like idiots trying to have a conversation.
Without any sense of gravity of the situation.
What, are you coming back to visit a sick friend?
You're not going to escape?
I’ll help everyone escape.
Ah, I see.
You’ll be fine leaving this prison escape notebook here?
Is that fine, Hosei?
He went on.
He ignored us.
What is this?
It’s scary, isn’t it?
It’s scary.
Who knows what's coming.
And you can guess it’s not going to be anything good.
It's open.
Kida Taro* is defecating
*Note: Kida Taro is a composer.
I've never seen that before.
What are you doing?
He was laughing like crazy.
What’s going on?
It’s the first time for us to see it.
What the hell…
Yes.
He’s back.
He’s come back.
You got smacked?
You got smacked, right?
Yes, but
I made it.
We can make it.
Really?
We can really make it.
Matsumoto, could you…
Just in case
If you just learned the route now
it’ll definitely be good!
Hosei guides the next victim
Since we have to find our way out in the end.
Why me?
I just wanted to show you.
If you can make it out.
Huh, why is it me?
Ok, I’m gonna go.
Whoa!!
It’s pretty long, huh?
Right?
It's pretty long.
Huh!?
Wow!!
You're doing that as well.
Shibata Rie* is defecating
*Note: Shibata Rie is a comedian and tarento.
Ahahahaha!
Huh?
He’s laughing like crazy.
What?
What is it?
He’s laughing like crazy.
Geez!!
He isn't escaping at all.
Seriously.
Haha
But the route is really…
He was laughing so much.
Oh yeah.
You all as well.
He’s come back now.
That’s amazing.
Right?
Escape!?
Wow.
We can get out.
"We can get out," I thought
And I got excited.
And that caused me to go  "Babaam!"
Right?
Firstly, having our seniors
escape first would be…
That’s right, we’ll…
The next victim is Hamada
Thus,
the next victim is Hamada.
You can just go ahead and escape.
I’ll just lead the two of them out.
Since you know the route.
What?
Here?
Kida Taro is defecating again
You could see it  already.
You could see it?
The entrance or the exit.
I don’t know if it’s an entrance or an exit, but you could see it.
Oh, you could already...
You could get out.
It hadn't come out  yet, as in...
It hadn’t come out yet, but...
You had gotten that far out, is what you mean?
Could have gone out but didn’t.
Had gotten that far out?
So I can just get out?
Here he comes.
That's how you open it?
That’s just…
It had gotten that far out.
Mfhahahaha!
That's excitement from
being able to get out?
He was laughing a lot.
Being able to get out, or...
It doesn’t sound like that kind of laughter, though.
This guy’s all rough.
There are those rough ones.
He’s just putting them back on as if everything's fine.
As if everything's fine.
A little got out, I think?
A little might have gotten out already.
So they're able to get out a little.
A little got out already.
Oh, Hamada’s back.
Does an escape look possible?
Mmm.
Like, is it already coming out?
Already coming out?
We’re able to come out,
but their side is also kind of coming out.
What's their side?
What’s their side?
Their side?
Their side...
Their side is also coming out...
No, you see, you see.
You see...
Wait.
Yes, yes.
Who was it?
When you went.
It was the same, right?
The same…
Did you see the face?
I saw it.
Glasses, right?
Someone you'd call a sensei*.
*Note: Here, sensei is an honorific used for people of certain professions that are considered traditionally high-end or academic, including musical composers.
Someone you'd call a sensei?
A sensei?
Well, right?
Right.
It was the same, right?
Kida Taro?
It wasn't.
What?
What’s the matter?
What is it?
You’re kidding.
What’s going on?
No, you see, if you go in, it leads to a bathroom.
So you can get out through a bathroom
But when I and Yama-chan looked up
Kida Taro was there with his butt out
taking a dump.
It came out.
Then I was different.
It was a different person?
How many people are there, then?
It was different?
That’s where...
That’s where they put in
a large number of personnel?
That’s unbelievable!!
That is...
Well, anyway, then just...
There’s two…
Watch it at the studio!!
Just... yes.
Three hours into prison life.
The desk drawer pranks continue.
Three hours into prison life
Should we watch it?
Well, let’s get it out of the way.
1 mysterious DVD
That’ll be everything, right?
Yes.
Once we watch this, that’ll be everything
Yes, we might as well.
inside the desk drawers.
Because of last year, you know.
I know, really.
Last year’s DVD
A thank you letter from one’s son led to a Thai kick
This fearful thing.
Not one good thing has come from this.
Here goes.
You're all flustered.
It’s just one DVD this year?
Just one.
Muscly Old Man
Storyboard:
Munakata Jou
Illustration, Artwork:
Miru Miru
Once upon a time, long, long ago
What's this?
there lived a kind-hearted man, Old Man Tanaka.
Old Man Tanaka just loved animals
This seems...
and he loved his dog
as if it were his own son.
This seems kind of…
Oh, Shiro
you are so cute.
There, there.
Next to him lived Old Man Matsumoto.
Old Man Matsumoto just
loved muscles, and
he loves his tight t-shirt
We’re going to stop-and-start this frequently here?
I guess so.
This is like Jimmy's section*, isn't it?
*Note: Jimmy refers to Jimmy Onishi, who often appears in videos during the New Year's batsu game episodes.
This frequently?
Old Man Matsumoto just
loves  his muscles, and
loved his tight t-shirt
as if it were his own son.
ghjghjghjghjghj
T-shirts gotta be one size smaller and from Avirex.  Only way to go.
That's not true.
One day,
Old man Matsumoto as usual
was working out in the mountains when
What the hell, be quiet, I'm working out over here!
When he looked, there stood Old man Tanaka and his dog, Shiro
Shiro-han, what's wrong?
I have no idea what you mean, but do you want me to dig here?
There, there.
And when old man Tanaka dug where Shiro told him to...
Protein
My God, what is this? It's protein!
I'm speechless!
What the hell is with this world?
Yeah, I know...
It is so weird though, right?
It's so weird!
It definitely is strange...
This world they've created  is bizarre!
This world they've created is so weird
And the Osaka-ben (Kansai dialect) is a bit off too!!
When old man Tanaka
dug where Shiro told him to...
Protein
My god, what is this? It's protein!
I'm speechless!
From the ground, a hell of a lot of protein came out!
Old man Matsumoto, who was watching all of this said...
Oh man, that's so awesome
If I had that much protein...
how much would I bulk up?
Naturally being addicted to muscles
and moaning that he will not drink water unless it's at room temperature
and just generally acting like a super model
old man Matsumoto was just so jealous of the protein, he couldn't control himself.
So that night...
Shit, shit, shit
Doesn't this just piss you off?
Doesn't this just really piss you off?
This is really funny.
Doesn't this piss you off?
This is bad...
Shit, shit, shit
This world is really bad
That mask is a no-no
like talking about water  being at room temperature and stuff
like talking about water being at room temperature  and stuff
memos about what you like
So that night, wearing a large mask
and a black cap
He sneaks into Tanaka's house
The mask suits him
shit...
He kidnapped Shiro the dog
And the next day...
Oi, you bloody dog. Where do I need to dig to get me some protein!?
Here huh? There, there...
Now I can become a real machine too!
Hang on, nothing is coming out!
You bloody dog, you tricked me, huh?!
Old man Matsumoto got so cross that nothing came out
that he tied Shiro to the tree and left him there...
Shiro! Shiro-han, where are ya!?
Shiro, what happened? You poor thing!
When old man Tanaka untied Shiro from the tree...
Shiro suddenly...
What's wrong bud?
Is there something over there?
Old man Tanaka was lead into the forest by Shiro.
When suddenly...
Wow, holy shit, what is this?!
What a huge castle!
When out of nowhere, a beautiful castle he had never seen before
appeared before him.
This was a castle which was full of dogs
and because Tanaka saved Shiro,
he was treated to great food whilst being entertained by dancers and music
and he received great hospitality here
Haha, this is so fun!
And, when old man Tanaka was about to go home...
the dog looking after him brought two wicker baskets.
As a souvenir, we present you with a big wicker basket
and a small wicker basket.
However, you can only open one of these wicker baskets.
No matter what, you may not open both wicker baskets.
And old man Tanaka, who was told this
cleverly using his chin
took home with him the two wicker baskets.
Hey, old man Tanaka.
You have some awesome wicker baskets there.
Give me one of them!
No, this is a precious souvenir of mine.
However much you beg me for it, I can't give you this.
Oh just shut the hell up, I'm taking the bigger one!
You're such a bad person!
Unbelievably, old man Matsumoto didn't even listen to old man Tanaka's story,
and just took the bigger wicker basket
and went back to his house.
Could there be a life time supply of protein
in here?
I can't wait anymore!
And so old man Matsumoto went to
open the big wicker basket...
Unbelievably, out of the wicker basket
came out monsters we could not imagine from this world
This is not good, this is really not good!
Eventually, old man Matsumoto
was dragged down into hell.
HELP MEEEEE
Meanwhile
when old man Tanaka opened his smaller wicker basket...
What, what is this?!
Unbelievably, inside the wicker basket, was a Thai Kick boxer!
The Thai Kick boxer jumped out of the wicker basket
and kicked old man Tanaka's arse as hard as he could!
THE END
This is absolutely ridiculous!
Punished for opening the second wicker basket
That is amazing
That is brutal
No no, this is just absolutely ridiculous!
This bloody story.
Well there is no escape...
is there...
It was inside (the basket)...
You opened it...
Is it possible for both to contain bad things?
It's because old man Matsumoto opened the other one...
Hang on a minute...
Hurry up
No I don't want to
I don't want to
Hurry up and get it over with
Every bloody year, I'm sick of it
Hurry up and stand up!
Just get ready...
Stand up you piece of shit...
First things first, stand...
There's no point doing that
There is nothing we can do about this...
No point..
Stand up!
Get ready for it anyway...
I do understand how you feel...
There are  unnecessary options  with this situation
Just before he's going to get kicked...
There are other options too...
What an unnecessary option...
Please, wait a minute...
It's going to happen eventually so...
Isn't this... strange?
Isn't this just really strange?
I do understand how you feel...
You have to stand still!
Please wait a minute!
It's dangerous, man!
No, wait, wait, please.
It won't hurt as much this year
Yeah, he's right.
It's every bloody year...
I know...
Hurry up, he's not sure what to do!
I will, but isn't this just really strange?
See, that's your other option...
There's your other option right there.
There's no point, right?
It hurts so much...
The second one was a beautiful connection...
It really hurt... ARGH!
UGGGAAAAA!!
good job...
I'm sorry he took so long to get ready...
This hurts so much...
Yeah it really does...
It hurts...
It hurts
It hurts so bad
It hurts so so bad!
So bad...
My chinko hurts so bad
You can't say that...
For crying out loud Tanaka...
My chinko hurts...
Tanaka...
My chinko hurts so bad...
What's wrong with you?
How did it hurt your chinko?
Why... how?
My chinko hurts so bad...
Tanaka, you're not the kind of person who says things like that, right?
Yeah, you're not!
Stop it this instant, Tanaka.
Where does it hurt?
My chinko...
Don't say it!...
1:00 PM
Just after finishing looking through the drawers.
Right, shall we get going?
Off to a rehabilitaion meeting
a lesson for  prisoners
The 5 will take part in a rehabilitation meeting
A rehabilitation meeting?
It's here, guys
Can you come in here?
Oh great, the front seats are available...
I've seen this guy before...
There are other prisoners present
Come in guys...
Prisoner
Nakamura Yoshinobu (producer)
Suga Kenji (director)
Prisoner
Umezu Kazuo
I'll come get you when you're finishedso pay attention!!
I'll come get you when you're finished so pay attention!!
Why is the seat next to me open?...
Seat next to Matsumoto is empty
I have a really bad feeling about it...
Maybe another talent is coming?...
Policeman
Takahashi Shigeo
My name is Takashi and I'm in charge of this meeting...
Okay, first of all...
We're going to do a roll call!
1st of all, Kitamura
Yes
Second, Sato
Taking roll call of the criminals
Yes
Third, Nagahara.
Fourth
Sorry...
Comedian
Ito Ichirou (ELT)
Hey, you're late!
These kind of guys tend to be planning an escape
Do a body search to make sure he's not got any weapons on him!
Body check for late attendance
Put your hands in the air
Nwooooooooo!!!
Grabbed his chest as hard as possible
Too hard, too hard!
What the hell..
Of course he would say that...
Jesus...
Is that okay?...
He doesn't seem to have anything on him...
Okay fine, go sit down then.
Sits on chair next to Matsumoto
Sits down beside Matsumoto
Before we start our training, we compiled a few examples of life lessons for you.
Before beginning the rehabilitation for all you guys who  live here
Before beginning the rehabilitation for all you guys who live here
We invited some singers to sing them.
Training program (1)
Invited singers to entertain
Hopefully this famous song can help you calm down.
Now, let's welcome them.
Could it possibly be~ Could it possibly be~
Dobu Rock
Eguchi Naoto               Mori Shintaro
That she is hitting on me~
While I was eating at a Chinese food restaurant
There was a Chinese waitress
She was fighting with the cook in the kitchen in Chinese
Could it possibly be~ Could it possibly be~
That she fell in love with me and told him she wanted to change her nationality?
Dobu Rock's Eguchi
Azuma Mikihisa
That she is hitting on me~
※Even if they laughed, we are continuing on, so please watch.
When I was walking in my hometown, Shibuya
A gal came out of 109 department store
She suddenly passed out and caused a ruckus
Could it possibly be~ Could it possibly be~
Does this mean she wants me to do some french kissing CPR to her?
Is he an idiot!?
What the hell is "French kiss CPR"!!
Could it really be~ Could it maybe~
Dobu Rock's Eguchi
Gushiken Yoko
That she is hitting on me~
After 12 rounds of boxing
She said my stamina as a boxer is so amazing
Could it really be~ Could it maybe~
That's wrong!!
Even your tempo is wrong!!
Could it possibly be~
Do you want to fight the 13th round with me?
He changed most of the song.
Hey!
You're not suppose to shout "Hey!".
Could it possibly be~ Could it possibly be~
Dobu Rock's Eguchi
Mori Kumiko
That they are hitting on me~
I went to a restaurant in Nishiazabu
I ordered wine for drinking
When I was asked "Red or white?"
Could it possibly be~ Could it possibly be~
Does this mean you want to check the color of my panties?
Dobu Rock's Eguchi
Umemiya Tatsuo
That she is rolling over for me~
He can't even say it...
I was fishing in the sea
A young girl was fishing beside me
She got stung by a bee and panicked
Could it possibly be~ Could it possibly be~
Does she want me to urinate onto her as first aid treatment?
All the popular celebrities seem to be successful
But a certain researcher told us
Most of the celebrities are just a bunch of PERVERTS~
Yeah~ Yeah~ Yeah yeah~
Could it possibly be~ Could it possibly be~
Could it possibly be~
Gushiken-san was so bad.
His was really bad.
He couldn't say it.
Even that "Could it possibly be" is wrong.
He couldn't say it even once!!
That was a really good song to listen to.
When you go through bad times, remember that song and try your best!!
Training program (2)
Hypnotherapy to purify the prisoner's heart
And now they will participate in a hypnotherapy session to purify their hearts.
It will be done by a world famous hypnotist called Mitchel.
Very famous hypnotist
Mitchel can hypnotize anyone!!
Mitchel-san, who will you hypnotize?
Then, the four of you.
Please come to the front.
The 4 people are called to be hypnotized
Mitchel-san wants to hypnotize you as well.
Being called out to be hypnotized by Mitchel
Please come forward.
Do your best!!
This is the start of a disaster.
It really is.
I think we laughed so much at this.
This is hell!!
I think this will be hard.
It really is.
Please relax.
Your consciousness is mine.
Are they hypnotized?
They are?
They are all completely hypnotized.
Endo is now hypnotized
Now I will touch 3 people's shoulders.
When I touch you,
You will be a tyrannosaurus.
The 2nd person I touch will be Stegosaurus.
The 3rd person will be a Pteranodon.
Tyrannosaurus.
Stegosaurus.
And you're Pteranodon.
GOoooo~!!
OGO! OGO! OGO! OGO! OGO! OGO!
What the hell is he even saying?
Do they actually go "OGO OGO OGO" like that?
How do you feel to be hypnotized?
Was I really hypnotized?
Yes, you were.
My body feels really hot when I was under...
1:30 PM.
The five prisoners are talking about hypnosis.
But that was good, right?
OGO!! OGO!! OGO!!
Even his hands were like this.
Endo's Pteranodon
It was really amazing.
That was embarrassing!
But you did it!
I don't remember it at all.
Yeahhh, serves you right!
Because you were laughing when we're not suppose to laugh!!
You're right, I laughed.
Sorry, sorry.
That was amazing.
Well, yeah.
That was the most brutal yet.
The Pteranodon?
Yeah.
I think they're amazing.
They still went extinct even though they were strong.
They were really strong.
OGO!! OGO!! OGO!!
Did you laugh?
That was a nice hit!
That was gorgeous.
Because you laughed!
Gorgeous!!
That was gorgeous!!
1:30 PM
Life in prison is unexpectedly occupied.
Uwah, it's a gymnasium.
Come on in.
Compete with rival prison
Participate in a recreational competition
They are going to participate in a recreational competition with a rival prison.
This kind of setting, huh.
Becuase it's recreational from now on, it's okay to laugh.
Special rule
During recreation time it's OK to laugh!!
Now, everyone. Please wait for your entry to the stage.
Alright.
Fat-face West Prison
KABA. chan
FUJIWARA's Fujimoto
Animal Hamaguchi
Madame Dewi
Kano Eiko
Bobby Ologun
Peace's Ayabe
Their rival for the recreational competition are the prisoners of Big-face West Prison.
And the host for this show is...
Prison rivals!
It's the battle recreational competition!
Some funny person is coming out!
Thank you for thinking that. I'm your host, Chihara Junior!
Chihara Junior
Nice!
Nihon TV Announcer
Tokushima Erika
My name is Tokushima Erika.
Animal-san, what do you need to win?
Yes!
Here I go! Let's say it!!
IT'S SPIRIT! SPIRIT! SPIRIT! IT'S SPIRIT!!!!!!
IF YOU HAVE THE SPIRIT YOU CAN WIN!!
I see, thank you!
Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison
Tsukitei Housei
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Ogi Naoki
Agnes Chan
For Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison, Ogi Mama & Agnes Chan will participate as well.
How do you feel, Ogi Mama?
Hopefully you will kindly teach me the secret to winning ♥
Yes.
They're on our team?
Yes, your teammates.
Ogi Mama & Agnes.
Yup, Ogi Mama & Agnes Chan.
I'm Agnes!
What can this useless person even do?
That's mean!
He called you useless.
It's okay.
She said she's fine.
Even to this day, her Japanese is still broken.
The first match is "Between the wall, conveyor belt battle!"
Between the wall
Conveyor belt battle!!
For this game, 5 representatives from each team have to do certain things to clear the stage.
Between the wall, conveyor belt battle
5 representatives will challenge each round
If even one person fails, everyone else will get punished as well.
Failing the MISSION will get everybody punished
That is the system that we will use, so please do your best.
Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison
Fat-face West Prison.
With their spirit and pride on the line, it's a serious battle.
Putting their spirit and pride on the line
A serious battle!!
The first recreation is...
Blow away all the ping pong balls!
BLOW OUT ALL THE PING-PONG BALLS!
What the hell...
A bowl with 30 ping pong balls is going to come
Rules
Right, a bowl containing 30 ping pong balls is going to come your way.
Blow the ping pong balls out of the bowl.
You each take turns and you need to blow the ping pong balls out of the bowls.
Blow all the balls out and you are clear
If you can blow all the ping pong balls out of the bowl, you clear this mission. If you don't, however, you will be punished.
I think we can do this.
We can do this I think?
Fat-face West Prison
Blow the ping pong balls out of the bowl!
First up, the Fat-Face Prison members
The members above will try the challenge.
Okay, here we go then. Start!
It's coming!
START
Punishment
Okay here we go, go!
Blow hard, blow hard!
Go, go, go!
Blow hard!
Harder!
Okay!!!
Let's go!
Get the balls out!
Wow, amazing
amazing...
You did so well, keep it up!
Go, go
Keep going
Go, we can do this!
Mission Clear
That was amazing!
That was amazing
You're kidding me!
Kano-kun, how did you find it?
It was so easy...
Yes
How was it?
The others worked so hard
and because of that
it was so easy
What the hell was that comment?
Gaasu Kurobikari Prison members
Blow the ping pong balls out of the bowl!!
Next, the Kurobikari prison members take the challenge!
Okay here we go then, start!
Come on guys!!
Do your best!
Come on guys!
Can they really do it?
Here we go!
START
Punishment
Come on guys!
You're doing well, keep going
Come on, Mr Big Chin
You're doing well
Okay...
Blow!
Blow hard, you can do it!
Keep trying!
Hamada-san!
You can do it!
Come on!
Old man!
Come on gramps!
Oh gramps...
That was great!
The old Rakugoka (storyteller) man, you rock!
Amazing!
Here we go!
The bold old hag!
Go!
Come on, keep going!
The bobbed hair old hag and the bold old hag were useless!
Shut up with your old hag!
The bobbed hair old hag was the worst out of all of us, right?
He was literally so close to the balls as well!
Now for the 'Knock over the pins with your nose pistols!' round!!
Knock over the pins with the nose pistol!
Come on then!!!!
Stuff the peas in your nose and shoot it and knock over the pins
Rules
The rules are easy
Put the peas in the bowl coming down your way in your nose
And if any one of the guys can knock all 10 pins, you pass the mission.
Fat-face West Prison
Knock over the pins with the nose pistol!!
First of all, these members from the Fat Face prison will take on the challenge!
Here we go!
I can start already?
START
Punishment
Oh okay, I get it
They're so big!
Hurry up!!
Stick it up!
Go for it!
Next one!
Deeper in your nose!
Again!
It's not hitting it!
Hurry up!
Okay, next one up!
Aim better
It's starting to touch the pins!
Things are starting to heat up!
Go!!
Okay, here we go...
It's not hitting at all though!
It's getting heated up in here!
Debbie-san
Okay, next person up!
This is actually quite funny...
It's not hitting at all!
Keep it there...
Come on leader!
3 peas came out there!
It hit his hand...
Calm down...
I got it, I got it!
You have to get them all down...
Finished!
One person has to get them ALL down...
Oh right...
Gaasu Kurobikari Prison members
Knock down the pins with your nose pistol!!
Next up, is the Kurobikari Prison members.
Right, I hope the team full of old hags are ready to give us their best.
LET'S GO!
Right, the youngest old hag
START
Punishment
You can do this!
Right...
Go, go!
Aim well!
You're doing great!
Keep going!
No, this is no good...
One more time!
Go!
Again
I got 2, I got 2
Go again, again.
You're doing well
The bobbed haircut old hag looks so funny!
Right, the bald old hag!
Keep going! You got this!
Aim well!
Hold on a minute...
Bald old hag.. right...
Next up is the Rakugo old hag
Go go go!
You can do this!!!
Just a bit more!
Come on, keep it up!
Good good!
You did well!
Right, the old hag teacher!
Come on, you can do this!
Man, you're slow to load up...
Damn you're slow
hurry up!
You old bitch, hurry the fuck up!
Hurry up!
We're in trouble
Go!
That old hag let us down...
Time is up!
That was so funny!
That bobbed hair old hag was just brilliant!
Just amazing!
Eat the super sour cold noodles round!
Eat the super sour cold noodles!!
Let's eat it!
That sounds bad...
Eat all of the level 1-5 sour cold noodles
Rules
There are 5 different levels of sour cold noodles
If the 5 members can eat all of them, they pass the mission
Fat-face West Prison
Eat the super sour cold noodles!
First off, the Fat face prisoner members are up!
These are the members who will take on the challenge.
If Fuji-mon can finish all the sour noodles...
You clear this mission!
OKAY!
We're counting on you, leader!
Okay, let's do this!
We can do this!
Start!
Bring it on!
Here it comes!
It's coming now.
Okay.
START
Punishment
It sucks we don't know which one is which...
Go, go, go!
That's the least sour one
Okay, good good.
Eat another one!
Okay okay.
keep going!
That's great!
Debbie, go!
Go for it!
That's amazing
They might be able to do this
Go go!
What's he doing!
Don't throw it up!
Swallow it!
Wait, hold on
Eat it, quick!
Bobbie!
Go for it!
It's SO SOUR!
Go go go
He's going for it
THAT'S FRIGGING DISGUSTING
Oh man, I don't want to do this!!
Oh my god, oh my god!
I don't wanna!
You can do it!
Keep going!
Go go go!
Eat it all!
Gaasu Kurobikari Prison members
Eat the super sour cold noodles!
Next up is the Kurobikari Prison members
Let's do this, come on guys!
START
Punishment
You can eat whichever one you want to
This one's easy, it's the ones later on.
Just relax and eat it.
It will be nice that way.
Just eat it properly
Eat more, go go.
She's going for the second one too.
Okay, I'll take over
Go!
I'm begging you man
please don't throw up!
No matter what man...
Keep going!
Okay, I got this.
Go now!
Go go!
You're doing well!
Right, next!
The only ones left are the...
What the hell!
That's grim!
Okay, go!
Keep going!
Come on, do your best!
They can't clear it!
It's way too sour man!
That was way too sour!
That sourness was ridiculous!
That was ridiculous!
Team Kurobikari
Team Fat Face
So, Team Fat Face have a one point lead, we head to the next round...
Kokontozai Monmari Battle!!
Kokontozai
Monmari Battle!!
*Note: Monmari here refers to the Gaki No Tsukai game where someone's face is planted into another person's butt.
Monmari!
Players
Recreation 2
Kokontozai* Monmari Battle!!
Rule:
A player from each team battles in Kokontozai*
*Note: Kokontozai, also known as the Yamanote Line Game, is a game where a category is given and players come up with answers that go under the category.  When a player cannot come up with an answer that goes under the category, the player loses.
A player from each team competes against each other in Kokontozai
while facing the pressure of Monmari.
Secret Character
Get 4 questions wrong and get a crotch to the face!!
If you get a question wrong
the Monmari machine moves the secret character’s crotch to the face.
Kokontozai
Monmari Battle!!
KABA-chan
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Matsumoto versus KABA-chan
And who are the secret characters?
We have invited these two.  Please come on stage.
You can do it.
Mimata Matazou and Big Daddy!!
Big Daddy
Hayashishita Kiyoshi
Mimata Matazou
What’s the matter?
Just not Mimata, please, I'm asking you.
You don’t know who will get whom yet.
That's right.
I'm not saying Big Daddy would be good.
It’s just that
we know each other, so it's gross.  I really don’t want Mimata.
Why not?  What's the big deal?
Well, Mimata
who do you want, KABA-chan or Matsumoto?
Gotta go with Matsumoto!!
Stop that.
Since he helps me out all the time.
Get him to be nice to you as always.
Monmari Role Mimata Matazou
Player Matsumoto Hitoshi
So the pairs have been decided.
Monmari Role Big Daddy
Player KABA-chan
The category for the two is…
Sushi dishes you can eat at Sushi Zanmai.
Sushi Dishes at Sushi Zanmai*
*Note: Sushi Zanmai is a sushi chain restaurant.
Sushi dishes. Here we go, Monmari battle, start!
You can do it.
Good luck.
Sushi dishes. Here we go, Monmari battle, start!
Sushi Dishes at Sushi Zanmai
Shrimp
The usual things, you know?
Fatty Tuna
That's good.
Shrimp
Sea Urchin
Fatty Tuna
Tuna in Soy Sauce
Sardine
Octopus
Medium Fatty Tuna
Tuna in Soy Sauce
Fatty Tuna
Sea Urchin
Shrimp
Greater Amberjack
Salmon
Squid
Sea Urchin
Shrimp
Greater Amberjack
Salmon
Squid
Sea Urchin
Shrimp
Egg
They have that.
Wow, nice.
Fatty Tuna
Tuna in Soy Sauce
Medium Fatty Tuna
Octopus
Sardine
Salmon Roe
Shrimp
Sea Urchin
Squid
Salmon
Greater Amberjack
Egg
Bloody Clam
That's right.
Fatty Tuna
Tuna in Soy Sauce
Medium Fatty Tuna
Octopus
Sardine
Salmon Roe
Sea Urchin
✕
Matsumoto!
Sea Urchin!
That was already said.
That means that…
It’s hard to hear.
Matsumoto, incorrect.
Monmari
Stop, that's it.
Wow.
Who chose these stages?
Can you just tell me
how many stages I have left?
The next Kokontozai category is
Titles of Japanese Folk Tales
titles of Japanese folk tales
From KABA-chan, start!
Titles of Japanese Folk Tales
Issun-boshi
Momo Taro
Urashima Taro
Hanasaka Jiisan
That's good.
What was that one?
Anything.
Issun-boshi
Urashima Taro
The Tortoise and the Hare
✕
Oh, The Hare and the Tortoise.
It's reversed.
Correctly, it's "The Hare and the Tortoise.”
It’s The Hare and the Tortoise.
You said it reversed.
Monmari, first stage, start!
Monmari
All smiles.  He's suddenly all smiles.
Big Daddy is all smiles.
Because he had a fire*...
*Note: Big Daddy (Hayashishita Kiyoshi)’s home and business was lost in a fire on October 5, 2014.
All right, let’s continue.
Singles by Matsuda Seiko
Next is titles of
single CDs by Matsuda Seiko.
There are a lot.
All right, starting from KABA-chan, start!
Singles by Matsuda Seiko
Blue Coral Reef
Red Sweet Pea
That's good.
Missing You
KABA-chan might have the advantage here.
Uh oh.
There’s a time limit, too.
Pink Mozart
Sweet Memories
Oh, not that...
Oh, that one!  That, that!
Azure Earth
That’s not a single?
That's an album.
How the hell would I know that!!
Since it isn't a single
Matsumoto's Monmari, start!
Monmari
It was an album.
Oh no.
Whoa.
Hold on a second.
Junior, look at this.
The color changes.
Isn’t it slipping out a bit?
It's like an astringent persimmon.
Look straight ahead.
The next category is
Top 10 Overseas Destinations
of Japanese Tourists
the top 10 overseas destinations of Japanese tourists.
All right, starting from KABA-chan, Kokontozai, start!
It's from the sweating.  It's from the sweating.
Top 10 Overseas Destinations
of Japanese Tourists
Hawaii
Guam
Ok.
Hawaii
Korea
Guam
Bali
✕
Bali is not in there.
We can’t help you now!!
Oh, that wasn't correct.
Monmari, start!
Monmari
It stopped.
Stopped by an inch.
You’re just barely OK.
Barely OK.
13th: Indonesia (including Bali)
According to the
Japan Association
of Travel Agents
Matsumoto, it’s not over until it’s over.
All right, let’s continue.
Types of Alcohol
Types of alcohol.
Come on.
From KABA-chan, start!
Types of Alcohol
Sake
Beer
Shochu
Vodka
Sake
Shochu
Gin
Beer
Vodka
Tequila
That's good.
Sake
Shochu
Gin
Rum
Beer
Vodka
Tequila
Barley Shochu
Shochu was already said?
✕
Matsumoto!
Yes!
So, condolences to you.
Uh oh, the Monmari!
Mimata’s Monmari, start!
Monmari
It’s long!!
Sorry.  Really sorry.
Um...
Sorry.
It just smells like poop.
The end!!
Mimata's poop would be the worst.
It goes human ➡ gorilla ➡ dog ➡ Mimata
2PM.
Prison Life   5 Hours and 30 Minutes
There is no rest for the five.
That’s right.
There's a possibility there are new things
in here...
Yes, since we were out for a while.
OK, everyone.
There’s nothing OK here!!
Now, uhh,
Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison has
a surveillance system that can prevent any prison escape.
We're going to go to an experiment of our super-advanced surveillance system.
We're going to have you be guinea pigs  for
the experiment.
What the hell is that?
Who says it so clearly like that?
Then, now...
Let’s go.
OK, let’s go.
Cutting Edge Security System
On to the Experiment Location
Guinea pigs?
He says so clearly that we’re guinea pigs.
"We're going to have you be guinea pigs"?
He says so clearly that we're guinea pigs.
Who would want to go to that?
Absolutely.
Can everyone get on board?
They board the bus to be transported.
Of course, the way there
will not be smooth.
What lies in wait for them beyond?
What Lies in Wait for them Beyond?
The Curtain Rises on a New Act
The curtain rises on a new act.
The five ride a bus
Prison Life    5 Hours and 30 Minutes
that takes them to the prison’s experiment location.
Where is this going?
The experiment location.
The guinea pig thing, right?
Oh, the guinea pig thing.
Geez.
They have things like that even in this day and age?
The human rights here are completely messed up.
You’re gonna say that again?  What Matsumoto said?
I already said that.
Well, I just wanted to once more, since I thought so, too.
The rights of people are just…
You’re just changing it.
You're just trying to say it with more words.
Pahahaha
Endo, why are you looking at me like that?
Well, you were laughing.
I wasn’t laughing.
But you can’t do that.
You can’t just take what someone else said.
The bus arrives at a stop
I just wanted to say, "Yes, that’s true."
Go really hard.
You don’t need to go really hard.
That’s one of those where the sound wasn’t much but it hurt.
I can tell.
My ass, seriously…
We're stopped?
What?
Is something gonna to come?
Oh, yeah.
Hahaha
I don't get it...
Who is this supposed to be?
Climb up properly.
I was wondering who...
Yabuki Kaoru (Asano Atsuko)
Jinnai Tomonori*
*Note: Jinnai Tomonori is a comedian.  He is playing the character of Yabuki Kaoru from the 1991 drama TV show "101st Marriage Proposal."  The actress who played the character of Yabuki Kaori in the actual show is Asano Atsuko.
I couldn’t tell.
Could this be the 101st…
Come on.
You’re kidding me.
Hoshino Tatsurou (Himself)
Takeda Tetsuya*
*Note: Takeda Tetsuya is the actual actor who played the character of Hoshino Tatsurou in the 1991 drama "101st Marriage Proposal."  In the show, Hoshino is the male lead character and Yabuki is the female lead character.  They are doing a parody of a famous scene from the show.
Kaoru!
Seriously?
Come on.
No way, seriously?
Ow, my back.
This isn’t really the kind of place for this, but
will you...
Don’t!!
Kaoru.
Please don’t be around me.
But, but I...
I told you:
101st Marriage Proposal Story
Kaoru is scared of believing in and falling in love with another person
five years ago,
I was forsaken by a man to whom I was engaged to,
and so I swore I wouldn’t fall in love again.
So please don’t be around me.
But that’s why, will you, will you marr—
I’m scared!!
I’m still scared...
I'm afraid of the acting ability of that golf idiot.
Even though it was great that he was chosen as the main actor in that "Bus Jack" movie,
The movie was so bad, it looked like a cheap theater play.
I'm so scared of ham actors like him!
I...
I won't act in a shitty movie like him!!
Even if I only read the script roughly once,
I won't act in a sketchy movie like him!!
I'll somehow someway read the script twice!
Even though the movie is made into DVDs, generally that is good for sales...
But on Amazon's DVD popularity ranking list, he was ranked 40850th.
The highest price you could buy his DVD is for only 31 yen.
I will not star in a shitty movie where you can buy the DVD but not have enough money to even buy water.
Because I like you...
That actually makes
me wanna see the movie...
So it ranked so low huh
Is that even true?
Around 40,000th...
This is shocking...
Tatsuro-san!!
You're willing to do that for me...
That's why I'm asking you to mar...
But I'm afraid!!
As I thought, I'm afraid...
I'm afraid of that tsukkomi gorilla's senility you know.
Every time before we start recording for a show, when he farts...
His shit completely leaks out.
I'm so scared of that depressed gorilla's senility!
Before a shooting, I won't shit myself like that!
Because I like you...
It was just
a little bit of shit.
I heard of another thing as well.
He called his junior, "Durians" over.
Even though his own show is in a competing slot with their show.
He was completely into a show that is on another channel.
He suddenly went and faced Durians earnestly.
It's good that young lads like you could make it.
His eyes got teary and said, "It's bright in here."
What is with that seriousness and sudden sighing state.
I won't be like that big lips gorilla!
That's embarrassing!!
Did you really say that?
But it was really bright.
You really said something amazing.
Tatsuro-san, you're willing to do that for me...
That's why...
BUT I'M AFRAID!!
As I thought, I'm still scared.
I'm scared of that funny muscular idiot.
When a certain disease was featured in a show...
Plus, recently his blood pressure was really high as well.
He was worried that he was infected by that disease.
With great excitement, he went to the hospital and the result was...
"You have too much muscle" was the reason.
I'm scared of the stoicism of that muscular idiot!
I won't build so much muscle and raise my blood pressure like that guy!
Because I like you!!
That's right..
Going to the gym and light jog for 30 mins to warm up his body, then moved on to another exercise.
And when his favorite equipment can't be used...
He gives up.
And went to another gym and jogs lightly for another 30 mins to warm up again.
I won't be like that muscular idiot!
When his junior asked him, "What is the number one thing you want right now?"
He answered earnestly, "I guess..."
"Probably to get just one large sum of money at once"
"Hmmm...?"
"The next thing that I want is more time I guess" was his answer!
I won't be like that Naniwa comedian!
TL Note: Naniwa is the old name of Osaka, so he's basically implying Matsumoto is old. I think.
Scary!
Because I like you...
Scary! He wants money...
I did say that
That's scary!
At least he admits it.
Amazing.
Please.
Tatsuro-san, you're willing to do that for me...
Yes.
That's right! That's why please let me say this one thing.
Please marry me...
BUT I'M SCARED!!
After all, I'm still afraid...
Someone who will fall dead at any time.
I can't marry you because I'm scared of 70-something-year-old grandpas.
He's badmouthing him
YOU IDIOT!!!
Why would you say that kind of thing?
Even though that is the case...
Tasuro-san... I'm so sorry.
You're not getting off?
Are you not getting off?
Seriously?
I want this guy to get off too...
He looks like Sasaki Kojirou.
Really is Sasaki Kojirou.
Sasaki Kojirou lol
Uwaaa!!
That famous scene once more...
Get out of the way, idiot!
I won't die!! I WON'T DIE!!
Because I like you!
I will make you happy!!
Tatsuro-san!!
They are doing this as scene as well...
That was so dangerous!!
It was a really famous scene
That's true.
Ah, that was surprising
A little bit more on the bus trip left
Prison's experimental center is before their own eyes
There's only a little bit more on the bus trip.
The experimental center is approaching closer.
Fujiwara-san, come on...
Let's just get there without stopping.
We're about to arrive, guys.
Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison
Surveillance System Experimental Center
Uwaaah, is this for real?
The view is really nice.
Come on guys, we've reached our stop. Let's go.
You gotta be kidding me
You gotta be kidding me.
This is Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison's...
You can't run away at all.
This is our first Surveillance System Experimental Center.
There's a long and round track there.
I see it.
Uwah, that is huge.
There it is.
Experiment center's waiting room
Before your experiment, you have to change.
We have to exchange into this.
Before the surveillance experiment
Change into clothes that is easy to move
Before the experiment, they will change into clothes that doesn't restrict their movements.
In order to test to see if they can break out,
What is this latest surveillance system experiment?
they will be the subject of this new surveillance system.
Guys, are you ready?
Then, let me show you around what is this Surveillance Experiment is all about.
So, we're experiments, huh?
I feel like doing stretches in this occasion.
In the middle of an experiment.
SO WIDE!!
Exercise field
So huge.
This is bad.
This is...
Seriously...
Is this for real?
Okay, everyone.
This is the experiment that you will be doing!!
So, it's here. This year as well.
This place is too huge for this.
For now, it's okay to laugh but
During surveillance, oni will be around
When you're caught, you will get punished, okay?
You can't just punish someone when you caught them!!
Also, I thought just having you guys doing it would be too ugly so I called someone.
I called a really big star over. It's this person.
Really?
Him? Really?
Helper
Toshihiko Tahara
I see.
How are youuu!!
Happy Merry Christmas!
[T/N: He is making a joke by instead of saying Hacchi (eight) he said Happy Merry Christmas. ]
What is he even saying.
And a Happy New Year!
You can bombed a joke this amazingly huh!
So loud. His voice echoed everywhere.
He failed so bad though!
Toshi-chan is amazing.
Everyone, are you ready?
First of all, one of you will be lock inside that transparent room.
And the other 5 people, in order to rescue that person
Pfft... Sorry.
What was so funny?
This area...
So cute.
Is that cute?
Oh, he's went there.
Excuse me.
How long are you gonna keep doing that!
This is weird!!
This is seriously weird!!
An oni is already out!!
It's better for the TV staffs if this person is not caught.
3 oni will come out at the same time at the beginning.
Surveillance Experiment
At the start, 3 oni will make an appearance at the same time
And after 10 minutes, more and more will come out.
Oni will increase after every 10 minutes
Someone will be trapped in the transparent room and the other will have to find the key.
Surveillance Experiment
Find the real key and rescue their friend
If they manage to rescue their friend, the experiment is a success.
I will announce who is the person that will be locked in that room.
Matsumoto! It's you!
It's true, I just recently injured my ribs.
Because my sides hurt, really
Since your sides are hurting
My sides hurt
Really!?
It's not hurting
No no no, really, it's true
What the hell is this person doing!? Seriously!!
I really hate this!!
I hate Tahara Toshihiko!!
That was pretty good
But if the key is wrong
and you try to open the door
right there and then, there will be a
harsh punishment for Matsumoto
If the key is wrong, a punishment for Matsumoto
Surveillance Experiment
Everyone, use the real key to rescue him
Are you serious?
Well well, let's just do our best
Until he is rescued, he cannot go outside
Do Not Get Caught Prison Escape
And now the experiment...
Starts!
Surveillance System Experiment Begins
Slipper
What is it?!
What?!
Ooohh!!
Alright alright ok ok ok!!
Already? Really?
That's gotta hurt
Ow...
Ow ow ow ow ow
That one sucks
Looks like a disaster
Fu hahahahaha
Second oni's entrance
One just came out! Are there supposed to be this many?
It's not over?
Paper Fan
Wait!!
That's dangerous!
Two of them
Fu hahahahahahaha
You are all full of energy!!
a nonchalant Matsumoto, on his own
Watching and observing from afar
This is the worst
They just keep coming!
What does that one say?
Ass Bat!!
Ass bat!
Ass Bat
Oh he's pretty fast!
Get Toshi-chan!
Toshi-chan runs really fast!!
Toshi-chan is going to get caught
Toshi-chan, you're going to get caught!
Catch Toshi-chan!!
Yes!! Toshi-chan got caught!
Tahara-san...
Toshi-chan's getting it!
That was a full swing
Ow, that hurt!!
Toshi-chan got a
full swing to the ass
That was awful!
Toshi-chan
That slipper hurt like hell!!
You did indeed say that
That was a full swing
That hurt!
Let's go search for that thing
with the key
Yeah really, let's search
He's here, hey, he's here!
It's Ass Bat!!
Ass Bat
Ass Bat is here!
This right here...
Hosei hiding behind Hamada
That's just the angle!
Wait wait wait
See?
Ah...
Damnit, you scared me!
That was so scary just then
Ah, it's Toshi-chan again
The oni is locked on
He's not going to get away
Tanaka, stop him!!
Stop Toshi-chan!!
Toshi-chan, not this way
Toshi-chan, he's going straight for you!
He doesn't have the energy
He's completely honed in on you!!
Why only me?
Eh!? Not me, wait a minute
Captures Hosei for some reason
Don't abandon your choice!
Don't give up!!
Too soft
Alright alright alright
That was too soft
I was completely dragged into that situation
Punishment hell
The 5 of them don't have any time to spare
Where should I go?
I have no idea where the key is
Ass Bat
Nooo wait a minute, just wait!
Oh, it's Hamada
The Ass Bat got him
Hamada in pain and
Alright alright
A delighted evil Tanaka
They caught me doing that
Paper Fan
What do you mean, "Alright alright"
You didn't even try to run away
It's because you were enjoying me getting hit
Surveillance Experiment 10 minutes has passed
This was extremely long
Additional Onis are released
It really was
Hosei, searching for the key by himself
?
Uehhh!! Ehhh!!
What!? Hold on a second!!
Wait!! What is this!?
Hold on!!
Ahhh!!
What the hell is this!
Wait
Giant shackles 150cm in diameter
What's going on?!
Shackles
Oh come one! Give me a break!!
What is that!? That!! What is that!?
What was that just now?
What a nuisance!!
You're so easy to find now!!
Easy to find...
This thing is too huge!!
Hey Endo...
It's impossible with that...
No, Hosei, no way
What the hell is this
Slipper
He's making use of the sphere
That's no good!
I hate that one the most
This is hell
5 of them search the building interior
Over here, this path here
Since there's a bunch of doors
Let's go
You can't enter here
I can
Can you go through?
Yes
Just right!!
So noisy
The 3 search the hallway
Go, go look inside
I wonder if the oni are gonna come
If I do this, I can get all of them at once right now
If the oni come from that side
Ehh, really on this floor though?
Slipper
Endo abandons Hamada
It was like that, huh
Hey you!!
Don't mess with me!!
What kind of face is that!!
Hold on hold on hold on
Ass Bat
This guy is the worst!!
Hosei betrays his comrades
No, don't you dare double up
You can't double up!
You can't double up!!
Don't double up!
Oni!! Look!! Over there!!
There's another person over there
You!!
Get out of the damn way!!
Please
Wait, please!!
No no, this guy is the worst
Seriously, it's all Yamasaki
It was a double!! Double!!
Immediately aiming for Hosei is
Ass Bat
In the end, you get hit anyway
AHHH HAHHHHH!!
AHHHH HAHHHH!!
You were also running for your life
Huh?
"You can't double up, you can't double up"
That black thing is still attached to him
You're really an awful person
Watch out watch out watch out
Why are you doing this!?
This is dangerous!
What the hell is wrong with you!!
What's wrong?
What is going on, Yamasaki?
If you don't move this out of the way...
It'll be your fault that we...
Don't give me, "Move this out of the way"!!
It's your fault
I got hit with a double over here!!
No you didn't!!
Yeah I did!
I got hit too!!
I've had enough of all of you!!
Paper Fan
WAHHHHHHHHH!!
Of course that would happen
Of course that'd happen just like that
See? See?
Toshi-chan all by himself
Are those guys trying to plan something?
Those guys leave me by myself too much
He doesn't come with us
You definitely see the truth in people. Like Yamasaki and Tanaka
You're right
you both have despicable natures
Well, if you say that, it applies to everyone
Ah!! Ahhh!!
Isn't that the key!? The key!!
Should we wait for Toshi-chan?
It's a treasure box
Toshi, we found it, it's right here!
Wait for me!!
I'll check it!!
Discovered a treasure box
Okay
With this, we can release...
Oh!
It's a key
Then let's open the door, let's go
Yes
That's amazing
Let's go rescue him
Um, Yamasaki, you're in the way
You're exactly right
That's only going to lure them in
You're doing that pretty cleverly
To Matsumoto who has been waiting
So damn noisy
Hurry up
Yes
Open it please!!
If we can open it, it'll be over
It doesn't fit?
It doesn't fit
It's too big
It doesn't fit?
The shape is different
Commence Matsumoto's punishment
Who is it?
Is it that person?
Ah, it's Obachan
It's Obachan
She's shaking her hips
She's shaking it
Note: Song is Emmanuelle (French Version) by Pierre Bachelet
Man...
TG
She started with the forehead
So gentle...
She's so kind!
She didn't go for the mouth or anything
We're sorry
I'm sorry!!
Come on guys seriously, get your shit together
We had to try
Doing this loads of time is too tough
Like seriously, I'm begging you, hurry...
I understand
Do you not think we can try
that key one more time guys?
Do you not think we can try that key one more time guys?
Don't say shit like that!!
Maybe...
We'll try the other way.
Leave it out!
Tanaka, just stick it in anyway.
Wait, what?...
Really, you come now?
ONI arrives, not reading the atmosphere at all
You're kidding me...
What bad timing Tanaka, eh?
I know, this timing is just...
Man this takes a while...
Of course it's going to take time
Tanaka, let's try opening the door with that key again
We can't do anything obviously if it's wrong but...
Maybe Toshi-chan put the key in the wrong way, you never know...
There's no way...
Go!
I know it made the wrong sound now as well...
but it was wrong before as well...
so don't use the same key
again and again...
You guys just did it before...
You knew it was going to be wrong...
Yeah, so of course I knew it was going to be wrong
Wow shit, she's already here
She went for it
It's the scent which really gets you
The mouth soon...
Of course, of course
He's closed his eyes and all guys!
He's left it all up to the Obachan...
Look at him...
Don't fucking use
the same key again and again!!
I can't hear what he's saying, can you?
30 Minutes have past in the experiment
We are now increasing the numbers of Onis...
Tanaka-kun!!
Quick! Please, come, come with me.
Daddy Endo
What the hell are you doing?
Hold on, father, sir...
Is this normal?...
Father, sir, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I'm playng Onigokko (Tag)
It's fine, it's fine.
Wait, what?
Hey guys, it's Tanaka-kun!!
Endo Family takes him in
Endo Family
Just please, wait, hold on a second.
What exactly are the Endo family doing here?
(Endo Father) Tanaka kun
(Endo Father) thank you for
(Endo Father) taking care of Shozo all the time.
No no, he always takes care of me and all too so...
You got a stiff neck so I will massage you.
(Endo Father) It's been ages since
(Endo Father) you debuted with Shozo as a combo
Yeah you're right, it's 22 years now
(Endo Father) Thank you for always looking after him
no problem
(Endo Mother) And you
(Endo Mother) are working with Uchimura-kun
(Endo Mother) and Okamura-san
(Endo Mother) and you're on lots of TV shows
(Endo Mother) you seem to be earning a hell of a lot at the moment, huh?
Mother jealous of his success
No, I'm really not
But you look like you're earning loads
(Endo Mother) So please sort out Shouzou as well please...
(Endo Mother) Please please
(Endo Mother) take care of Shouzou as well.
Come here you piece of...
The father suddenly gets angry
Endo family's pro wrestling move
Give up?
I give up!!!
YOSHAAAAAA (COME ON!!)
Endo family defeat Tanaka
What the hell man!!
(Endo Father) Okay, so take care of Shouzou.
Okay, well anyway... Take care...
Meanwhile, the other 4...
I've found something I could use
Hold on, I might be able to use this to my advantage...
Slipper
What!?
No
Please no!!
What?
Oh my god, it's off!!
I'm so happy!
He was a real good guy!!
Hosei-san's been freed from his shackles
Yeah!!
For real?
Yes
What the hell are you mumbling?
Emmanuelle.
Oh I see
Obachan prepares herself next door
Endo, I got it off
I'm happy for you
How?
The Oni
took it off for you?
There's an Oni who will take it off for you
A genuinely good guy
I see
For real?
Wait, where did Tanaka go?
Tanaka is having things done to him in one of the rooms
For real?
They run to the building to find Tanaka
Toshi-chan said
Tanaka is screaming in one of the rooms...
Oh, no no...
You're okay?
It wasn't me
Oh right...
Yup...
Tanaka casually lies
He's such a bastard, right?
I can't fully understand what has just happened in all honesty
Toshi-chan alone... again
Man I'm thirsty...
Matsumoto's having tea, he's so lucky...
You got tea?
I didn't have anything to do
You really love this song.
Hum a different tune!
You're loving it!
Like really getting into it
I haven't seen Tanaka...
He was trapped in one the rooms
Tanaka was over there.
When?
Just now
For real?
He was definitely here before
Look look look
Where were you? We were looking for you for ages
Sorry, I was looking for the key!
You were looking for the key?
Yes, I was looking for it
That's fine, that's fine
That's fine that's fine
Hamada-san
WOW!!
Daddy Endo
Can I just borrow you for a bit?...
Welcome, welcome
Hamada falls for his trap
This way, welcome
Ummm... okay
Tanaka's fucking face
Evil Tanaka laughs at Hamada's misfortune
Endo family
Hey, it's Hamada-san!
He's always been good to us
Oh, hello there
You've taken good care of us
Please, please sit down
Umm, yes
(Endo Mother) Thank you for always taking care of us
Thank you for taking care of our son all the time
No no no, it's not a problem at all
(Endo Father) You've been good to him for over 20 years now so thank you so much...
No no no, not a problem
Your muscles are tight so I'm going
No no, I'm totally fine
today is a tough day for you too
No no, father, sir, it's fine
I've never given a massage so this is the best I can do...
No no, that's great
Does it feel good?
(Endo Mother) Hamada-san
I've heard you're quite
close with Nan-chan
and I have a little request...
Oh, yes, umm okay...
Shouzou is on the TV program 'Hirunandesu' ...
Oh yes, I know..
But he told me that Nan-chan isn't that nice to him...
Endo's mother is concerned about her son's slow advancement in his career
and I've been really concerned about everything...
Oh, really?...
Could you get in a good word...
with Nan-chan for him?
No no, umm...
They are really friendly with one another
They are doing their job fine together
Are they really?...
Yes yes
Endo Shouzou
our first son
please take care of him
The Dad freaks out again
What the fuck are you doing!!
What the hell, what's going on?!
What the hell is wrong with this family!!
YEEEAAAHHH!!!
YEAAAHHH!!!
Endo family get revenge for their son
BANZAAIII!!!
What the hell, man...
I'm fine..
What the hell, seriously...
Hold on a moment..
what the hell, man!
Your bloody family!...
Y-... You framed me.
Tanaka...
Wait, what, what? I'm lost...
Apparently he was in the building screaming before...
according to Toshi-chan... that's what the screaming was all about, right?
Yup!
Tanaka was getting his arse handed to before.
He's trying to play dumb
You were with the Endos, right?
Why would you say all of this?..
Are you saying you weren't?
I mean... I was but...
Please don't say it...
Enough of that, let's find the key!
Yeah, let's find the key
Meanwhile, at the Endos
As expected, Hamada-san is easy to talk to, huh?
He's such a nice guy
He's so respectful
You fucking kidding me?
You’re kidding me.
(Endo Father) He’s genuine.
(Endo Father) We're done.
That was dangerous to record on tape.
What are they doing?
Leave them chatting there
and you don't know what
they're going to
say about you.
(Endo Father) Great job all!!
The key.
Treasure box found
I found something that has to with the key.
The five find a new key
and go back to Matsumoto.
We’ve come to save you!!
Hurry, hurry!!
This’ll work.
Oh, this way.
It looks wrong from the beginning.
Come on.
At least it goes in, right?
This definitely won’t go in.
It's wrong.
The last one was already too large.
I guess it’s no good.
Seriously?
No good.
There's more of this.
This was quite long, too.
It's getting to this stage, now.
She licked…
She’s saying, “Caress me.”
She licked my nose...
Will you hurry up!!  Seriously!!
50 minutes after the start
The shadow of an oni sneaks up from behind
From behind the five...
the shadow of an oni...
I couldn’t tell at all.
What, what?
Hamada: “Hattoshite! Good”*
*Note: “Hattoshite! Good" (Gasp! and then Good) is a 1980 pop song by Tahara Toshihiko.
What do you want?
What’s going on?
What is that?
What do you want?
A hat* with a massive load of firecrackers
*Note: The Japanese transliteration of the English word "hat" is "hatto."  Tahara's song title "Hattoshite! Good" thus becomes a pun, meaning "Put on a hat! Good."
That was the sound.
This was crazy.
Wait, what is this!!
Stay still!!
*Note: The music playing in the background is from “Hattoshite! Good.”
This was done under the guidance of a professional
This is bad.
Your voice is gone.
Your voice is gone.  Your voice.
The surveillance experiment has passed 60 minutes.
Further onis are added
Onis will be increased.
It’s gotta be somewhere.
It has to be, or else it’d be silly.
What is it?
There’s one there.
“Danger."For positionnnnnnnnnnn
It says "Danger."
Danger
Stop, stop, seriously no.
Seriously, no.
Stop!!
I don't want this.
That's really scary.
It says “Danger”!!
Really scary.
It says “Danger.”
It’s the first time they’re being so clear about it.
Tanaka got cau—ght!
“Danger” has gotta be a bad one.
How is it dangerous?
Yama-chan, you’re pissing me off.
You’re always betraying people.  That’s why this is happening to you.
That is right.
You’re always betraying people, that’s why you’re getting punished.
“Danger.  Do not enter,” it says.
There’s no way this’ll turn out well.
What’s gonna happen?
The hood?
No way.
You’re kidding.
That’s why it says “Danger.”
Hold on a second.  Hold on...
This is a joke, right?
I mean, this isn’t ready-made equipment.
Right.
It’s an original.  The staff just made it themselves.
Pahaha.  I'm scared.
Whoa!!  Seriously?
I’m sorry!!
What do you mean “I’m sorry”?
I apologize!!
The ground shuddered.
That freaked me out.
This was done under the guidance of a professional
Tanaka?
He’s crying!!
You can’t even tell what the color of his face is.
Was it that scary?
He’s crying!!
I apologize for everything before.
You were acting like an ass, that’s why you got what was coming, you see?
This is messed up!!
It’s Fujiwara.
There's no key anywhere.
There's no key.
About the key that everyone's looking for,
it was in my… my pocket the whole time.
What was that?
He stuttered.
And that’s where you stutter?
Let’s go, then.
What were we here for?
Answer Toshi-chan.
There was a huge explosion.
Hurry.  Hurry.
Experiment Complete
It opened, it opened.  It opened!
Everyone, there’s still a lot to do.
Don’t say that, geez.
After the shock of the experiment,
the five return to the prison.
Okay, everyone.  For now, wait here again.
Something’s written there.
The contents
of the drawers
have all
been reset
The terror of the desk drawer pranks, again
Give us a break.  We already did that so much.
Whatever.
Well, yeah, every time it’s like this.
Are we required to give in to this?
We have to open them at some point, right?
Should we go from here?
Starting from Endo this time
I’m going to go, OK?
Starting with Shozo.
Yes.  Here I go.
Let’s go.
There it is, right from the get-go!!
There it is.
A Mystery Envelope
Oh, there it is.
This, oh, geez.  What is this?
We’ve seen this kind of thing before.
“We know everything,” it says.
Whoa, whoa, I’m just
What!?
I seriously hate these envelopes.  Seriously, I…
2 years ago, this envelope led to the exposure of a secret date between Endo and a woman
This, really—Endo has said that recently there’s seriously been nothing happening—is what I’ve been told.
There’s seriously nothing happening.
So if there actually was something going on, I really just can't like you as a person anymore.
I have nothing like that.
Nothing.
Seriously, nothing.
Ser…iously nothing.
If you’re confident, then…
...then you're innocent.
May I?
“We know everything.”
Whoa!!
Seriously!?  This!
Endo Shozo’s Drawer
Weekly Photo Magazine
MONDAY
The Scoop in
the Hidden Pages
Finally Captured!!
Endo Spends a Night at his Hometown of Osaka and his Partner Unbelievably is _____!!
It’s exactly the same as before.
Endo spends a night at his hometown of Osaka, and his partner unbelievably is…
Whoa!!
It’s Osaka, man.
Hey!!  Endo.
Whoa!!
Hold on a secooond!!
This is bad.
Ah—ha.
He’s laughing!!
Sorry, I was laughing again.
Look, he’s laughing.
I trust you, OK?
Endo, there’s no problem here, right?
What do we do, what do we do.
This is a really big deal!!
It says Osaka.
Nope, nope, nope, nope.
Endo Shozo’s Drawer
Weekly Photo Magazine
MONDAY
The Scoop in
the Hidden Pages
Finally Captured!!
Endo Spends a Night at his Hometown of Osaka and his Partner Unbelievably is _____!!
No, Osaka, see…
Your reaction there is already strange, you know?
If there really was nothing,
you’d just be like, “Wha—?”
No, there’s nothing.
First of all, you have been going to Osaka recently, right?
Endo goes to Osaka once a week for his regular spot on a news and information TV show
But I mean getting meals together—and I don't mean with just one other person—
but I do go with the staff for that.
He's crumbling bit by bit.
Meals?  It's not about meals...
The staff.  With the staff…
Is there a woman on the staff?
Are there any women among the staff?
Are thereany women among the staff?
There are like the local announcers and like...
Endo Shozo's Drawer
Weekly Photo Magazine
MONDAY
The Scoop in
the Hidden Pages
Finally Captured!!
Endo Spends a Night at his Hometown of Osaka and his Partner Unbelievably is _____!!
I'm seriously traumatized by this...
It's sealed up so let's open it anyway.
I hate this bloody Monnday magazine...
It's the annual Monnday after all...
Monnday?...
It's Monday...
You're kidding me...
Please tell me you're kidding...
It does say Monday...
What the hell is Monnday?
It was never going to be called
Monnday!
They have a magazine called Friday (Gossip magazine in Japan is called Friday)
I bloody said 'The Annual Monnday'
So embarassing!
I know, Hosei-san is just as guilty!
I'm so embarassed!
It was never going to be called Monnday!
I'm so embarassed...
You are just, seriously, I am sick of you Endo!
KIEEEEEEEEEEEE!!
Like that kind of...
Stop making
those kind of sonuds
What the hell is  KIEEE?
Don't repeat it!!
Yeah man, seriously
I really am scared at the moment!
You don't need to repeat it though!
IEEEE man...
I'm begging you!!
Ohhh man, just that event from 2 years ago...
that really traumatized me
2 years ago MONDAY magazine
Endo's secret conversation with a girl was published
Man, you're so bloody loud...
What was 'this' again?
Oh...
Wait, what was it again?
I don't remember it at all to be honest...
OGO!!
What the hell...
I don't remember it at all...
I was safe there, surely?!
I hate this!!
That OGO sound just killed me...
I'm surprised you remembered that!
Even I didn't remember that.
I will never be able to forget that
Oh shit man...
You didn't do anything though right?
I didn't do anything
Just open the first page
Then we will know more
This doesn't have anything to do with your story...
That's something else...
What?!
What is this?
Endo Shouzou's drawer
Weekly photo magazine MONDAY
Endo 'That night in Osaka'
with THAT person
at their secret location!!
Yoshimoto agency's Wakki reveals
In this edition
lots of photos
and evidence!
Yoshimoto's comedian Wakki reveals...
Wakki did?!
Everything from that night in Osaka...
Everything that night in Osaka...
Endo was with a beautiful woman in Osaka that night...
Revealed!
beautiful woman in Osaka
Endo spends night with
A beautiful woman??
Are you serious?
There's no escape route now...
Wakki really did that?
Can we open it?.. I guess we have to now...
Yeah, you have no choice, there's a pen knife there for you as well.
You didn't do anything right?..
Monnday got you
real good.
Monnday...
Monnday?
I've cut it open
Wow you're good at that
Here I go...
Photo magazine MONDAY
Endo Shozo's drawer
BIG SCOOP!
Endo Toshihide and
his wife Kiyomi
On a Yakiniku Date
It's just your bloody Mum and Dad!!
I'm just in disbelief
We are both Endo's I guess but...
A late night Yakiniku (grilled meat)  date apparently
Wait, what the hell is this?
Super exclusive. Endo Toshihide and his wife Kiyomi's Yakiniku date.
Hehehe
So my Mum and Dad were...
You could totally imagine them like this
You're right, you can imagine them.
But I'm kind of happy...
Yeah, me too.
Well yeah, seriously I haven't...
I have seriously done nothing wrong!
Yeah I know, right?
I thought Endo's Dad was
cheating on your Mum or something...
This is your Mum right?...
Yes yes, that's my Mum
Both father and son...
Yeah if we both did that kind of thing...
That would just be ridiculous
You're just normally laughing...
Nothing you can do...
I'm so happy though...
Yeah, seriously..
I'm relieved
I'm relieved as well...
I can trust you again.
That's great.
That was like a gun salute
You're right.
Like seriously man, seriously..
I'm so happy...
This is not me, not me.
I was about to lose faith in humanity there.
It's just about Mum and Dad...
Okay, I'm going to open mine up...
Huh, why did it do that?...
Can you not even bloody open a drawer normally?...
No no, it's just...
They're made so you can open them easily...
There it is, another locker key
Mysterious Key (Number 7)
Locker...
Oh just one
Oh, it's the locker there...
Number 7
Locker Number 7
Let's go for it!
Over there
This is a bit big, no?
Yeah, it's pretty big.
Hold on!
It's back again!
I knew it...
2nd face art of Hamada
He actually does this face...
This is a different expression from before!
Face Art 1
Face Art 2
It's got a totally new expression.
This one isn't smiling like before.
He does that face from time to time...
Yup.
He does do that face...
Like when it really stinks
That's just amazing
Okay, we are done here.
If we're doing it in order...
Tanaka, can you just turn it the other way?...
Yeah, please do...
I wonder who  made that?
What would you do if that
was created like 20 years or something?
so the real thing's face just keeps heading towards that direction
so the real thing's face just keeps
heading towards that direction
He screwed up!
Something's there
What is that?
There's something there...
A warning?...
Perhaps...
A mysterious envelope
Okay I am all done
So this envelope...
This is the question...
There's a question I think
No, it's not.
No, it says
OK on it
I just saw, it says OK
The 'For ten minutes, I can laugh' card
Rule
10 minutes
OK to laugh Card
The person who holds this card
can laugh for 10 minutes
The 'For ten minutes, I can laugh' card...
If I use this card, only I can
laugh for 10 minutes
When you choose to use it, you have 10 minutes
where you can laugh without punishment
When you want to use this card, you must state that you want to use this card.
What the hell is this?
What does that mean?
I see..
So from the moment you state you're using the card...
So whenever he chooses to, he can laugh for 10 minutes..
That's such a good card
Well yeah, it's awesome.
You can just act totally normal
You don't need it yet, to use it?
Well we're not really in that bad a situation.
That is so awesome.
You're so lucky...
Okay Yama-chan
Yama-chan has one too...
There's similar envelope in his drawer too
Mysterious envelope
You guys have lucky drawers...
What the hell is this, man?
I'm lucky this time...
AH!
What??
I got another Notebook
Secret Escape book- Number 2
It says Part 2
Nothing here... Nope!
I'm going to open the card first then
10 minutes casual chat card
Rule
10 minutes
casual chat card
The person who holds this card
can chat casually for 10 minutes
The person who uses this card can for 10 minutes...
speak casually.
I see...
It's like before...
You need to think when to use it
That's good
That's cool.
Let's open the book last
You're right.
Tanaka, you go.
He might have something like you guys too...
Oh man, there's another one
There it is...
One mysterious DVD
Again?
I did think there would be more to be honest.
Every year there are 2 DVD's to be fair...
So you probably won't have anything
in the other drawers right?
Yeah probably
Tanaka just has a DVD probably...
AH!!
Wait, what, you're kidding me!
Mysterious envelope
I had one too
So far, there's been a 'Okay to laugh' and 'Okay to speak casually'...
What else is there?...
What's the next card going to be?
That's so unfair...
I will open it now!!
We'll watch the DVD later
Punishment...
It's a 'Let off from punishment' card!
Rule
Punishment
Let off card
The person who holds this card
can be let off from being punished
That's such a good card!
That's the best card!
If this card is used, only the person holding the card
can be let off from being punished. When you want to use the card
you must state that you will use the card.
That is just so good!
This is amazing
So you're protected from Thai Kicks and stuff...
Why not my draw....
You're right!
This is a reallylucky card to have
My card is not eventhat good after all...
My card is not even that good after all...
But that is also an awesome card
But I don't know when it's good to use it though!
Like I don't know when it's best to use it
You'll be able to decide that though
I don't really like get the point of this card
I don't really likeget the point of this card
I don't understandat all
I'm going to use it!!
You're speaking casually to me right now!
I would like to activate the '10 minutes casual chat'
card as of now!!
Announcer
As of now, you are okay to speak casually for 10 minutes
The 10 minutes 'casual chat' card has been activated
As of now
you are okay to speak casually
for 10 minutes
10 minutes casual chat
Well it's only really useful when speaking to Downtown
Hosei casual chat card activated
You speak casually
to the Coccorico's anyway
You're right
That doesn't change
Yeah I know that...
Shall we open the how to escape notebook now?
WHY THE HELL!!?
casual chat doesn't mean like...
you can attack us or something, you know?
Questioning is a bit different to that...
Oh, is it?
Like 'WHY THE HELL' is just...
That's wrong
That's just weird, we didn't say anything funny or strange
You can say like 'Oh yeah, you're right'
Yeah man, exactly.
Oh, so I should talk to you like...
I should just talk to you like
when I talk to the Cocoricos, yeah?
Just like normal casual...
You'd prefer to watch the DVD
last right?
so let's open the  how to escape Notebook first...
I see...
You're right there...
Shall we go for it?
Maybe, yeah...
Do you mind if I have a cheeky peek, yeah?
This is just a huge problem for me and Hamada...
There's just an uncomfortable feeling right now.
You're right...
That uncomfortable feeling's going to make us laugh...
Hey
It went in just now
It went in
He was doing the "guts pose" just now
Yes
Seriously?
That's annoying
We won't watch
Why not?
What do you mean why not?
Just go look
That should be safe!
This is unfair to Downtown
This is unfair to Downtown!
Yes I agree
Definitely!
That is uncomfortable
Why are you high-fiving ?
A high-five is very cruel
A high five isn't good
They did a high-five
Why?
When your elders were getting beaten, you did a high-five
Those kinds of things happen sometimes
Hey, read this
Secret Prison escape note
To whoever picked up the note,
this took ten years for me to complete.
To show the secret path to the outside of the prison.
To whoever picked up the note, quickly use the secret path to escape from the prison.
Look, it's the same as before
The King of Escaped Prisoners in Heisei
It said this before
It had it
Ah, yes it did
It's the same place
Oh, then it's right there
Map of the Room
Secret Prison escape note
Open this door to
reach secret passage
Let's go
Please lead us
But, the first time we went
there was nothing there
We went there
and stayed there
We'll go anyway
Not THERE!
That's not it
That hurt
Of course it's not there
For one second, I thought "oh it might be there"
That's what you did before
Same as before
Please stop
It's not that one
That really huuurts
Okay, okay
It was there
Yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes
It's the same
That led to the bathroom
It might have changed
It really might have changed
Wait for me
Whoa!
Oh, again!
Again
It's here
Wait
It's a good one
What!?
A baby and a letter are...
What?!
THIS IS TERRIBLE!!
It changed
THIS IS TERRIBLE!!!
Tanaka, you should go check on him
Wait,
Is he calling us?
Is he coming back?
Hey!!
You aren't gonna believe this
What what what?
A baby...
A baby!!
A letter
The face looks like Hosei-san's face
It does kind of look similar
They look similar
Hold the baby
Will do
Do it properly
Oh sorry sorry sorry
Oh, like that
Oh, a totally different reaction
The baby cheers up when Hosei holds it ❤
Of course!
It likes Hosei-san
Why don't you hold it?
Can I hold it?
Yeah sure, but
the neck is still... you know
Ahh yes yes yes
What a shaky head
Thank you for letting me hold it
It's crying
No no no...
Matsumoto still has a
young child
so
It's crying it's crying
Ah it cried
It's okay, it's alright
That's amazing
The baby definitely feels better with Hosei ❤
Do you have a tissue?
Yes
Tissue, tissue
Tissue
Ah I found one here
Its nose is running
How cute
Isn't it laughing too much?
It shouldn't be laughing so much
Hold it
Even if it is cute...
Use that tissue
Ouch
Ah it's crying a lot
No no no no
It's crying
Boob
Boob boob
Nope...
Nope, nope...
Here
Alright
Matsumoto san, what's written in the letter?
Wait, just leave it because it's already too loud
Yeah, let's just put it down
Hey you, that's enough
Stop treating it like it's a real baby
Seriously just put it down!!
You treat it like it's real
Whatever, it's fine
Happy, happy!
How cute, what a happy baby
Let's see
A letter from mother
To kind-hearted you,
Please take care of this child for a while.
He is a boy.
Please name him and treat him lovingly.
I want to name him...
Akio.
Akio?
Akio
Why did you choose that name?
That's my dad's name
You REALLY named the baby after your father?
I was already thinking to name him that
You were already thinking that?
Yeah, if I had a son next
Is Akio alright?
It might make Hosei's father bless him
Yes
The baby is named Akiob now
It's not Tameguchi at all
Announcement
Tameguchi OK ends in
5 seconds
Is it okay?
4...
Hey, watch watch
3...
2...
Quickly, WATCH!!
1...
0.
ZERO
Please watch
I already saw it anyway
It's impossible
This really makes me mad
That really gets me
That gets me
Alright
He really does look like you
You've got a really big burden
Right, he really looks like him...
He looks like Hosei-san's child
Wait, he looks like he's happy
Yes
Isn't this in the way?
It should be okay
Isn't this Tanaka's
last DVD?
DVD
It seems like you guys found a baby
Exactly!
Yes
I'll take him up!!
Please, just...
It's safer that way
Take him up well, alright
He seems really upset
Tell him to "name him and treat him lovingly"
I will take him up
His name is Akio-chan. We named him.
He's safer that way though
You're right, it is noisy here
We'll do it that way.
So much happens here
It's unbelievable, a baby
DVD
Shall we?
That's all that's left, right?
In the worst case, you can use that card, so...
Right!
So you'll be totally fine
The DVD isn't scary at all
The part that makes me hesitant
Yeah
Nothing is scary, but...
Mmm, sure
Now, we resume Gaki-Culture. We will talk about the Ice Bucket Challenge.
We got the scoop on the worldwide phenomenon.
Various famous people gathered together and
the Ice Bucket Challenge boomed worldwide.
The boom began with celebrities
and spread to ordinary people.
And now,
a new challenge is beginning to spread worldwide.
And that challenge is...
I've never seen a challenge that amazing!
Even in my country,
everybody is talking about it.
The Ice Thai Kick Challenge!
Yes, Ice Thai Kick Challenge!
This worldwide challenge began in Italy,
then spread to Germany,
then Spain,
right now, this Thai man
is travelling the world
and is kicking 4,674 ordinary peoples' butts.
And now, he has arrived in Japan
his target is...
Wait, wait! What are you doing?!
What are you doing!?
This challenge, like the Ice Bucket Challenge,
will connect the last victim to the next.
So, Yaku will now nominate...
Who next to kick?
What are you saying?
The comedian Tsukitei Hosei
YOU'RE KIDDING!!!
YOU'RE KIDDING!!
Hosei, Ice Thai Kick Challenge
WAIT!!!
IT SHOULD BE TANAKA!!
Wow, this is...
You're kidding!!!
Here he is, here he is
Oh come on
Even if you say that...
Are you serious!?
Shouldn't it be Tanaka?
Hold on, Yama-chan
Don't move
Yama-chan, you need to keep still
Hosei-san
You have to stay still for this
Stay still
Note: He says this in a very thick Thai accent
Stay still!
Ice Thai Kick!
First is the ice
Here goes the ice
AHHHH!!
Next, who are you going to nominate?
Who are you doing to nominate?
HAMADAAAA!!
I never thought he'd choose me
This has nothing to do with ice
Ahhh!!
I don't like this
I shouldn't have looked at him directly
This is hell, this is pure hell
Man, it's hot in here
This is hell
It lingers long after, you know
You are right
See, this is what happens
Yes, it turns out like this
It's a Thai Kick after all
Did you see that?
Hamada's face, after he got kicked
That was scary
Are you okay?
So much pain... It's been so long since the last time
But really, this, it's what this is
It's this face, this expression
This was a prediction
It was a prediction!!
Completely the same expression
That's just too much
That's the exact same expression
But but, you know
If Hosei didn't challenge Hamada, then this wouldn't have happened
You can't do that
That's right!
Because it wasn't pre-determined!!
Terrifying!!
Please, just give me a break...
I even thought, "Oh God!"
Why wasn't it Tanaka?
Wow, I was spared
The one looking this way was Hamada
It's not like I was trying to look your way
The person who was looking my way was the person I nominated
No no no
This was the perfect time
to use this
Punishments Go Easy Card goes unused
This could've been Tanaka...
That's true
If it had been me
That's right
I could've used this
There's no harmony
There's no hope for harmony
World peace is still very far away
He also says, "Hamada," not "Hamada-san" after the Tameguchi OK card had already expired
HAMADAAAA!!
He did say that
That was ridiculous
He was in the wrong, indeed
Unnecessary
You knew what you were doing
This is not helping your cause
No one asked for that
No way
Feeling exhausted after getting smacked really sucks
You didn't see Hamada's face when he got kicked, did you?
Well, no...
It was repulsive!!
You can see it right there
It's reflected accurately right there
It was that expression right there, that expression
That face though... really was...
I should've been okay on that one
Okay okay
Endo, you were laughing out loud
The judge...
I don't really like it there
Gives me a bad feeling
You think so?
Geez...
Hosei, you're all wet, aren't you?
In the room next door
A change of clothes is prepared for you, let's go
How many times are you gonna get changed?
Seriously
Just say "Tanaka" next time, seriously
I could've made use of it
No kindness at all
That is certainly right
Ended up with no kindness at all
Hosei's course of action already disturbed all the others
It's only just the beginning
What is this!?
4:45PM
Passing the 8 hour mark of prison life
This is so scary
You know, he...
When Chono appears, he always tries to get Tanaka and me to switch with him, right?
Indeed
That kind of thing, you know
He has a dark side, don't you think?
It comes out in those situations
It's just that
I didn't have that expression when I got kicked
This is the truth
You don't even know
That image right there was...
Changed to Masked Pervert
See?
Pu
What the hell
I really don't get it
What the hell is that?
Are we allowed to do anything?
Um, what?
What kind of prank is this?
What is that?
Why are you playing around?
The bandages on your shoulder...
The bandages on my shoulder...
Are we allowed to do anything?
What the hell is that?
I don't even really know
I... honestly don't even want to do this
It's this
Exactly, just when I thought I was going to get changed
This was the only thing there
What are you doing..?
There's no way this was the only thing there, seriously
There wasn't anything else, I'm telling you
I also don't like doing this
I don't get the meaning of it
Kahhh!!
Got me good!!
Your underwear is stained yellow as well
It's stained yellow
So full of malice!!
You're equipped with malice!!
Really, I know this is full of malice, but
Who was it that made the yellow stain!?
The yellow stain was...
Was it that way from the start?
It was that way from the start
Equipped with malice
Would you please?
"Would you please?"
Would you really say that?
Please stop
What the hell do you mean, "Would you please?"
That's gotta suck
Please, not me
Not me!! Seriously!!
Ahhhh!!
No way, that would hurt so bad
That hurt so much
No no no
How do you even put this on?
Like I don't mind wearing it, but it'll be lame
That part by your nose is all yellow
This isn't even funny at all
Your senpai is saying so
But even if you say my senpai...
Your senpai is telling you
Yes, but...
No no no, really
You can't do that
Really though...
Endo, you cannot do that
Your senpai is reaching out to you
See?
Right?
Just for a bit
Oh no, I mean...
Our senpai is telling us
It's already went around so...
Our Prison's Own
Amazing Model Prisoners
It started on its own
At Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison
We have Amazing Artisans
We have amazing artisans
Duty aside, they stand out from other prisoners
Stand out from other prisoners
as model prisoners
in their duty
Right now, let us present to you the model prisoners
They say he previously was a glass sculptor
Previous Glass Sculptor
Mr. K (42 years old)
Regarding his work with glass
he makes use of his artistry
Making use of his artistry
to significantly increase production
and significantly increases production
Not only that, but with these skills
Like a robot
he produces with such delicacy
he's almost like the newest model robot
He makes glass items with very little inconsistency
A work of art
with such delicacy and speed
And here, we have this model prisoner
Superstar Model Prisoner
Mr. Y (67 years old)
This man prides himself by using his artistry to be popular as the superstar of the prison
Just by going on with his daily life, he aspires to release a masterpiece
An unconventional and unthinkable
craft is what he hones
An unconventional and unthinkable craft is what this model prisoner hones
He shows us the debut of his great masterpiece
At this moment, he shows us the debut of his great masterpiece
7:00AM - Breakfast
2:00PM - Recess
9:00PM - Sleep
The model prisoner, carrying out his penal servitude
He carries out his penal servitude in a normal fashion
When will his masterpiece be debuted?
Just when will his masterpiece be debuted?
That's when...
The model prisoner slowly stands up.
He is about to use the toilet.
The moment of creation
of his masterpiece
In fact, it is said that this is the moment that his masterpieces are made.
After using the toilet, on his crotch
is a large stain.
Model Stain
Yes, this is what is called the Model Stain, and it is none other than this that is proof of the masterpiece.
Proof of the Masterpiece
In order to commercialize the briefs that have had the Model Stain firmly stained into it, we now collect.
Superstar Model Prisoner
Ebisu Yoshikazu
He is Ebisu Yoshikazu, the model prisoner.
Why did you make me wear it?
I didn’t even have anything to do with it.
The Masterpiece
Hentai Mask with Model Stain
You have that string going right up into your ass.
What the hell?
What was that?
Don’t turn back!!
Ow!!
No.
This is bad.
The Ebisu stain was rough.
Let me change, come on.
This Ebisu product…
The Ebisu stain...
That was just...
This doesn’t make sense.
This doesn’t make sense, seriously.
That is seriously rough for your ass.
I'm bare here.
It’d be nice if you could
borrow Tanaka’s card.
Even with this, I can’t do this.  I can’t do this.  Seriously.
Punishments
Go Easy Card
Punishments Go Easy Card
The next time it comes, I’ll quickly put this hand towel in the way.
What?
If your punishment comes around.
Wha-, what do you mean?
So right when it comes, I’ll quickly put this here.
The pain will probably be halved.
The next time it comes.
‘Cause I can’t even watch this any further.
Will it really make a difference?
It’ll definitely make a difference.
It’s made from two layers.
That’ll totally make a difference.
So when it goes “Yamazaki Out!” and the guy comes, I’ll quickly come to the side
and when the guy winds back, I’ll quickly go like this.
Like this. Bang.
This’ll definitely make a difference. It’s cold, too.
This is a nice idea!!
Nice idea!!
I feel sorry for you, watching you.
Yes, that's rough.
If I could take your place,
I would.
But it’s not like I have the power to do that.
If you asked for it seriously,
I think it’d go through.
No, it definitely won’t.
First of all, if I asked for that, then Hamada isn't going to just sit there quietly.
If I step up and say “I’ll do it,”
well, Hamada’s also a guy with a strong sense of responsibility.
So Hamada will end up doing it,
and that,
I can’t allow.
Because I also have a strong sense of responsibility.
These senses of responsibility, together, are
causing your situation right here, instead.
So, in the end…
We stay just like this.
Right?
What a quandry...
If only we could use Tanaka’s card.
Switch cards with me.
But…
No, no, come on.
I mean, during the guinea pig thing,
people kept saying, “You’re a bad person...."
You can speak tameguchi with this.
Can he really use that?...
But the person who originally got the card already used it.
Punishments
Go Easy Card
Rules:
Only the person holding this card
can have punishments go easy on them
It won’t have any effect anymore.
No, it doesn’t say that.
It doesn’t say anything.
Nothing like “Only the original receiver…”
But if you could use it multiple times, I mean…
That’s right.
If you use this card – “Only the person holding this card,” it says, so that won’t…
So if we switch and I hold the card, then isn’t that fine?
But your card can’t be used anymore.
Right, it was already used once.
So, “As long as people switch, it’s OK”
– we’ll just make that the rule.
Who are you telling that to?
It’s difficult to make that judgment here.
Why don’t you use it and then try laughing?
And then you'll find out if they go easy.
Then, in that case,
if I can switch cards, then I’ll laugh.
Let me switch cards with you, and then I’ll laugh.
You’ll laugh, and then they’ll probably go easy…
They’ll go easy, plus…
Oh, the hand towel.
Then I’ll laugh.
OK, then here.
Let’s do that.
That’s fine.
That has been officially handed over.
Request it. Declare it.
Yes.
I will use the Punishments Go Easy Card.
Announcement
The Punishments Go Easy Card is now in effect
We will go easy on punishments
Punishments Go Easy
START
And this, please.
Do we need this?
Well, they’ll go easy, right?
But, that,
you came up with the idea so can’t we use it?
Well, I guess.
OK, here I go.
OK.
Here it comes.
That's an out.
It’ll definitely come.
Yes.
This is it.
Ow...
What is this?
It’s totally wrong, what the hell is this?
Come on.
What the hell?  It’s a lie!  We were lied to!
That was totally meaningless.
We’re being lied to.
Scary
It’s not in effect at all.
They didn’t go easy.
Goes into effect only for the owner of the card
That means it only works for Tanaka.
That’s it.  That must've been it, right?
So…
Well, yeah, since it was in Tanaka’s drawer.
What about my hand towel?
Did it work?
It made
no difference at all.
It just licked my butt a little, like this...
Argh, I see.
Come on.
It was a lie!
Seriously, that was a lie.
It’s a lie.
You can’t just lie.
Prison Life
8 Hours and 30 Minutes
The sun is starting to set.  It’s 5 PM.
This way.
An essential part of prison life
Engaging in labor at the work area
The five will take part in an essential part of prison life.
An essential part of prison life
Engaging in labor at the work area
Engaging in labor.
Sit at the end.
This is better.
We will now have everyone
do some work.  Put these flyers into envelopes.
Task:	    “Making Flyers”
Take your job seriously.
Yes.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Roger.
Everyone,
fold these flyers into thirds,
and put them into the envelopes.
The opposite way?
I think like this is fine.
He said into thirds.
I’ve brought the three that are assigned to cleaning.
Prisoner
Gekidan Hitori
Roger.
Clean the work area.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm thirsty.
You’re in the middle of work; not until you’re done!
Yes.
He’s strict.
Rehydrating while no one is watching
That’s quite a lot.
He was drinking like crazy.
You’re kidding me.
Huh?  There’s no water.
Pouring water into the vase
He's drinking too much.
There's no need for more.  All right, already.
What the hell?
He’s a freak show!!
It’s a merlion.
That was really amazing.
So amazing.
Is he really drinking all that?
Oy!! What are you doing!?
Take this guy away!! Quickly!
Amazing.
Uuu Guuguuu...
Gururururururu
Nnnn naaaaa
He couldn't get it out at the end.
He couldn't get it out at the end at all.
He looked like he enjoyed it.
You two, your cleaning duties are done for now.
Let's head over to the next place.
For you guys, keep doing what you're doing.
Current duties will be continued
Okay.
Alright.
You didn't even do much.
I'm doing it.
Fugitive
Itao Itsuji
Escaping while crawling along the ducts
Bangs
You will be found out
Seriously... he'll see you.
He'll definitely be found out.
Can he even go through that thing?
Secretly brought mayonnaise
Why the hell did he bring mayonnaise with him?
Maybe it's important to him.
Maybe it was an important item for him.
Maybe it's something he always uses I guess.
I guess so.
What is he gonna do? Keep crawling?
Maybe something will come out from that side.
That's impossible.
He should go back.
Going back would be even harder.
Takes a toll on you physically.
But even if he goes back...
Ah, so it's like that.
Then why didn't he do the same thing on that side?
Maybe it won't turn.
It's 6pm.
Been living in the prison for 9 hours 30 minutes
The five prisoners are getting tired.
But...
The thing that Matsumoto is concerned about is...
This card... I want to use it but I'm not sure when to use it.
This is huge, because it's 10 minutes.
It's bad if you just use it and you have to go someplace else.
It's bad if you use it and someone enters, right?
That's true...
Then, I'll just use it now. It'll be a waste otherwise.
Now that I finally am using it, I really want to have fun; I think Endo would be great for that.
Just do anything that will make me laugh for 10 minutes.
But asking me to do that...
Because for me, Endo is my weak spot.
But that is...
Just like your Pteranodon, that really tickled me.
I don't even remember doing that.
Matsumoto-san has been bringing that up a lot.
It was really out of this world.
OK to Laugh for 10 Minutes Card!!
Inside announcer
OK to Laugh for 10 Minutes Card is in operation.
In these 10 minutes, it is okay to laugh.
OK to Laugh for 10 Minutes Card
It's only okay for me though.
Yup.
Whatever I do now is okay.
I'm gonna totally laugh a lot now!!
Now, I guess...
A Triceratops now is quite...
Don't you think so?
I think so too.
Now wait a sec...
Triceratops?
How did I do it before? I really can't remember.
It was like this.
Yeah, you were like this?
Like this?
Yeah, that's right.
Then, I'll be Suga-san, okay?
Ehhh...
I'm Nakamura-san.
Yes, Nakamura-san.
Yup, Suga-san was like this.
That's right.
Like this...
You were Tyrannosaurus.
Yup.
And I was a...
I think he was a Pteranodon?
Pte...
It was a Pteranodon!
Stegosaurus!
I'm Stegosaurus.
Yeah, that was it.
I'm Stegosaurus, and he is Pteranodon.
Suga-san was on this side, right?
Reenact the position at that time
Then, I'll be on this side.
They're wasting a lot of time.
It's a waste. Since I only have 10 minutes.
Just start anytime. I really can't remember anyway.
Start!!
OGO
OU
OGOGOGOGO
OGO
OU
It wasn't like that
I think it was funnier than that.
It was more furious.
I wonder how I did it last time. Maybe because the place is different.
Since he himself can't remember how to do it...
It was way funnier that time.
Really?
How did I do it? "OU OU"?
Just now it was like you were aiming for something.
You were acting more freely before.
Can I even reenact those circumstances again..?
Start!!
OU
OGOGO
More!!
OU
SAY IT LOUDER!!
MORE!!!!!!!
MORE!!!
YOU'RE DOING IT TOTALLY WRONG!!
You're making the use of my card pointless.
AGAIN!
Go!
Sorry.
OK, ready!
Go!
OU
I think you have to go back to how you were feeling back then.
That's important.
Just remember. We just have to do it again, right?
Why don't you go and practice once first?
Maybe you're being too mindful in front of everyone.
Just go outside and practice.
And when you are ready at your own pacing, just come back in.
Maybe that will be better.
- So when he enters...
Just start when he enters, I think that would be better.
Then we will be on standby over there. We'll wait for you.
Maybe that would be best.
Since we're running out of time.
Because I don't find it funny at all.
Just think about what would be best for you to do.
Tanaka, what are you again?
I'm a stegosaurus.
Stegosaurus is a bit slow-moving, right?
You have to think whether this is a life or death situation.
Because you're not giving out that kind of feeling at all.
Maybe if you do that, I would laugh.
Why does this feel like a theater?
Maybe I would think, "Wow, this guy is giving his all" and I would laugh.
It's like a farce.
Theatrical farce.
Then, let's do this.
Let's do this.
Let's go.
OU
OU...
Enough, that's enough.
I'm so disappointed right now.
It was better if I didn't use the card at all.
Inside announcer
Laughing is OK for the next 5 seconds.
Laughing is OK for the next 4 seconds.
Laughing is OK for the next 3 seconds.
Laughing is OK for the next 2 seconds.
Laughing is OK for the next 1 seconds.
Laughing is OK for the next 0 seconds.
Time is up.
OK to Laugh for 10 Minutes Card
Time's up
I wanted you to do a bit more...
I want 10 more minutes too...
Maybe it would be better if you ad-lib more.
Since you're just saying "OU OU" and not anything else.
Maybe if you had shouted something else I would have laugh.
You could use the "OU OU" to have our attention
and then just change it at the end.
I wonder why you didn't say anything besides "OU OU"
I keep wondering, "Say something else Endo!!"
Even though you used up all of the time allocated...
Do you want to try and change it? The "OU OU" part.
But you can't laugh anymore.
It was really messed up.
What is he even thinking?
Just say something besides "OU OU".
Please go ahead.
Here I go.
OU
He won't get away from "ou"
Yeah
Ultimately he hasn't stopped saying "ou"
Ultimately he hasn't strayed from saying "ou"
Yeah, but...
This guy is laughing too
Your "tata-ta-ta" was great though
But you brought back the "ou" so
I give up, I give up
Your "tata ta-ta" moment
was looking good
but then you felt like you weren't generating laughter
and you went back to using "ou"
The "ou"... yeah
I got that feeling very clearly
Can you try a bit more?
The two of you, to Endo
Are we still going to try it?
How many times do I have to do it?
Do it again
Yeah
We might have to do it onstage sometime
Yeah, let's do it
Let's do it right
Let's just finish it
What the hell is this?
We should practice so we can do it onstage
Let's complete it
To me, honestly, it's not like a
I get it or I don't get it type of thing
Even I am thinking "what is it"
You said it!! In the beginning!!
YOU said it first!!
What do you mean "not seeing it"?
You suddenly just said it!!
Right
Do it
Yes, I will
No more, no more
Seriously what the hell
I'm seriously getting confused
Oh no
Ah I can't
I don't understand your
point of view
My point of view is...
I seriously don't understand, but
Thank you
They've experienced prison life for over 10 hours now
It's over here guys
This way
Observation of
prisoner's reunion
The five of them will observe the prisoners' reunions
Hosei on the very end
Yes
Everyone you will listen quietly!!
Listen quietly...
Yeah
Dojima Tamaki
female
Dojima Tamaki, you have a visitor
We have to be careful...
Tamaki's man
Nakajou Kiyoshi
How annoying
Really?
I'm starting to see the point of view!!
They will show this off!!
Yes they will
Tamaki...
You...
It's been a while
Did you lose weight?
You lost weight too, didn't you?
Yakuza and female prisoner's reunion
How is prison life?
I'm doing well
What's with that face?
Are the younger members okay?
They're doing trivial things
that don't make money
These days, young men are easygoing and don't work hard
The Yakuza are eating well and making love with good women
That's how we live
That's typical of you
I remember what you said whenever you used to get mad
Once you bear the responsibility...
you can't put down the mikoshi partway
Note: Mikoshi can be translated as a palanquin or a portable shrine carried in festivals
Lately,
when I drink sake at midnight,
I get fed up with Yakuza life.
When you get out of prison, we'll get out of Yakuza life
and go somewhere far away.
That's nonsense
Yes it is, but because of me-
Say no more
I won't take it
You
are the woman who made me a man
Without you, I was just a lowlife Yakuza
You're stupid
What's going on?
Yes yes yes
We are forced to watch this show!!
Yes, definitely, that's deep enough
You're so close to me, but behind the glass you feel so far
Your
I want to feel your silky skin
I want to be embraced by your warm chest
I want to taste your body
Here
With this hand,
I want to hold your body
Really..?
Seriously... I'm not lying
Seriously..?
It's not a lie!!
So you're serious right?
When I see your crushed up cigarette butt, I see your lie
Lie (Nakajo Kiyoshi/1974)
You have some good women, you have
Ah~ It was just over half a year
Ah~ She looks good in an apron
(about mic)
Where was she keeping that?
You asked me not to paint my nails, and then I cried
You are the man who can tell sad lies
It's a singing show!!
The story follows the song
Yes, that's right
Yes
What?
It's a lie, right!?
You left a bad habit, phone calling in the middle of the night
Oh no, no more
That's enough
Going to bed without locking the door
We already understand
That's enough
We're good
You have no intention to get together
Ah~ What will you do with the wedding dress?
It's really long
You were kissing me and telling me you liked kimonos
You are a man who can tell cold lies
They are in love
(prison guards) waited for the song to end
Yes, that's right
Tamaki!!
You!!
That's completely fine
At 7:30 PM, a strange scene unfolds in the reunion room
Dojima Tamaki
female
Dojima Tamaki,
you have a visitor
She just had a visitor
Tamaki's man
Nishioka Tokuma
What a powerful existence
What a powerful presence
They've brought in amazing people
What a bleak place to have a reunion
Amazing
Tamaki-san is amazing
It's the same person
Yes, I know
Tamaki
You
It's been a while
Did you lose weight?
Aren't you the one
who lost weight?
Yakuza and female prisoner's reunion
So,
I've been doing well, thanks to you
Are the younger members okay?
They're doing trivial things that don't make money
We (already) heard this
We heard this
The Yakuza are eating well
and making love with good women. That's what we live for.
These days, young men are easygoing and don't work hard
That's typical of you
I remember what you said whenever you used to get mad
Once you bear the responsibility...
You can't put down the mikoshi partway
Notes: Mikoshi can be translated as a palanquin or a portable shrine carried in festivals; you've read this before too.
They just did that!
They've already done this
This happened already
We already know
This is just a waste of time
They already did this
This woman knows what she's doing
She definitely knows what she's doing
You're so close to me, but behind the glass you feel so far
Your...
I want to feel your silky skin
I want to be embraced by your warm chest
I want to hold you close to me
Really?
Yes, really
You truly think so?
Yes
Yes, it's true
But...
I can't do it
What?
The man I am right now can't do it
Can't do it
Tamaki!
Forgive me
This is how it is
Exits after a different progression
Honey!
Even though we loved each other so much...
Why... Why did it turn out this way..?
Why did it turn out this way!?
Why oh why did it turn out this way~
Tetsu & Tomo arrive as they overhear "Why did it turn out this way"
Nishioka Tokuma joins in
Is this for real?
Such energy!!
So much energy!
What the hell is he saying?
Why oh why did it turn out this way~
Completely copies Tetsu's movements
Taking a group photo at the gathering
Look at the photo after it's done, there's always a guy who looks like this
There's always a guy with eyes half-closed
You're really into this!!
Why oh why~
It won't stop
I've had enough!
He can't breathe!!
It must be Tokuma, it must be Tokuma, it must be Nishioka Tokuma
Are you okay?
Just a little more, just a little!!
It must be Tokuma, it must be Tokuma, it must be Nishioka Tokuma
Wow, this is a long one
Wow, you're really into this
Keep it up!!
It must be Tokuma, it must be Tokuma, it must be Nishioka Tokuma
You're so cool!
That's pretty amazing
It must be Tokuma, it must be Tokuma, Nishioka, Nishioka, it must be Nishioka Tokuma
Amazing
Bravo
Made it to the finish!!
That just now was...
So amazing, Tokuma-san
What is this?
That was amazing
Magnificent
That was magnificent, wasn't it?
It was magnificent
He can really move
There's still something left
What a bunch of fools
Why is it that I could never hate them?
It must be the weakness of a woman in love... That's right
No way...
It's a loss for a woman in love... That's right
What the hell is this?
Tamaki-san...
No more, no more
This is no good, huh?
8:00PM - Living as a prisoner: 11 hours and 30 minutes
In no time, a laugh-inducing trap is set
Announcement
Hey you guys!!
It's time for some amusement!!
The super popular drama will be starting
so be sure to watch!!
Drama, huh...
Gaasuu Public Middle School
3rd Year Class B
This...
Alright everyone, please take your seats
Class is about to start
You can't do this
Oyakata...
Wow
This is messed up
The happy-go-lucky teacher appears
Yes...
This is just...
My ass hurts, ow ow ow
That hurts
Let's do our best here
Yes, really
Alright everyone, please take your seats. Class is about to start
Notes: Takamisakari Seiken was a sumo wrestler, but retired and became Furiwake-oyakata, with "oyakata" being a title for sumo coaches.
Sakamoto Furiwake
Sumo Master Furiwake
Like really?
Was that cutscene necessary?
Was that expression really necessary?
Not necessary
He just did that on his own, didn't he?
I don't get it
Overall, it was not needed
So true
If he could've just dropped that, it'd be fine
I wonder what facial expression the script asked for...
Alright then
That was awful
So hilarious
Furiwake-sensei! There's an emergency!
Did something happen?
Katou started a riot and then in the broadcasting room...
WHAT'D YOU SAY?!
He's got the volume, but...
Wow
What a loud voice
Amazing
Would you really be that surprised?
Although other than being loud, there's nothing else
Furiwake-sensei! There's an emergency!
Did something happen?
Katou started a riot and then in the broadcasting room...
WHAT'D YOU SAY?!
3rd Year Class B!
Furiwake-sensei!!
3rd Year Class B
Furiwake-sensei
Notes: This is a parody of a famous Japanese drama called Kinpachi-Sensei
What the hell
Notes: This is the opening theme to Kinpachi-Sensei, called "Hitotoshite"
I can see from far away
Why the hell are you singing this?!
Very nice
Good
That, just now, was great
Nice, very nice
I can see from far away
Isn't this terrible?
I grasped my hand around yours
This isn't any good
Isn't this awful?
Sumo wrestlers are usually pretty good at singing
No good
Yes, they do have that stereotype
Right
Very good
Though I have no words to give to you
Sounds so gentle
Does he not know this song?
There's no way he doesn't know this song
I repeat the same feeling of sadness
That's right, I'm just human
If you laugh here, there's no end to it
That's exactly right
I meet other people as a person, I'm confused by people as a person
I hurt other people as a person, I bid farewell to people as a person
You're not going to go get it?
You should've went at that point!!
Don't give up, go for it!
Don't give up and go for it!
Why, was it laziness?
No more, no more of this
No no, this is no good
He must've thought it was a pain at that point
I hurt other people as a person, I bid farewell to people as a person
He already gave up
He gave up
But even so
I can only
He's completely given up at that point
love people
Broadcasting Room
Is this where Kato is?
Kato! Open up! Kato!
To all students of the school:
Be quiet!
Kato Masaru (Himself)
Naoe Kiichi*
*Note: Naoe Kiichi, the actor here, is the original actor who played the character of Kato Masaru in the actual Kinpachi-sensei TV series.  The scene being portrayed here is from an episode that originally aired in 1981.
I am Kato Masaru from 3rd year, class B.
Wow.
That’s really him.
Yeah, that’s really him.
He looks like an old lady, doesn't he?
You really need to go that hard?
To all students of the school:
Be quiet!
I am Kato Masaru from 3rd year, class B.
We did not take over the broadcasting room.
We’ve only come to settle a matter with Mr. Shimizu.
So when we’ve settled the matter, we’ll leave. Good?
It's not good! Kato!
You're damn right it’s not good!
Now, sir,
can you tell us why you tormented us so much?
I didn’t torment at all.  I was only instructing.
I didn’t torment at all. I was only instructing.
Give me a break.
How is throwing out a rotten orange instructing?
I liked school. I had friends as well.
You see,
your friends were the problem.
What kind of face is that?
Get out of here with that.
We have a right to come to school.
Apologize to us for taking away that right.
Get on your knees and apologize!
Kato!
I was wrong.
I regret causing this misunderstanding.
What the hell is this?
Good for you.
It’s the police!
The famous scene.
Stop!
Get your hands off my students!
The world is always changing,
so only the stubborn suffer sadness.
Take something that doesn't change and use it as a metaphor,
and every time that something crumbles, blame it on just that.
Waves of protest slogans...
Why the hell?
Why?
Come on.
There was nothing like that before.
Why is Obachan…
Was she always there?
It was so sudden.
She wasn’t in there at all.
She wasn't there, right?
No, no.
Waves of protest slogans pass by.
That’s a hideous sight.
Wish for an unchanging dream upon the flow.
Look at that.
Stop the time, to fight together with those
who want to see an unchanging dream.
What a two-shot.
We are taking you back because
Is this going to be ok?
these adults here thought about what would be best for your future.
Apologize to them, properly.
That hurt for sure.
I thought no way, but…
Yeah, I know.
But to do the parody, yeah, it’s a slap and then a hug.
The scene, yeah.
Wow, Kato.
This is a KO scene.
Wow.
That sound.
You’re my students! Don’t forget that!
Kato! Don’t forget that!
We have a new star.
9:30 PM
Prison Life
13 Hours
The entrapments of laughter continue.
Let’s go.
It keeps on going.
The five go to observe a reporting session that the prison staff participate in.
Prevent crimes before they happen!
Observe a reporting session among prison staff!
The five go to observe a reporting session that the prison staff participate in.
Oh, this.
*Note: Comedy duo Ameagari Kesshitai: Miyasako Hiroyuki on the left and Hotoharu Toru on the right.
This.
*Note: Comedians Katsumata Kunikazu on the left and Shinagawa Hiroshi on the right.
*Note: Comedian Kimura Yuichi.
We would now like to begin the
reporting session for Gaasuu Kurobikari Central Prison.
Just in case, let me state that the purpose of this session is
*Note: Comedians Jinnai Tomonori on the left and Tamura Ryo on the right.
for us prison guards to go undercover in various professions
Undercover Prison Guard Reporting Session
A session to report on the behavior of suspicious people in show business
who are likely to commit crimes in the future
*Note: Tarento/Actress YOU (Ehara Yukiko).
in order to investigate people who we suspect are likely to commit crimes in the future
and report on their behavior.
Now, someone who has some information may begin.
We can start with anyone.
On Hamada,
Hamada Masatoshi Classified Information
A common occurrence on the golf course
He really likes golf.
And he often goes golfing with his juniors.
There’s this common occurrence
where Hamada mistakes a mushroom
for the golf ball.
This happens frequently.
Frequently, it goes, “Let me look for the golf ball."
"There it is! No, it's a mushroom."
That occurs frequently.
So on one day, Hamada takes a shot and it goes
in the rough.
So everyone’s looking for the ball,
and he goes, “I found it!"
“No, it’s a mushroom."
Again with the mushroom.
“Oh, no, I got it, I got it," he says.
So Hamada hits the ball from there.
And he gets it on the green nicely.
“Nice shot!” everyone says, and they go to take a look,
and it's a mushroom.
Is that real?
Seriously?
It's impressive he got it on the green.
He got it on the green.
That's the kind of thing that happens when you're nearing the end.
Come on.
I can tell what are mushrooms.
And he examined it.
This is something
Hamada Masatoshi Classified Information
In the parking lot...
I heard from a junior of Hamada’s.
“I parked the car in the parking lot,
so can you bring it around?” Hamada told him.
“I parked it in spot number 3.”  So he went,
and found the parking spaces were organized by alphabet.
No way.
Was it a B?
The B became a 3.
It was probably an E.
On Tsukitei Hosei,
Tsukitei Hosei Classified Information
At an on-location shoot for his main program…
There’s a program called
“Drive A GO! GO!” Hosei's on that’s important to him.
For 2014, they went to  Hokkaido for the summer.
Summers in Hokkaido
It doesn’t have a rainy season and is dry,
so it’s a popular destination.
During Hosei’s on-location shoot, it was pouring rain the whole time.
That’s true.
Unlucky for him, even though it’s an important show for him.
It’s dry during that time.
I have something on Matsumoto.
Matsumoto Hitoshi Classified Information
Halloween Party
Recently, we had Halloween.
All of Japan was in excitement for Halloween.
“But when we were young, this Halloween business,
it was nothing like this."
This guy called Miysakao kept saying this to Matsumoto in the dressing room.
“Was it like this when we were young?"
“No way!!"
“People walking around dressed as Japan Elekiter Union*?
*Note: Japan Elekiter Union (Nippon Erekiteru Rengou) is a comedy duo that became popular in 2014.
No way!!"
So he won’t join in on the excitement.
“Back in the day, no way it'd be like this."
He’s disliking this more than anyone else.
Makes sense.
Sada, a TV writer,
who’s always with him,
says, “Miyasako, hey…"
“What, Sada?"
“Um, Matsumoto…
“at Don Quijote* the day before yesterday
*Note: Don Quijote is a discount chain store in Japan.
was buying
an alien head mask."
An alien?
The silver kind.
The most cliché kind.
That's a gaffe, right?
Alien Mask
The most unfunny kind.
But since he has a daughter, you know.
Oh, I see.
It’s not like him.
It's not a story like that but I have something on Matsumoto, if
that's ok.
I’ve been having these regular lunches
Matsumoto Hitoshi Classified Information
Regular Lunches with Junior Comedians
with Matsumoto.
It'd be me, Matsumoto Hitoshi,
and a junior who
Matsumoto hasn’t met, and we have these lunches set for 2 hours.
It’s a really nice thing to have, regularly.
As if to show off to his juniors
that he’s always funny...
So the junior and I are always there first,
and Matsumoto always arrives a little late.
With a pretty high frequency,
he arrives and then,
“Jinnai, how’s the wife?”* he'll say,
*Note: Jinnai Tomonori had a high-profile marriage to actress Fujiwara Norika from 2007-2009.
and in a pretty loud voice.
When I say, “No, no, we divorced,”
he goes “Whaaat!!” and takes a peek at the junior,
but his bit falls flat every time.
Every time?
This guy... Pisses me off.
Matsumoto falls flat often with his juniors.
Is that really true?
And he arrives with full intention to do the bit even if it falls flat, just for the junior.
It makes things awkward.  Doesn’t break the ice.
That’s right. It doesn’t break the ice.
He falls flat quite a lot.
On Tanaka of Cocorico...
*Note: Comedian Komoto Junichi.
Recently, with Komoto
Tanaka Naoki secret information
story about giant salamander
He went to see a Japanese giant salamander.
Perhaps because he likes Japanese giant salamanders so much,
so he crouched down to the salamander's eye level
and he kept yelling,
"It's a giant salamander!!"
Is that it?
Is that really it?
No, no
Something else happened after that, right?
Like he got bitten by the salamander or something?
Um, no
Nothing else?
I have the same birthday as Tanaka: on April 26th
Tanaka Naoki secret information
TV show reunion
And we did this regular TV show together which ended 5 years ago, so we met up for the first time since then
and we recorded a show on our birthday, April 26th,
and Tanaka said, "Do you want to go eat dinner?"
And at that time, Miyasako-san was with us,
and at 4 A.M., after Miyasako-san went home by taxi
he said,
"Why don't you take a walk around the Asahi TV station?"
Just take one more lap
and right before I got into the taxi,
he said, "Shina,
you looked very sparkly" to me
Is he a homo?
I'm not a homo! There were many reasons!
Doesn't he have a kid?
Tanaka Naoki secret information
Latest information
This is very fresh information!
Right now, Tanaka seems to be doing a 24-hour job
but,
today his second son
receives his school entrance results.
He doesn't know the results,
but his son
got in.
What the hell!
That story!
His second son?
Ah, wow
Congratulations
Congratulations, congratulations
How embarrassing
Embarrassing
Over here!
Yes, yes
In the happy Tanaka household,
there is something called "service pants"
Service pants?
and it seems to be Naoki's
favorite thong
Tanaka Naoki secret information
service pants
and this is information from his wife
For what purpose?
It's from a brand called "hanky panky".
It's black and lace
He seems to like those type of thongs,
and the reason they are called service pants
is that even if his wife wears normal panties
and he wants to have sex with her,
he makes her change to the service pants.
This is information from his wife, so
there's no doubt about it
Is he a domestic pervert?
Isn't this information from his wife?
Usually, he is the quiet type, but when he is drunk,
Tanaka Naoki secret information
when he is drunk ...
he tends to his highly praise his wife's body.
He tries to seduce her by saying things like
"you are so cute; your face is very pretty"
in order
to have sex with her
Let's stop this
Let's stop
That is very unexpected
I like her, I like her
This is about Miyasako Hiroyuki
Are you okay?
So he was in this private room,
Miyasako Hiroyuki
at a meal ...
and he was eating
and it was Miyasako, Sada and me, and then he said to Sada,
"At Donki,
go buy me supplements."
So Sada said "Alright", and he went then came back
and he did an ad-lib,
and I've never seen something like it before
he bought an incredible %#@$
and I was taken aback! I thought "What the hell is he doing?" And Miyasako got very mad,
and he said, "Hey Sada,
this is one I already have!"
I'm seriously gonna kill you later.
I feel hurt by your unfunny story...
What could it be?
I have something...
My story is about someone named Miyasako
Miyasako Hiroyuki secret information
at a party ...
I don't really know the details,
but 8 years ago, he said
to my wife,
he said, "Unless you come with me in the taxi, I won't go home," and he was very fussy
That's a lie!
8 years ago?
not even married 8 years ago
You were not married 8 years ago
Who?
You weren't married 8 years ago
I was.
It's been 26 years since I've met my wife: unbelievable
Oy you're gonna end it here?
Alright, let's go
Stop here!
Oh, you're gonna go.
It's 10 P.M. Misbehaving prisoners are causing trouble
It's terrible!!
There are so many bad things
Gaasuu Kurobikari's two big gangs have started fighting
The guards can't subdue them,
so can you go and help?
Let's go
Two big gangs fighting
These 5 go help!!
There are two opposing groups everywhere
That's not rare
You can find them anywhere
They do exist
Yes, you're right
Can we really stop them?
Do they really have to fight at this hour?
Workplace
What the hell man!
Fight could break out at any minute
You did it!
It was you!
Hey everyone, can you be nice to each other?
WHA?
WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU GUYS LOOKING AT!?
YOU GO TAKE A SEAT!
Yeah!
Go sit down!
Your enemies are over here, Ueshima!! Look over here, dumbass!
Who do you think you're talking to, you son of a bitch!?
This isn't a show; go take your seats!!
#%@#&*@!!
You good, Ueshima?
Let's see whose body is stronger! Let's start now!
Let's do it then, dumbass!!
truce is unsuccessful
Conversation was not enough, so now they will use their bodies to show their strength
Two big gangs will fight mercilessly using their bodies
Let's go!
Alright, here we go!!
The way to settle it is to fight!
Changing into fighting clothes
That's what we're doing!
Yeah!
#@$&%*!!
Let's go!
Alright! Anyway, bring that thing out!
Here we go
Let's get it ready
Is it ready?!
Are you ready?
Yeah it is ready!
This is the "Chinko Machine"!!
What is this?
The legendary "Chinko Machine" has come out!!
Yes, the legendary "Chinko Machine"!!
Penis strengthening machine
Legendary Chinko Machine
Behind the part shaped like a cross
lies the punishment bar of the machine
Penis how will it be trained?
How will the machine work?
Our Tanaka...
Degawa gang
Tanaka Takushi
No matter what the machine does to him, his penis can withstand it
Degawa gang's pride
His penis can stand any amount of punishment
Show them!
What? What are they gonna do?
Oh, that's what they're gonna do
Don't push yourself too hard!!
You'll be okay!
Begin punishment!
Ah, it's coming it's coming
Weak
Strong
Punishment strength meter
You can do it!!
Show them!
Easy does it
Okay, this is the weak setting
It's still weak
Who controls this machine!?
Did you see that!?
He can do pretty well!!
But we have a good one over here!
Ueshima gang member
Kendo Kobayashi
Chief of Ueshima gang
Hey Yoshinobu!!
Yes!
Your turn!
Ueshima gang
Nakamura Yoshinobu (producer)
Yeah!
Can you handle it?
Ueshima Gang's Pride
Withstand the hitting machine longer than Tanaka
Alright, Yoshinobu!
His penis can stand all damage
Show them!
Yes!
GO!
What a producer!
Can you handle it?
You must be getting scared
Weak
Strong
Strength meter of hitting machine
When you want it to stop just say stop
It's hitting him
It's not so kind anymore
What the hell is this?
What is this?
That must really hurt
It's not hitting him!!
That's cheating!
That wasn't even hitting him!
It wasn't hitting you
Ouch
It just touched your back like a feather!!
What the heck!?
It's all over the place
Have you ever heard of the "steel ass"?
"Steel ass"?
That's about me!!
What the heck?
Bring it here!!
Usually "kanadarai" is
something that hits you on the head from above
That's not what that is
The bowl will fly up from below against gravity and hit your ass
Ueshima Gang's Pride
Use ass to catch the bowl that flies up from below
The name of the game is
Exploding revenge bowl
We will show you!!
Tsuyoshi!!
Yes!
Please take care of ignition
Yes
Ueshima gang
Nakagawake Tsuyoshi
Tsuyoshi-san
Alright!
You can only use your ass
Can you even do that?
If it's me, I can do it. Just watch!!
Let's go!
Alright!
It started
Alright
Catch it...
It's ignited
Hoi-yo!
Don't get scared
Of course I'm not scared!
UWATA~!!
Ha~
Ta~
He said "ha-ta"
He's saying "ha-ta"!!
Oy he's crying!
Are you crying?
Yeah he is!
Man you're crying, aren't you!?
Yes I am!!
You said "ha-ta"!!
I did say "ha-ta"!!
Over here there's someone who can truly handle a bowl!!
Are you gonna do it?
Is he okay, boss?
I'll do it!
Bring a real bowl!!
Bring it bring it!!
It's not even that different
This one is a little bit bigger
You're stupid. It's the same thing.
This is real!
This is a real bowl!
You can do it!
Are you ready?
Hey, be careful!!
What are you so scared of!? You son of a bitch!!
Okay let's go!
Let's go!
Yeah it's much bigger this time
I'll show you!
Come on!!
Please show us!!
Come on!
It's coming!
He said, "Oh ouch!!"
I DID NOT SAY THAT!!
I didn't say it!
That's nothing!!
No problem!
It's like I got bitten by a bee!!
That's painful though!!
That is painful
Over here there's someone more amazing
Oy Iwao show them!
Can I even do it?
Show them the exhibition!
He doesn't seem very excited
He just always seems kind of hesitant
Let's do this!
Go on!
This is 3 consecutive explosions, you son of a bitch!!
Let's do three!
What!?
3?!
Show them show them!
Yeah!
Alright
He's so bald!
Alright!!
Seriously?
What? Can he survive this?
It's 3!
Don't get scared!
It's lit!
It's off!
You can do it!
Okay let's go
Let's go!
Yes!
He's laughing!!
Only the rhythm was okay!!
So Iwao
that's not the only thing that will torture his ass
Liar!!
Show them!
Your ass can't stand anymore!
He doesn't seem very excited
He's sitting hardcore
This will challenge the strength of the surface of your ass
What do you mean?
On this fake grass,
he will be fine if he is dragged on it only on his butt
Show them!
How many seconds will it take you?
I can do it in 30 seconds!
He said he can do it in 30 seconds!
Easily!
Show them, show them!
Really?
Ouch ouch ouch ouch
Don't hurt yourself
That will hurt
Start!
You can do it!
Ouch ouch
Ouch
He's saying "ouch"!
10 more seconds!
Wait wait!
Alright!
Come on!
Can you do it?
But he didn't do it
He didn't make it, did he?
Just time!!
Okay
Okay okay!
Yes!
Kuro-chan from Ueshima Gang
Ueshima Gang
Kuro-chan
declares he can cross it in 15 seconds
Cross the fake grass in half the time (15sec) than previous attempt
Ueshima Gang's Pride
I'll show you
You can do it in 15 seconds right?
I will!
Ay!
Start!!
*screaming*
He's just screaming!!
Hey! Hey!
He couldn't do it
You couldn't make it!
Over here there is someone more amazing!!
We'll show you a real "hot-hot king"!!
What is the "hot-hot king"?
Our Haranishi is the real hot-hot king!
Degawa Gang
Haranishi Takayuki
With a pot full of very hot water,
he can catch anything!
Show them, show them!
What is going on?
We've prepared
5 pots that prevent hot water from cooling down
What's that?
Prepared Items
Pots of boiling water, assortment of items
Away from the 5 pots full of boiling water,
there is an assortment of items
Haranishi says he will catch any item with the pot of hot water
No matter what is thrown, it must be caught with a pot of boiling water
Degawa Gang's Pride
Can you do it?
Ready?!
Yes!
Okay!
Item #1
Spinning top
YES!
Okay! Change the pot!
Item #2
Wood carving of a bear
Item #3
Japanese Pumpkin
Mochi! Since it's New Year's!!
Even then...
Such harsh training
Amazing!
How amazing!
Awesome!
Haranishi is gonna be in charge of the hot challenges
Now it's my turn! Bring that thing in!!
Oh what is this?
It's here it's here!
I will go down on the slide
using a express-sled
Sled Delivery
Slide down the slope with a sled
and deliver an item to his comrade on the opposite side
He will ride the slide on the sled
then he will deliver an item to his comrade
What will he deliver??
Since it's New Year's,
Sender
Item
Receiver
Hoshida
I will be delivering VERY HOT sweet sake
to my boss
Hot sweet sake
Boss Degawa
Please wait there!
Yes!
So he was the boss
So please just wait there with the stamp
Okay I will!
He said "VERY HOT sweet-sake"
Shall we begin?
Just hold the stamp
I will hold the stamp
I will start!
I will deliver it!!
Alright!!
The sweet-sake that contains my love!
Bump
Sorry
What happened?
What are you doing!?
This isn't good at all
Next challenger: Nakagawake Tsuyoshi
Ueshima army
Next, Ueshima army's Nakagawake Tsuyoshi faces the challenge
He will send hot wax to our boss
Sender
Package
Recipient
Tsuyoshi
Hot wax
Ueshima Boss
Boss, the wax will be coming soon! Okay, bring it on
Tsuyoshi doesn't look like he likes it
Ready
He's putting on such a grim face
He's been looking like that the whole time
Is he really willing to do it?
Do it properly
Good luck!!
It burns!!
What is wrong with him?
It's hot
You didn't get much (wax) on your armpits
Even though there's no wax, why does your armpit feel hot?
I got hit by the board
He's only complaining
Bring it on, you bastards
That was a different level from Amazake
It's the same
Then in that case...
We'll end it with that!!
OY!! Bring it out here!!
It's here
Who's going to come forth!?
Ueshima Ryuuhei
Ueshima Army Boss
A representative from each team will face off at arm wrestling
While arm wrestling, their butts will be filled with air
and they will wrestle as such
the rule is that whoever farts loses
That explanation is unnecessary
It's completely unnecessary
It's the same every year
Every year
The way you say it is so bad
Good luck!
(This is for what happened 2 years ago)
Final Battle
Arm Wrestling with their butts filled with air
Whoever farts is the loser
You're on a roll today
I'm on a roll today
Degawa Army
No Farting Arm Wrestling Showdown
Ueshima Army
Go go!
You look fully ready today
Yeah, he does look ready
Fill it up fully
Ueshima never gets filled up (with air) does he?
Because you've got hemorrhoids!
SHUT UP!! DON'T SAY THAT!!
Don't mention my hemorrhoids!
Zits in your butt
I told you not to mention that, didn't I!?
It has nothing to do with this!
Shut up!
It's irrelevant
He got so pissed when that was mentioned
Excuse me
Air is pumped simultaneously for both of them
Boss, what's this thing?
Don't say it!!
Ueshima, why is your butt purple?
Enough
Tanaka is filled, hurry up Ueshima!
Give me a minute; the tube came loose!
The tube is inside Tanaka
Is it inside?
The tube, the tube
The air is escaping through the tube!!
*Fart*
Air is coming out from the tube.
All right, let's go.
The tube was removed without problem
Pull it out
Gotta pull it out
That's true
Let's go, quickly!
Both butts have been filled up
His butt is rumbling
Ready
Go
Ah, it's coming out
Shit!
Fart*
*Fart*~~
What the hell is wrong with you guys?
Buu~ sound came out!
Ueshima escaped to backstage
There was a buu sound
Please wait for the boss to return
Boss
Boss ran away
Get back out here
Boss
You can't go empty your system like that while we're live
Just do it properly!!
Let's go let's go!!
Wait wait are we actually doing it again?
Of course, let's do it
Restarting, air is pumped in again
This is a battle
Ah, wait
Ah, no more
Too much!!
*Fart*
Sorry, it's almost done
Wait
Both butts have been filled up
Battle, battle!
What the hell is happening!?
Ready, go!
*Fart*
We won!!
Somehow in the final showdown our team lost
You guys aren't too bad
Ends with reconciliation
Sorry for saying all those things
You're all pretty good
Time to go
It stinks
They ended up friends again in the end this year as well
When the life-threatening battle ends, the guys put on a look of relief
The life-threatening battle ends
Expression of relief on their faces
On one hand, for the 5 of them it isn't over
That person waits for the 5 of them!!
After this, that person will strike
11pm
Finally, the moment arrives
Hey, could I get some wat-
Indoor Announcer
Emergency incident
Stay indoors now
A prison escape has occurred in the facility
People who are indoors
must report for immediate roll-call
Gather at the gym
Gather at the gym?
Itao ran away, but nothing happened...
Let's head to the gym
Prison escape occurred
Go to the gym for roll-call
Itao ran away but nothing happened.
Gym
Wow
Yeah, awesome
Indoor prisoners are all gathered
Matsumoto, Hosei
Explanation of the situation from the jailer
Be quiet
Actually, in this prison, there has been an escape here.
There are a total of 15 escapees
To verify, I will now do a roll-call
First, in sequence we will beg- start from the first
GOD
DAMN
Chief jailer
Masahiro Chono barges in!!
Eh? That out is-
At the same time as the out
Just now there has been a prison escape
This is extremely upsetting!
There is a woman
Prison Escapee Information 1
A woman has given birth in the prison!!
who gave birth to a child in the prison
The biggest problem with this escape is
that someone helped them!
And now, I'm looking for the husband who can provide us with more information on them.
Prison Escapee Information 2
The man who helped them is here!!
Is he here in this place!?
Not here?
There is information that will provide a clue
1 more clue...
Oy!
Bring it here!
Oh yeah
What an awful series of events
It has started
This kid's name...
is Akio
Prison Escape Information 3
The baby's name is Akio
Children are honest
When held by their parents they always laugh
So nowone by one
So now one by one
hold the baby.
If Akio laughs, then proof of fatherhood
Investigating who aided the prison escape!!
End
All right.
Starting with you.
*Crying*
You’re not holding him right!!
The baby bawls if it isn’t the father
It’s not you.
Okay.
You’re next.
Yes.
Sorry.
*Crying*
It’s not you.
You’re a woman?
Let’s have you hold him, just in case.
I forgot about that.
Who would remember that?
I totally forgot.
*Crying*
Ain't you, either.
That'd actually be rude, though.
All right, you’re next!!
Yes.
*Crying*
It still makes you nervous, right?
It does, it does.
Really?
It’s not you.
I see.  If the baby laughs there.
By some sort of reversal.
Right up until that moment. Just a bit.
I see.
All right.
You...
are next!!
Can you hold him?
Hold him!!
*Laughing*
Akio gives a big laugh
Well, that’s right.
The husband of the escapee has been found!!
So it was you…
What is this, then?
This is not my chi...ji...child!!
Come on.  What is that?
That's where you twist your tongue?
It’s begun. This year, again.
Stand!! Come over here.
That’s your child!!
His face is similar,
but it’s just a coincidence.
I pick...-ad up-a this child.
I was allowed to pick him up.
Get on the stage!!
What kind of explanation is that?
First, just get on here!!
But it’s really not mine.
Demanding an explanation on the stage!!
What’s his name?
I don’t know this child.
Isn't it Akio?
I don't know.
You're the one who named him!!
I didn’t name him.  I don't know this child.
You named him!!
I didn’t!!
I don't know this child!!
Can I just leave him somewhere?
Are you capable of doing something like that?
I can't...
What the hell are you expressing?
What is this?
What the hell, man?
I got the emotions mixed up.
This child is innocent.
I can’t do anything if you’re with the child.
Give him to someone.
No, no.
No.
I will hold the child!!
"Akio" to be taken away
Preparations for the punishment
Hey.  Take the child and hold on to him.
Give him the child!!
No.
Hurry up, you!!
No!!
Hurry up, guy!
Stop it!!
Stooop!!
It’s dangerous.  It’s dangerous for the child.
All right.  Take the child away.
What are you doing?
“What are you doing?” he said.
He was asking genuinely,
“What are you doing?”
Guards!! Come on stage, all of you!!
Come up.  Team, gather up.
All right, everyone hold him.
This is turning into a huge fracas, come on!
Hosei!
This is turning into a huge fracas!!
All right.  The child.
Stop!!
Akiooo!!
What is this?
What is the story that's going on here?
It’s because you didn’t let us take him.
Akiooo!!
The story has gotten out of whack!!
So it is his child!!
Ready yourself.
The accomplice of the escapee gets the slap of punishment!!
Get up.
The same routine as always, now.
Seriously, it took a while to get here.
Face this way, you.
Please wait a second.
Yes.
Face this way!!
I’m sorry.
Face this way!
I’m scared.
Sto~~p, please.
This is your fault!
No! Don't! No!!
Akiooo!!
Heeelp!!
Come on, what the hell?
Why are you asking Akio for help?
What the hell was that?
You can’t ask Akio for help.
The child isn't here anymore.
Okay.
Can you just listen to my last request?
What is it?  You can ask, that's all.
Please put Akio beside me.
Is Akio still here?
Can you bring him over?
Then, beside, here.
In front of Akio, got it?
All right.  Come over here.
All right.  Bring him over here.
All right.  Say one last thing to your child.
Akio, I wish you happiness in your prison life.
What, what was that?
“I wish you happiness in prison life.”
What the hell is that!?
Let’s do it.
Here it comes!!
What is it?
Here it comes! Get over here, further!
Don’t move, don’t move.
Here it comes!!
The slap of punishment strikes!!
Say something to your child.
Akio... I got slapped.
*Laughing*
God
Damn!!
In the end, he made it his own son.
Seriously?
You’re bringing him?
You’re going to recognize him as your own child?
Is that going to be all right?
He was screaming, "Akio!  Akio!”
am    0:00
The date has changed, and prison life has past 15 hours.
Prison life
15 hours and 30 minutes
My ass hurts.
So you brought Akio back.
You put him down quite carelessly.
Hosei,
we'll take care
of Akio at the prison, so I'll take him.
Hehe
Huh?  He laughed as if nothing was going on!!
*Laughing*
The baby is in a good mood when held by Fujiwara
Isn't he supposed to cry?
He's laughing.
What is with this story?
This story is scary!!
Scary.
It was Fujiwara? The father?
But he’s supposed to be a woman, so it makes no sense.
Then it can’t be that.
Yeah, since he's a woman too.
That one was hard.
Hey guys, it turns out that in this jail,
uh, have a cell for really bad criminals
They gave us special permiss-uh...
They gave us special permission so let's go check it out
Let's go then
"Really bad criminals"?
Special Learning Opportunity
To the Really Bad Criminals' Cell
We don't need special permission
to see the "really bad criminals"
So this isn't something you usually see?
"Really bad criminals"
"Really bad criminals"?
Guys it's over here
What? It's so close!!
Furthest over there is Tanaka, then Endo,
Cell
Hamada, Matsumoto, then Hosei. Line up like that
There were these bad criminals this close to us?
Wow, it's in a place like this
Really Bad Criminal
Mukai Seitaro (Tenshin)
I Am Noda (Onigashima)
It was right next to us
To give us a cake on New Year's Eve
the prison chief is so nice
Cake!!
CAKE!!
Let's split the cake!!
Okay split it in half!!
Wait what are you doing?
Give me my half!!
Why!? We can share!!
WHY!?
I want it!!
We can just eat it all together!!
I want to eat it!
Petty fight over cake
WE CAN JUST EAT IT TOGETHER!!
GIVE IT TO ME!
Oy  what are you guys doing!!
Oy what are you guys doing!!
Get away from each other!!
If you're gonna fight over the cake, I'm gonna take it away
YOU BITCH!!
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO TO MY CAKE!?
ISN'T THAT ODD!?
Really Bad Prisoner's Wrath toward Guard
IT'S MY CAKE!!
LET GO OF MY CAKE!!
Somebody!!
SOMEBODY!!
Alarm in prison goes off
MY CAKE!
KEEYEHHH!!
Chief Guard
Egashira 2:50
What are you doing!
BEHAVE @#$%&
Punishing them for petty fight
KYEHHHH!
OOOOOOH
Punishment #1: sucking nipple
Okay
Stop that!
I don't understand the reason!!
Explain his reasoning!!
There was a noise
Alright!
NOW LICK MINE!!
Punishment #2: Prisoner now licks his
He said it clearly: "now lick mine!!"
What the hell is this!?
Alright!
Punishment #3: Wedgie
That must hurt!
Wait, aren't you done with that kid?
What's gonna happen?
Carbon Dioxide Gas
Punishment #4: Carbon dioxide gas to the penis
My jaw...
Your turn
Wait- wait...
My jaw has dislocated so...
PUT IT BACK!!
It came loose!
It's fixed!!
Did you hear that?
What?!
Lie down like the character "kawa"!!
Note - Kawa is written with three vertical lines
What are they doing?
*gibberish*
YOU ARE NOT TO DO THIS AGAIN!!
GOT IT!?
Devil guard's punishment (of the prisoners) is over
What just happened?
Amazing
He punished them so severely!!
How incredible...
So messed up
His jaw was dislocated?
It must be easy to dislocate
The guard is the really bad criminal!!
Really...
The 5 men have one last task to do...
Sudden lightning bolts
What?
I'm scared.
Whoa what!?
What what what?
Undercover guards storm in
Scary scary scary
Wait~
Ahh they're here they're here
I'm so scared
This is just the worst
Hosei and Cocorico taken somewhere...
Whoa what is this??
Scary scary scary scary
I'm scared I'm scared ah
What?
Waaait
WAIT~
What about me? Somewhere else!?
What why!?
Hosei and Endo confined to the same room
Hosei-san?!
Help me, Tanaka!!
Help us!!
Endo!!
They put me in a cell!!
Come on!!
P- P- Put me with them!!
P- P-Put me with them!!
Please wait!
Damn it, Tanaka
Wait!!
Tanaka placed in solitary confinement
Come on, Tanaka
Why am I away from the others?
3 confined, as for remaining Downtown...
3 of them are confined,
and as for Downtown, who are left in the room...
Okay, so this is how it's gonna be
Restrained by handcuffs
That scared me!!
Hey Fujiwara what the hell is going on?
I'm sure it scared you, but
Hosei and Cocorico were abducted by my men so res- rest assured
So now this is jailbreak training!!
Rescue those three and work together to break free!!
You can laugh, but if you get scared, you're OUT.
Alright let's hurry
Why is a prison holding  jailbreak training the direction you're going in?
Special late-night rules
Special late-night rules - absolutely no getting scared: big prison break!
Absolutely No Getting Scared
Big Jailbreak
Hosei and Cocorico Rescue
Receive 5 Jailbreak Medals!!
The two have to help Hosei and Cocorico escape,
and then they have to get the Jailbreak Medals
in order to complete their training!
I'm so afraid of getting injured every time
Come on, help them
Whose voice is this?
The voices were
the worst part
Immediately attacked by carbon dioxide gas
Already?
Hosei/Endo confinement room
Whoa what is this?
Excuse me
Forgive me I'm sorry...
Interesting position
Tanaka confinement room
Gas there, too
Carbon dioxide rigged to 3 locations
Ow
Everyone got
something weird
Who's there?
Creepy noises resonate
Yasei Bakudan Kawashima
Imitation Face-Making Mansion
Where?
What was that?
What is this?
#1: Muscle Man
Flip the panel!!
It says "flip the panel!"
Announce
Welcome to the imitation face-making mansion
flip the panels one at a time
enjoy watching my masterful face imitations
#1: Muscle Man
Should we?
Here!!
What the fuck
It's Hiromi
#2: Hiromi
Here!!
No more no more!!
Don't present anything frightening!!
Flip the panel!!
There's more?
#3: Shibata Rie
Here!!
What the hell?
What a mess
Why does it have to be Tsunku!?
#4: Tsunku
Secret performance
Here!!
WHOA!!
LONELY... is everyone all alone?
Real life appearance
LONELY... are you by yourself?
My shoulder hurts!!
That was so scary
My shoulder popped
End of performance!?
It's done?
LONELY... is everyone all alone?
LONELY... are you by yourself?
Secret performance
LONELY... is-
What the hell?
Attacked by giant ball
Tsunku?
Hatake has come to Tsunku's rescue
Garittochu Fukushima
What the hell?
Hatake gives up and retreats
What the hell was that?
I hear something weird
The phone's ringing
I thought I heard it ringing
Payphone rings
Don't get scared  Telephone question!!
Here is the question
Why so loud?
People who are 30 years and older are called "arasa", however
*TRANSLATOR NOTE: arasa is short for "around thirty"*
what are people 40 years and older called?
(please write the answer on the board)
Oh, what was it again?
*TRANSLATOR NOTE: arafo is short for "around forty"
Isn't it arafo?
Arafo, right
Secret topic
what do you call people in their forties?
(Write the answer on the front of the board)
People in their thirties are called arasa* but
*Translator's note: Arasa is short for "around thirty"
Secret prank in
I wrote it
Hard Gay Razor Ramon congratulates their correct answer
Foo! The answer is...
ARA-FOO~~~!!!
My shoulder is messed up
Congratulations!!
For you two who got it right,
I shall award you the first "Prison Escape Medal"
1st Prison Escape Medal Attained!
Congratulations!
It's that big?
Please continue this way
Tanaka is in confinement
Okay, we get it, so...
Really though
I messed up my shoulder
His shoulder seems to be messed up!!
Looks like he's got old stiff shoulders!!
Sign
Rescue Tanaka, who is
confined in this room.
Vocal confirmation is needed
before entering
Rescue Tanaka, who is confined in this room.
Vocal confirmation is needed before entering
I don't want to do this kind of thing...
Is it here?
Yeah
There it is!!
Ah, I see
Tanaka is confined in the back room
How do we do the vocal confirmation?
Are we supposed to sit here?
The hell? My hands are tied, I'm holding a medal, I'm scared...
Vocal Confirmation System
Announcer
The vocal confirmation will now commence
Yes, vocal...
Face the microphone and say your own name
I am Matsumoto Hitoshi
Announcer
Vocal Confirmation
System
Vocal confirmation in progress...
Vocal confirmation is complete
Phew...
You are Matsumoto Hitoshi, correct?
Yes!
Vocal confirmation done
Vocal confirmation is a success
Announcer
Next person, please take a seat
Thank God
Face the microphone and say your own name
Announcer
I am Hamada Masatoshi
Vocal confirmation in progress...
Vocal Confirmation
System
Vocal confirmation is complete
You are Sato Gajiro, correct?
They sure love using Sato as a joke...
His voice matches with Gajiro's
Maybe it's broken
We already did this
No, not correct
Did the voices
match up?
Announcer
Vocal confimation has failed
We will start over from the beginning
You failed!!
We've done this before
Face the microphone
and say your own name
Please, just work
I am Hamada Masatoshi
Failed confirmation causes carbon dioxide gas spray
Announcer
We have confirmed you as Sato Gajiro
The door will now unlock
That's all it took?
Don't just let it be
Tanaka's Confinement
Room
Pardon me
My shoulder is messed up
Seems he's got the old stiff shoulders
Why are you by yourself?
I don't know! I was just brought here...
And I can't move
Sign
One of these boxes
contains the key
to release Tanaka
One of these boxes contains the key to release Tanaka
What should we do? There's one over there too.
The first box's contents are...
I'm counting on you
Can I just do this one?
But your shoulder isn't doing well...
There's nothing in here
The first box was empty
Go open that one
I'm really counting on you, please
I just opened it normally
And there was nothing in there
Oh, there it is
Zap
Bam!
Electrocuting key and collapsing chair
I really hate this
I didn't want to do this, I told you!
What the hell are YOU doing?
Tanaka, why are you rolling around?
The order of this, is it simultaneous?
What the hell, it was successful?!
The chair, the chair...
Seriously though, that really hurt
My body can't take this abuse!!
Whoa, scary!
The masked jailer releases Tanaka
There it is
We got the second piece
Huh what?
2nd Prison Escape Medal Attained
See, we have one too
We need 5 total
We have to collect all 5
Going to release Hosei & Endo, but...
After attaining 2 pieces of the medal, the three guys
try to leave the room, but...
Why won't it open?
You're right
The door won't open...
What? What's going on?
You're joking right?
What the hell!
The wall closes in on the 3 guys
The door!
Open it, open it, open it!!
It won't open!
It stops right before it flattens them
What the hell?
Scary!
It opened!
It opened
It opened, it opened
The door unlocks
Maybe you were pushing it the wrong way
Me?
What was up with that guy just then?
Hatake
Garitto-Chuu
Fukushima
What was that about?
That was kind of scary
Ominous Locker
I really don't like this...
Tanaka, seriously, don't get startled
His shoulder is messed up
Because of this, I...
PARADISE!!
Seriously, I'll kick your ass
I'll kick your ass, really
From the locker,
it's Nakagawa Paradise
Why is he here?
I don't get what's happening.
Please stop
Go somewhere else!!
Push push!
Shut up
Never say "Paradise" again!!
Yeah
Paradise!!
SHUT UP!!
Prison 2nd Floor
If these shackles weren't on me,
my shoulder wouldn't be like this
True
Arrived at Hosei's & Endo's confinement room
Oy! Over here!
It says for Tanaka to sit on the chair and wait
Sign
Release Hosei & Endo!
Tanaka, sit on the chair
and wait!!
Really? This chair also seems scary...
Help us! Help us!
The 2 are together.
Tanaka, just wait right there!!
I'm just supposed to wait here?
What happened?
Please help us
We're confined here
Release
depends on
this game challenge!!
At this time, Downtown
The release of the 2
must complete the mission,
for Hosei and Endo's release depends on it
Release Mission
Inside the room are 4 plastic bottles
The 2 must transport the bottles 1 by 1 between their faces to the trash
The 2 of them must transport the bottles 1 by 1 by putting the bottle between their faces all the way to the trash
If in 30 seconds all the bottles are transported, mission complete
If all 4 bottles are transported in 30 seconds, the mission is complete
The bottles get smaller and smaller, but we're counting on you!
30 seconds okay?
We're counting on you!
Okay, nicely done, nice!
Thank you!
3 more to go!
3 more!
They're getting smaller, but please!
Please do your best!
Thank you!
Sec
Remaining
Time limit
Thank you!
Just a little more!
1 more to go!
Thank you!
MISSION SUCCESS
We did it
It was a success!
Why does this have to happen?
The chair collapses for some reason
Why?
It was a success
Thank you very much!!
Someone's coming
They're gonna open it
since the mission was a success!!
Thank you very much!
Hosei & Endo are released
3rd and 4th Prison Escape Medals Attained!!
Hosei and Endo are released safely
Downtown's shackles are also taken off
They get 2 more medals
Only 1 more medal!
The 5 rush to for their Prison Escape!
There is only 1 more medal left
The 5 rush on to their Prison Escape
Secret Prank
Nooo...
"Prison Escape Medal"??
Yeah
It's supposed to be prison escape training, but
why do we gotta...
What the hell is that!?
Tokyo Skytree official mascot
Introducing Sorakara-chan on a Segway
You're kidding me!!
No way, no no no
What is that?
It's what's-her-face-chan
It's the Skytree girl
Sorakara-chan!!
Why are all of your shoulders in pain?
There's something here
Gaasuu's mouth
Put your hand in Gaasuu's mouth!
Only those with a pure heart
will get a Prison Escape Medal!
A medal for the pure-hearted...
Gaasuu's Mouth
Says you can get a medal
Only those with a pure heart
Matsumoto goes for Gaasuu's mouth
Please!!
Something touched me!!
Maybe they're trying to give you a medal?
Maybe they'll give it to you
Don't you dare lick or bite me, you hear?!
Don't do it!!
Lick
I got licked!!
That's gross
So gross! I just got licked!!
Ijiri Okada
Naked
It was definitely some old dude!
I was definitely licked, just licked! Smells bad!!
It's definitely some old guy
Probably is some old guy
Just some behind-the-scenes old guy for sure!!
No one likes being licked by some behind-the-scenes old guy!!
There's supposed to be a medal there?!
Excuse me, but really, just give me the medal
Hamada goes for Gaasuu's mouth
There's no end to this
Lick
You licked me!!
Try and smell it
Smells awful!!
Smells bad bad bad!
Give us the damn medal, you moron
5th Prison Escape Medal Attained!!
Why didn't you just give it to me right then?
Was it a naked old man?
A naked old man?
Prison 1st Floor
That's so gross...
A behind-the-scenes old man!!
A behind-the-scenes naked old guy...
What is that?
Come on...
A mountain of stuffed animals
Really now...
There's not much movement in there
You're right
A bunch of stuffed animals...
Let's go!!
That's our only choice
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
Shake
Inside the stuffed animals is Chucky
The attack of the Chucky army
So scary
Please stop!!
What's happening?
Masked jailers group, once again
Alright alright, geez
Wait wait wait, what? Okay...
Hold on!!
Someone's there
Introducing an ally of justice?
This is a relief
I feel relieved
Oh good
Yeah, we get it now
It's so cold, must be quite hard for you
So true
You must've been waiting a while
Who do you think I am?
Translator's note: Tamu-Ken is short for Tamura Kenji, a comedian
You're Tamu-Ken!!*
You're Tamuken.*
*Note: Tamuken refers to comedian Tamura Kenji.
No!
It's me.
An Ally of Justice?
Tamura Kenji
It's Tamuken.
He was right.
What the hell are you doing?
Ask yourself that!!
I’ll help you!!
You’re going to help us?
Really?
Lion dance
The last one is Asada Mai!!*
*Note: Asada Mai is a figure skater.
Bam!
The last move wasn’t Asada Mai though.  It was the lion dance.
To be precise, yeah.
Isn't this really funny?
This?
It is curious.
Do you remember?  It was all the rage.
Come on, 2007.
I really don’t know.
When Yamamoto Mona*
*Note: Yamamoto Mona is a tarento who in 2006 was caught having an affair with married politician Hosono Goshi.  After spending some time away from the public eye, she returned to TV in 2007.
emerged from exile
and hosted Owarai Ultra Quiz, she wore this.
Yamamoto Mona
She wore this.  Wasn’t that really funny?
You’re right, now that you remind us.
Since then, she hasn’t used this, so I took it!!
From her, directly?
Well, I didn’t confirm it with her directly.
Are you going to escape?
Yes, yes we want to.
That's why we're here.
Well, yeah, that's what this is.
I’ll take you!!
Let's go.
With Tamuken’s guidance, they head to the escape point
His role is this important?
Then let's go.
Just leave the horse?
The horse is fine.  I’ve told-ah them about it!!
Told-ah?
Telephone Booth
Hey, something’s written there.
One person shall
enter the telephone booth
and wait for instructions!!
One person shall enter the telephone booth
and wait for instructions.
Discussion over who enters
Well…
What?
Who’s good at this?
There's no good or bad at this.
The person who would fit just right in there
would be you, Tamura.
Why don’t you go?
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Me?  No.  You're the prison escapees.  You're the ones who have to do this.
But as long as one person…
No, I don’t think there’s any rule like that.
Do you want me to hold the lion dance mask?
I got it.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
After discussion, Tamuken to go inside
Get the instructions.
Really?  I can do it?
Shouldn’t you take the watermelon off?
Yeah, you should take it off.
Really?
Yeah, there you go.
So you prepared your head just in case.
You styled your hair!!
He’s serious.
I can really do it?  Ow!!
Jagged gravel
Well, yeah, that would happen.
The phone will probably ring, if it’s the same set up as always.
Give the instructions.
Okay.
This turned out well.
Yeah, it really did.
There it is.
A call comes in to the public telephone
He’s shaking.
Pick it up.
Just from the ringing.
Yes?
Other speaker
on the phone
Hello.  Is this the owner of the barbecue restaurant that’s deep in the red?
It’s not in the red.  It’s doing fine.
Other speaker
on the phone
Your financial bubble has already burst!!
Countdown to a
Secret Event
It hasn’t burst.
They hung up.
They hung up?
The door locks & in comes a massive amount of bubbles
Bubbles!
I see.
Oh, yeah.
What is this!?  It’s gentle!
There’s nothing to this.  I don't feel a thing!!
I think it’d be really uncomfortable.
Since the door has been locked, he cannot get out on his own
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You can’t get out.
There are more bubbles coming.
Door unlocked
Something's definitely strange.
Whoa.
Wow.
With all the bubbles...
there’s no oxygen anymore.
Right.
I thought I was gonna die.
When you thought it was about time to come out,
you couldn’t open the door and panicked!!
That’s a lot of soap bubbles.
I thought there was a malfunction.
It suddenly got scary, right? But for you, instead of us.
What the hell!?
A group of prisoners capture Tamuken
What are you doing?  Help!
I wasn’t told about this!!
The plan was for me to keep going after this!!
Then, we’ll
just go in the direction of the arrows.
All we can do is just keep going.
I’ll leave this over here, then.
At one point, he was really seriously trying to get the door open!!
He was serious.
He tried to open it like a grown man!!
Yes, since it wouldn't open at all.
Prison field
Is there something here?
So, how does it make sense that
Yes?
we’re practising a prison escape?
That's true.
Again, it's this...
Right, this setup is scary.
Again with this scary setup.
It really is that scary setup.
The path leads to the escape point
You climb over the wall to escape a prison, right?
Yeah.
What is this?
The way they’re haphazardly placed is really scary.
I know, right?
There’s
something over there.
Oh, yes.
This is Tanaka’s job!!
Let’s go together!!
Tanaka, don’t push me.
There’s something where we can match those things together.
Oh, we fit in each one for everyone.
When the 5 medals are inserted, the prison escape is successful!
Insert the 5 prison escape medals.
Oh, I see.
Mine’s the bottom one.
There.
Right... Here.
Mine is probably also…
Mine is…
Here.
The last one.
Okay.  It's in.
Wow.
Good job.
Did they find us!?
No, come on.
Announcement
This is an emergency.
5 prisoners have escaped.
Capture them at once!!
Capture them?
What is this!?
A horde of Pikachus & masked guards
It’s a crazy number of Pikachus!!
Seriously.
Why the hell is it Pikachu!?
He fell down again.
Tanaka, watch out!
Whoa!
It’s hot, it’s hot.
What a burden to the team.
Tanaka, are you all right?
He fell down again.
Sorry!
3 AM.
The men were forced to experience prison life…
For some reason this year,
the five men were forced to experience prison life.
After overcoming all the trials…
That moment has finally come...
Now, they approach that moment.
Here we go.
Everyone, be happy.
You are all to be released!!
Yes!
Now, each of you is a free man!!
Yes.
Good for you all.
Hamada.
Yes.
How was it?
We seriously gave it all we got...
but Toshi-chan (Tahara Toshihiko) really gave me trouble.
Matsumoto!!
I really say this every time, but there's a lot of misjudging and honestly, I think the others
should have been smacked more.  There are always 10 or 20 times where
I don’t think I needed to be smacked.
Everyone should
pay attention to Hamada more
and make sure his are never missed!!
Those are my thoughts.
Let’s go then.
It’s cold out,
so everyone wear these.
Ah, my behind hurts.
Are we going to be told in the end why we were arrested?
Yes, we still don’t know in the end.
That’s true.
And who’s going to raise the child?
That’s right.
What’re you gonna do with Akio?
Akio will be looked after at the prison!!
At the prison?
I want to meet Akio when he’s grown up!!
Since we’re released, that means it’s 2015 now!!
Prison Entrance
The new year has arrived.
That’s right.
Can you, over here...
Can you line up over here?
Happy New Year!!
The Legendary Prison Director
Suga Kenji   General Manager
This year is the year of the sheep.
If I could have Master Tsukitei* lead the call.
*Note: Referring to Tsukitei Hosei recently gaining official credentials as a rakugo performer (traditional Japanese one-man verbal comedy).
A sya-ah-llable sentence composition with “Hitsuji Doshi (Year of the Sheep)”
I would like to conclude the year in this way.
Hitsuji Doshi (Year of the Sheep)
Syllable Sentence Composition* with
*Note: Syllable sentence composition (A-i-u-e-o Sakubun, or acrostic poem to us westerners) is a word game in which the syllables of a topic word are broken up and the composer composes a phrase that starts with each syllable.  The phrases taken together should have an overarching theme that builds up to the final phrase, which is the most important line and acts as a punchline.
You messed up your line.
Master, if you will.  Hitsuji Doshi.
And now,
Hitsuji doshi: Hi
Through the wide world
Tsu
Finally will fly
Ji
The 5 of them, with outstanding ability
Do
With more and more gigs
Shi
Shieeeh!!*
*Note: A gag made famous by the character Iyami in the manga Osamatsu-kun.
Thank you, and see you next year.
What the hell?
When he did the Shieeeh, his pivot leg was…
Is it that hard to stand like that?
He couldn’t maintain it at all.
We're finally done.
Number of times their butts were smacked
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Tsukitei Hōsei
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Endō Shōzō
Tanaka Naoki
Yes, we’re done.
What, again?
Yes!
Ulfuls
Hooray ~I'm Glad I Fell in Love with You~*
Yay! I'm glad we did it again this year
*Note: The music is from "Hooray ~Thank Goodness I Fell in Love with You~" by Ulfuls, while the lyrics being sung have been changed to describe the episode’s events that happened.  The performers seen here are Ulfuls.
Happy that butts could be smacked on and on
Crime – you didn’t commit one.
But on and on,
the five in prison.
It's Ulfuls.
Guitar: Ulful Keisuke
Ulfuls.
Bass: John B.
They look good.
Drums: Sankon Jr.
Vocals: Tortoise Matsumoto
On a pointless journey, give D (Matsuko Deluxe) trouble
The more I think about it, the more it hurts
The jokes of the duos who kept laughing
Were Anna and Rola's rip off skits
I don't want to see uncool macho men
Just like how that mask that wouldn't come off
I don't want to see Kida's butt
That ass, baby, stop showing your ass
Yay! I'm glad that I love you
Tetsuya will keep on, keep on, saying yes until death
Hooray! I'm glad that we met Toshi
Staying in that little room, little room
La la la, just the both of them
Kizana Kiyoshi starts singing
Tokuma dances enthusiastically
Always want to mess around with comrades
Mimata, baby! Bring your crotch over
Yay! I'm glad that you got to drink water
Ebisu's panty that he's worn for a long, long time
Dosukoi*! Your slap was so good
*Translator's Notes: "Dosukoi" is a sumo wrestler's exclamation/shout
Let's just stay, stay and expose secrets
Akio, baby! Baby!
Stay, stay, stay by my side
Yay! I'm glad he spreads his body
Until death, always, always, naked and happy
Hooray! Glad that we escaped from prison
Finally this year, this year
Yay! I'm glad it's the new year
From now on, let's keep, keep, smiling and be happy
Hooray! There weren't any serious injuries
Gaki will always, always, be the 5 of them
We wish you another year
that overflows with laughter
So
That's the end, but we've already entered the new year
Happy New Year
The ending was performed by Ulfuls
Yeah, that was great
Yeah (didn't understand the last part)
It was good, wasn't it?
Next year maybe it could be a good idea to allow laughing instead
Then it will just be like any other day, wouldn't it?
Yeah, yeah, it would
It'll be just another ordinary day
At last
Perhaps, this year's chief of buzzwords will now be...
Endo Shozo
Sounds about right
After you say your piece, I'll say our farewell
Yes, understood
Everyone, please allow me
Please continue supporting us through the year of 2015
Please continue supporting Gaki no Tsukai this year as well
This story is a work of fiction.
The names of groups and other things shown are fictitious