Coloured, re-timed
and re-checked by:
Schwub
Re-re-timed by:
Corphix
Translated by:
John Loving
March, 2000
On the TV Show "Gaki no Tsukai"
a most rigorous punishment game took place.
It was called
24 Hour Endurance Tag.
Rules:
Stay in the Gym for 24 Hours.
When a tagger enters, Tag begins.
If you're caught you get punished.
Four men will have to endure this terrifying ordeal.
Hamada Masatoshi
(Downtown)
Yamasaki Hosei
Endo Shozo
(Cocorico)
Tanaka Naoki
Lastly, the man controlling
the game from the shadows
Matsumoto Hitoshi
(Downtown)
Giving it their all, body and mind.
Four men's heroic struggle is about to commence.
But first, it all began from this showdown.
10-year Anniversary Special Cup!
Matsumoto vs. Hamada, Cocorico etc.
End of Century 100m Relay!
In this relay, Matsumoto has to compete alone...
while Hamada's team will relay between four.
Of course, whoever gets to the finish line first wins.
I've got butterflies in my stomach!
Alright! Let's do this!
Ready!
Set!
Go on!
100m Relay Race
Matsumoto Hitoshi WINS!
I won!
Hamada Team
Punishment game forfeit!
It's fine! We'll enjoy it.
Trust you to say something like that.
Don't make me laugh.
So the result is Hamada's team: Punishment game!
YES!
Yea, right.
And so, the curtain of disaster falls on our four.
Enough already.
Today we'll be showing,
the latest punishment game we've completed.
It really was quite an ordeal.
So without further a due, let's call out the gang.
Everyone,
"sublime" would be a fair way to put it, right?
I'll have to admit, as a group we couldn't help being a bit dull.
I came to see you once or twice so I saw for myself,
I'd say you were huddled together like new born chicks.
Until now we've done a few different punishment games,
would you say this was the toughest so far?
Yea, definitely.
Really, I'd say...
Tanaka, you be quiet.
You've a blocked nose from a cold, you can't talk.
It's a result of the punishments.
That's how bad a punishment game it was.
Punishment Game Day
7:30 a.m.
(Begins in 30 minutes)
It's the morning of the punishment game.
The losing team slowly begin to arrive.
Each one as grim as the next.
Bugger off!
Shoving it in my face, first thing in the morning.
7:55 a.m.
(Begins in 5 minutes)
Five minutes before the game begins.
The groups spirits are still high.
We're going to start from here?
I don't want to.
How does it look?
Take a look for yourself.
It's big.
The floors covered in vinyl.
It's almost 8 a.m.
Starting time?
Well, it begins at 8 a.m.
Does it have to be so strict?
This place is huge.
What about the rules?
Rules:
- Stay in the Gym for 24 Hours.
- When a chaser enters, Tag begins.
- If you're caught you get punished.
What?
Come, gather around these manboobs!
Matsumoto's Messenger
Fujiwara Hiroshi (Manager)
Come over here guys.
Good morning.
Come, gather around these manboobs!
Why the hell do I have to get up
so early for you slackers?
Anyway, 24 hour tag will start shortly
but first, I have instructions
from Matsumoto for you.
So take what I say as if it's
from the horse's mouth.
Hamada! You in particular..
Oh sorry, are your allergies acting up?
- No.
Sorry, my mistake.
Anyway.. so, Hamada you're...
well known for acting the smart arse.
Today, just do as Matsumoto commands.
- Okay.
Alright, well let's start. Good luck.
24 hour tag starts in:
Let the games begin!
Origami Fan
You're going to get all of us?!
Another?
Metal Ladle
Kickboxer
Why me?
What, what you going to do?
(Ouch, that must have stung.)
(He was still wearing his shoes,
that was the worst part.)
What a tough start.
Are you okay?
..and we're only three minutes in.
(Man, you guys had it rough.)
All three got me.
A triple whammy.
It stings like hell.
Think it's okay if I just go home now?
It's hard enough just running.
I'm already feeling a bit queasy.
How old are you, Yamazaki?
I'm 32.
And you guys are twenty.. ?
eight.
- Twenty eight.
You're the youngest.
Hamada, this year you are?
37.
Talk about an age gap.
I don't think I can do this.
Don't you start complaining.
Conversation has moved on to
Yamazaki's weak rib bone.
No really. I mean it's not broken,
but it's cracked.
- What do you mean?
- Cracked?
It can't really be cracked.
Really, it's not broken but I think it's cracked.
Really.
I'll crack it in a second if you don't shut up.
Give me a break! I'm not kidding.
I think it might be serious.
It's nothing!
It is, seriously.
You can't crack your rib that easily.
What the hell!
Don't start messing around!
Sorry, sorry.
You're going to give me a heart attack.
See? No cracked rib, right?
It is, I can move at least that much.
What are you on about.
Let me feel it then.
What the..
What is it this time?
Come, gather around these manboobs!
I've brought you breakfast.
Really?
Matsumoto makes sure to take care of
even the likes of you.
He really is the model of an angel.
Before you eat,
let's give our thanks to Matsumoto
for feeding you layabouts.
You can eat once you say it.
Even the likes of us
All together now.
get to eat
because of Mr. Matsumoto.
Thank you very much.
Breakfast
Even while eating breakfast I'm nervous.
They've left their shoes on,
just in case the taggers show up.
(No time to take our shoes off, right?)
(Just in case one came.)
For fucks sake!
You're at it again!
I'm gonna die from fright.
Sorry, sorry.
It was my lighter.
It fell and hit the metal ashtray.
I leapt back automatically.
Please, just... don't do it again.
Each time it scares the crap out of me.
(They jumped to the sound of Hamada's fart.)
If you're going to fart, tell us first.
My arse still hurts from when they hit me.
Kendo Bamboo Sword
Wait! I'm holding a cigarette!
It's over right? You already got someone!
Surely that's enough.
You're not serious..
Hamada, what are you doing?
This is horrible.
I can't handle this.
Hamada... did you use me as a shield?
I think you just imagined it.
But I'm pretty sure...
Hamada grabbed me like a shield.
Sorry, my mistake.
- Don't worry about it.
Cheap shot Hamada using his junior,
Endo, as a shield.
9 a.m.
(1 hour in)
What if three of us run,
but one tries to hide here.
He might avoid it all.
No way.
Considering a plan to hide by the table
to avoid the tagger.
There's a chance it could work.
A small chance.
They'll automatically chase people who are running.
It's how people are.
Give it a try, just once.
Hold on a second, why me?
Let's do Rock-paper-scissors.
Come, gather around these manboobs!
Enough of that.
Matsumoto said your piles seem sore.
He told me to bring this for you.
I appreciate that, actually.
Matsumoto said to bring it.
He really is the model of an angel.
If someone does it, won't they get caught?
No see, we'll run.
I see, I see, he'll grab someone running.
Headbutt
Get away!
Are you alright?
You left me behind and ran.
It sounded like hollow wood.
Why did you run?
We can't test it if you don't try.
Do as planned next time.
I can't help trying to run.
Sorry about that, Hamada
Let's try some teamwork guys.
I saw all of you run in the opposite
direction in a group.
10 a.m.
(2 hours in)
When they come out, you get a shock, right?
But the massive writing on them gets me too.
Every single time they come out, BOOM,
scares the crap out of me.
And you can't help trying to read their chests.
With their featureless face chasing you.
Figure Four Leg Hold
Why? Why me?
Stick together this time!
Which way?
Hamada!
I give up! Please!
When I tried to run Hamada blocked me!
Yea? Really?
Cheap shot Hamada blocks Tanaka from escaping.
Is there really no way to get away?
I've decided. I'm going to try hide by this table.
If it works, let's all try it to take a break.
Yea, by rotation.
Okay, so we'll run and try distracting them from you.
Wait a sec, maybe I should go after, not first.
What's changed your mind?
No matter what way you look at it, Yamazaki
should go first as originally planned.
Okay let's do it like originally planned.
Why did you run the first time anyway?
So when they come, I should get in like this?
Exactly.
- Yea.
They won't take any notice.
We'll distract them.
It was the original plan so you should go first.
Okay.
If worst comes to worst and you get caught,
you'll have helped all of us.
Alright, I'll give it a shot.
Try not running away this time.
Definitely.  If I do it again I'll..
make myself.. ashamed.
That's hardly enough.
Well, I mean, I'm asking you to do it
but if you want to pass it on to Tanaka it's up to you.
Okay, let Tanaka do it.
No, I-
I'm big. Body's too big.
It's between you guys.
Decide by Rock-scissors-paper.
Wait, why me too?
Sorry but can't be changed. It's you know, been decided.
This isn't right.
Come on just do it.
First time is a blank throw.
It's Tanaka then.
First up to hide by the table: Tanaka
I'll give it a try and..
"Tanaka"
Scorpion Death Lock
"Tanaka's Victory Dance"
I give up! I give up!
Yes! Yes!
Thanks to you I was spared.
We've found a way to hide.
It's really easy.
Next up is Hamada, right?
Really?
It'll be fine if the last attempt is anything to go by.
That doesn't mean it'll work next time.
He wasn't looking at this area at all.
I went in a circle around here but he didn't notice.
Take a break, Hamada.
I should have gone first.
"Hamada"
Duvet Dust-beater
It really does work.
- Yea.
"Yamazaki"
Kickboxer
(He's screwed.)
No, wait!
No way, the kickboxer!
(Of all the ones to get caught out by.)
I wasn't expecting that.
What happened?
When he got to this spot, he just stopped
in his tracks and looked at you.
Noon
(20 hours left)
Come, gather around these manboobs!
I brought you lunch.
Slobs like you guys
get to eat and eat like you're normal people
all because of Matsumoto.
Don't hold Matsumoto back from now on.
Let's give thanks again before eating.
Even the likes of us
Hamada, you too.
get to eat
because of Mr. Matsumoto.
Thank you very much.
The group tuck into their curry lunch in a weary silence.
Even the smallest of sounds now cause them to jump.
I've had enough.
(You still jump every time Fujiwara comes in.)
(Get used to it.)
(If one person jumps it makes us all jump.)
Slide Show Story
What're you going to do with him?
The Slide Show bike has arrived!
(It's all completely black.)
Once upon a time,
there was an old couple.
"The fairytale of Peach Taro"
One day, the old man went to the woods
and the old woman went to
wash clothes in the river.
(There's no picture on the slides!)
(He really forced me to watch.)
4 minutes later
... happily ever after.
"THE END"
Did you see that?
- Yes...
It was horrifying.
It was all just black...
1:00 p.m.
(19 hours left)
If it really bent, I'd believe it.
But why is it always a spoon?
The group begin debating how to bend a spoon.
It doesn't work with forks.
I've never seen anyone bend a fork.
Candle
This one's fast!
Slide Show Story
"The Rabbit and the Turtle"
while the rabbit hopped along at leisure
3 minutes later
they lived happily ever after. The end.
"Headbutt"
I bet you didn't expect it to end like that.
3:00 p.m.
(17 hours left)
I wonder if we'll get any snacks.
That'd be nice.
I'm tired so something very sweet.
Pie
The Shows Chef Producer
World acclaimed: Heipo
What the hell?
It's Heipo.
Get him.
Bugger off.
He dropped most of it when he sprang up.
He was crap.
He's trying to ruin the show.
Everyone else is trying hard but he's acting the fool.
He made a complete mess.
When the floor threw him into the air it all fell on the stage.
You're still jumping!
- but you jumped before me.
Come, gather around these manboobs!
Yea.
After 6 hours of this that's about all I can muster.
Great, Snacks!
It's 3 p.m.
and what does 3 p.m. mean, Hamada?
Snack time.
That's enough of your cheek.
Here are your 3 p.m. snacks.
I've brought you something to play too.
It's the Game of Life. You good for nothings may
as well see what a proper life is like.
$200,000!
The group has perked up while playing The Game of Life.
Matsumoto Hitoshi has arrived.
4 p.m.
(16 hours left)
The Shows Chief Producer
World acclaimed: Heipo
He's not even trying.
Shove off.
And don't come back again.
4:30 p.m.
(15 hours 30 minutes left)
The group get back to playing the game.
You've got to be kidding.
We've become very sensitive to sound.
Any little sound and we leap in the air.
So, how're you getting on?
Hey!
We're still playing.
I was thinking of taking it.
Why?
I was watching you back stage and thought you were enjoying yourselves too much.
That didn't seem right.
But I'd just become a pro athlete..
Alright, everybody strip.
What's the point in us stripping?
You're getting very cheeky.
And getting on my nerves.
I might be back again, later.
I just came to tell you next time I won't be so nice.
I'm gonna kill you all, tallest first.
That can only mean me first.
Got it?
Please give that back.
No. Shut up.
Just the oxygen then.
Who the hell do you think you are talking to?
Who the HELL do you think you're talking to.
No, Stop! I've got a bad back.
I said I have a bad back!
That's enough, idiots.
What now?
Die!
I thought he had a bad back.
He's off.
I'll be back.
Don't waste your time.
What a pain.
Leaves us to clean up this mess.
We'll that lowers the mood.
Let's start with the pieces from the game.
He knocked the tea and all.
4:50 p.m.
(15 hours 10 minutes left)
I was wondering,
why is it whenever you hear the tagger noise
you always go "Waa!".
No matter how many times I hear it,
it scares the crap out of me.
Ass
No. Wait!
What's written on them?
- "Ass"
What the hell?
Oh god!
That's nasty.
It was soft...
But one of them
touched down right on my nose.
My shoulder's getting stiff.
What about your rib?
My rib has still got a crack.
You looked fine when they came.
You've been enjoying yourself, running around.
I didn't want to be a wet blanket
Open-palm Strike
This one looks bad.
"Rescue man" arrives!
Look, he's helping us.
Good job, Rescue man.
- Thank you!
Giant swing
He's huge.
5:20 p.m.
(14 hours 40 minutes left)
Ass
Why me again?
You just got me a minute ago!
You okay, Hamada?
Hamada?
He's okay.
I'm speechless.
The hair was sore..
His balls were just lying on my face.
It touched your face?
It's hair, scratching my face.
Lukewarm raw flesh.
It wasn't exactly pleasurable for me either.
Who'd enjoy squatting on their friends face?
We were really nervous the whole time.
I don't think that's noticeable.
Every single thing made us jump.
It stayed like that constantly.
We just couldn't get used to it.
Hamada kept faking it and throwing us off.
You were the worst!
I was just making sound, right?
No, whenever we were all sitting at the table
you always made this noise.
Right! Right!
Whenever the taggers came it went "PSST",
but whenever Fujiwara came it went "Donk, Donk".
Remember that much!
"Donk, donk" and you leap!
6 p.m.
(14 hours left)
10 hours have passed since the game started
Unpredictability of the attack has wiped the smiles off their faces.
(From this point on you didn't speak much.
- Yea, we were just tired.)
False alarm.
Metal Ladle
That's not fair.
We can't be sure where they'll show up anymore.
"Tagger sneaks in."
(Didn't someone notice?)
(I noticed first.)
"Hamada notices him."
(Why didn't you tell us?)
Open-palm Strike
(He's too slow.)
(He's chubby.)
(He needs to pick up the pace.)
(He can't make sharp turns.)
We'll never need to worry about him anyway.
I think we should watch different directions.
That sounds good.
I'm going to watch the front stage.
I'm going to keep an eye over here.
They decide to watch four different directions.
What about me?
- That side.
Excluding the main bit?
- Roughly that area.
Come, gather around these manboobs!
Yeah.
Listen up.
Matsumoto seems to be worried about your physical well-being.
So he's arranged for you to have a massage.
I don't think any of you deserve it,
but it's not my decision.
Hamada.
- Yes.
Don't you have stiff shoulder?
No.
Don't you have a stiff shoulder?
- No.
Never mind then.
Matsumoto really is a saintly being.
Please come in.
A masseur called in by Matsumoto.
Does it hurt?
- No, it's fine.
Is he stiff?
- Yea.
Romero special
Sorry, we can't help.
(You guys were properly keeping guard.)
The Shows Chief Producer
World acclaimed: Heipo
Come on then!
Are you okay?
(He didn't say a thing.)
What is he trying to achieve?
7:10 p.m.
(12 hours 50 minutes left)
Come, gather around these manboobs!
Yep.
Matsumoto has decided to let you degenerates eat something.
It looks good.
It's a special dinner by an excellent chef.
By his great kindness you'll get to fatten your stomachs.
Have you forgotten already?
Quit it.
Not until you say it.
Even the likes of us
get to eat
because of Mr. Matsumoto.
Thank you very much.
Dinner time
Table turning
No..
I had more than half a steak left.
I always leave the best bit 'till last.
What a mess.
My cushion is okay.
That's the most important thing.
7:40 p.m.
(12 hours 20 minutes left)
Come, gather around these manboobs!
We went a bit too far.
Matsumoto thinks you might need some energy,
so I've brought you some sweets.
He really is a God among men.
You're tired, I insist.
But they're all sweaty.
They're all sticky..
C'mon, eat it.
It touched the ground.
The tissue's sticking to it!
Matsumoto really is a God among men.
(He just said it twice now.)
8 p.m.
(12 hours left)
(We'd been sitting around for about an hour now.)
Matsumoto thinks you might be getting a bit bored.
He's going to let you watch a film.
Matsumoto's praise should be sung from every corner of the world.
I wonder if it's okay if I sleep.
Movie time
"Sea of Japan"
Why do we have to watch this film?
A 1991 film starring a young Hamada as the leader of the "Tepputai" gang.
Hamada (28)
You look so young.
1 hour 40 minutes later
"Tepputai"
Who'd have thought they'd come through the screen?
9:45 p.m.
(10 hours 15 minutes left)
Still 10 painful hours left to go.
Slaps for Yamazaki
I'm gonna get you!
He's only after you, get away from us.
(Former manager of Downtown)
Okamoto Akihiko
The cat legged it.
Hello everybody.
- Hello.
Are you okay?
My ribs are killing me.
He was calling out "Yamazaki!".
- Why only me?
It said 'Slaps for Yamazaki' on his chest.
You're still so jumpy.
You're the jumpy ones.
All you guy leapt up at the same time.
We just copied your reaction.
- Liar.
Come, gather around these manboobs!
Okay.
Matsumoto thinks you guys are going to start to get hungry soon.
So we've prepared supper for you.
Instant Noodles
courtesy of Matsumoto
You're very methodical with it.
Smells good.
They can't be serious.
They've done a crappy job.
Jerks!
Let's share this one.
Let's play Rock-scissors-paper to decide who eats first.
I'm first.
The fried tofu..
There's only one, and you just ate half of it.
There goes another half.
The soup's good too, though.
About done yet?
I can't stop half way.
Don't you think you had too much?
What are you doing?
It all went back into the bowl.
Some onion went down the wrong pipe.
It's fine, really.
(What's wrong with you.)
What's wrong?
I can't eat too fast, please don't rush me.
I wasn't rushing you.
It's gotten pretty small..
Ah, stop there.
You have to stop when you've cleared your chopsticks once.
You have to keep food on the chopsticks.
You should have told me.
Sorry. Okay, I'm taking my second run.
In that case I shouldn't have drank the soup.
Yes that's right.
Why didn't you tell me from the start?
I wouldn't have done it if you had said.
Ah, so that's how I should have drank the soup.
Is that okay?
Yea, if your lips are touching the bowl it's okay.
Really?
You have to keep it continuous.
Your turn.
Sorry, that's it.
You finished when you removed the chopsticks.
I only paused to drink the soup.
I don't want to make a fuss, but you know.
Never mind, it's fine.
You can have it.
Even though, you know, I'm your senior.
The rules are done with now, right? There's only soup left.
Sure, there are no noodles left.
What's he doing? That's not right.
He's twisting his arm around turning the bowl.
This twisting is okay?
Yes, when you twist your arm around the bowl, it's okay.
Okay, I see.
I'm done, here you go.
There's still a drop left.
You twisted it like a pro.
I'm full.
- The fried tofu was tasty.
Pitching machine
That can't be good.
Wantan Noodles
It's hot!
That stinks.
10:30 p.m.
(9 hours 30 minutes left)
As time goes on
the group gets physically and mentally exhausted.
One person still continues to get on everyone's nerves.
What now?
I have a fever.
- A fever?
First cracked ribs, then a rash, next a ripped ear
and now a fever.
Graduation certificate
We got away from it this time.
See? Your ribs not broken.
The way you were waving about.
It's cracked.
No matter how you look at it, you're fine.
I'm not. When you're being chased, adrenalin is released.
10:53 p.m.
(9 hours 07 minutes left)
Enough already!
You're just a bag of nerves
Come, gather around these manboobs!
- Okay
This is for all of you.
Eat it.
A pork bun.
Shouldn't there be four?
I don't really like this kind.
At least it's easy to divide, just cut along the lines on the bun.
We should take turns like before.
Why?
Rock-scissors-paper would be a waste of time..
Waste of time? We've got loads of time.
What's wrong with cutting along these lines?
Some might get more pork than the others.
The pork often isn't dead centre.
Okay, that seems fair.
I'll start.
Keep an eye out.
You never know when they'll come.
I'll keep watch.
You're all grown men, I supposed you'll need a bit more.
We're pretty full actually.
Well, Matsumoto has seen fit to give you more.
Thanks.
Yet another present:
a sausage
This one is easy.
Only one again.
This one's easy, no problem.
We just divide it into four.
As we did with the Noodles and Bun..
- Wait, wait.
If you're all full why don't you...
It's for a different part of the stomach, like a cow.
Fine, let's just divide it into four.
It wouldn't cut evenly as it's soft.
That doesn't make a difference.
Let's just get it over with.
The middle is noticeably thicker.
It tapers toward the ends.
What're you talking about?
It doesn't change that much.
Keep watch.
It's the same.
It rounds off at the corners, whoever takes that will get less.
I'll take the end then, just add a bit more.
How about that?
You don't want the ends, right? So I'll take it with a little extra.
That'll be more than your share though.
Even though you're my senior, it doesn't count now.
How about this: Half it then you guys eat it from the inside
then leave me the bits on either end.
Got it, that seems doable.
That's fine.
Seems fair.
Don't forget to leave Hamada's bit.
Why did you put it all in?
Why did you put it all into your mouth?
That's it, I'm done.
But we did it by your rules.
You put it all into your mouth.
I couldn't tell how much I put in.
Just hold it in your hand
and bite off the bit left sticking out.
This end is a little slippery.
If I put it in once..
Look, don't talk with your mouth full.
Just hurry up and eat it.
Why are you telling him to do that?
Just thought he was being rude.
What about my bit?
You've still got some left. Bite it off.
Just bite it off.
Why are you pushing it in?
Bite it off.
Stop that!
Why couldn't you bite it off normally?
Why did you do it like that?
Why twist it?
I told you to just bite it off, why twist it?
And what about you?
You've got nothing.
We made a deal, I get to have the ends.
I'd say about this much but I can't even work out what shape it is now.
You couldn't leave this much?
I was trying to make sure...
Are you an idiot?
Sorry.
- Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It won't happen again.
I just don't get it.
We're really sorry.
Well, I'm stuffed.
11 p.m.
(8 hours 50 minutes left)
Cane
Where you going?
- The bog.
Yamazaki goes to the toilet alone.
Pie
Hey!
Guys!
What happened?
In the toilet.
They were in the toilet.
The taggers?
- The taggers.
Three of them.
They were in the stalls.
Did you finish?
They attacked me half-way through.
Are you serious?
That's bad.
Your face is unbelievable.
You're totally unrecognisable.
We heard you screaming out like that.
I just hear a noise.
Then turned?
They attacked you when you turned around?
I didn't know what was happening at first.
This is hell. Pure hell.
No place is sacred.
There are so many of them.
When you see the video we seem to be energetic all of the time,
but between those bits there'd be periods of 30 minutes, or an hour,
just sitting there, completely nervous.
How much do you think you ran?
You ran quite a bit.
Seemed like dozens of kilometres.
- That sounds right.
It caused a bit of tension between us, though.
What do you mean?
Go on, explain.
Surely you get what I mean.
I thought you'd bring that up.
You know, about being senior or junior.
From here on, we got really tired.
Fatigue really kicked in.
Your rickety muscles must have started giving in.
12:30 a.m.
(7 hours 30 minutes left)
It's past midnight.
They have reached the peak of their fatigue.
Any energy to talk has long gone.
Come, gather around these manboobs!
What's this?
Futons?
Gather around, make it snappy!
It's bedtime.
We'll continue the game tomorrow,
for now, get some sleep.
Really? It's okay to sleep?
Enjoy.
One last thing.
Let's say goodnight to Matsumoto.
Matsumoto,
goodnight.
I'm the only one he kicked twice.
There's a single set each.
It's better than nothing.
It'll have to do, let's get ready.
Mine's a different colour.
You've left me with this one.
It looks cruddy.
Just my one.
We just took them in order..
It's getting late, we need to get some sleep.
Oh, yours is nice.
It's elegant looking.
Yea, elegant.
Look at mine.
It's green.
- Nice.
Swap.
I don't want this one.
Swap with me.
Even for a single size it looks small.
Just swap with me.
Okay, let's get some sleep.
Goodnight.
(It's tiny!)
Bedtime
This futon's as hard as a rock.
Very soon the group are all fast asleep.
(We were really tired.
- Yea, really couldn't stay awake.)
Emerging from the shadows, a silhouetted figure draws close to our sleeping group.
Did you eat?
Did you get enough?
Yes, I ate properly..
Are you trying hard?
Have you eaten?
Are you eating properly?
I'm.. I'm not eating anything.
You have to eat properly.
Keep up your strength.
(He was sleeping like a baby.)
I'm off.
'night.
Goodnight.
1:15 a.m.
(6 hours 45 minutes left)
(Notice how someone is hiding
under the table)
An old lady tagger arrives silently.
(She's a nightmare.)
French Kiss
(I wonder if that's okay.)
(You still just went back to sleep.)
She did it again.
(I was exhausted by now.)
Kickboxer
(That was real punishment)
That gave me a fright.
Can they do that? Attack us while sleeping?
It isn't right.
Whatever they do, they can't stop Hamada from sleeping.
Open-palm Strike
(Running didn't even enter my head.)
(They could do as they pleased.)
2 a.m.
(6 hours left)
(There's no way we could have noticed this.)
Volleyball Machine
(He got it in the face about twice.)
There's so many of them.
It gets worse every time.
They're breeding, I know it.
They looked strange.
There are different kinds, like those shiny ones.
2:30 a.m.
(5 hours 30 minutes left)
Hamada notices a suspicious rope
"Rope"
(He looks like a chimp.)
(Exactly like a chimpanzee.)
(A chimp who found a banana.)
Slap
They went to such effort coming down the rope just to slap us.
I knew it was a new species.
They weren't around during the day.
They move fast.
They're nocturnal ones.
Shiny.
They've daytime types and night time types.
Hamada's expression was priceless.
He makes a face like a baby gorilla.
Big round eyes.
Observe: Baby Gorilla Hamada
2:45 a.m.
(5 hours 15 minutes left)
Slap
(They slapped you full force.)
He hit me with his fist.
How are you doing, Tanaka?
It hurts a lot.
Come, gather around these manboobs!
Ribbit, Ribbit.
Matsumoto said
he's going to let you sleep.
Matsumoto's kindness really is deceiving.
Who said it's deceiving?!
He means it this time, you get some sleep.
I wonder if we can actually sleep.
The group are finally allowed to get sleep without fear of attack.
3 a.m.
A moment of peaceful dreaming.
But, it will be morning very soon
and once again their nightmare reality will begin.
5:30 a.m.
(2 hours 30 minutes left)
Wake-up call
(It was impossible to wake up.)
C*ck Machine
(That has to be the worst way to wake up.)
It's morning.
Whacked in the knob first thing in the morning..
Metal Ladle
Come, gather around these manboobs!
Maple Leaf Manju.
It's wake-up time.
Morning
(You guys look a mess.)
Let's greet Matsumoto.
C'mon let's do it.
Morning greetings.
Mr. Matsumoto,
Hamada.
- Yes.
Let's do our greetings.
If you don't do it the others won't.
Here we go.
Mr. Matsumoto,
Everyone,
Hamada is saying it, why don't you?
We'll start again.
Mr. Matsumoto,
good morning.
Here's breakfast
Matsumoto told me
it's no good if you can't try hard
so have some breakfast and get your energy back.
Eat up.
(He didn't have a problem with that.)
Breakfast Time
6 a.m.
(2 hours left)
Gang
If they're going to bring him at least bring him properly.
It's freezing.
6:42 a.m.
(1 hour 18 minutes left)
Kickboxer
He's not getting me!
(At 7 in the morning it can't be nice.)
Three times in a row is tough.
Open-palm Strike
There is an hour left until the end of the game.
No one in the group has anything to say.
Despite the end now being in sight, their spirits remain low.
Volleyball Machine
This is scary.
That has to hurt.
7:33 a.m.
(27 minutes left)
Open-palm Strike
If I wasn't on camera I'd have stabbed him.
7:53 a.m.
(7 minutes left)
It's the final stretch.
Finally.
Don't let your guard down until the end.
The Shows Chef Producer
World acclaimed: Heipo
Did you think you could win?
He must have thought could do it because everyone else did.
The fact he surprised me alone made me annoyed.
7:56 a.m.
(4 minutes left)
I've never looked forward to 8 a.m. this much in my life.
It's about time we were used to that sound.
Come, gather around these manboobs!
1, 2, Come, gather around these manboobs!
In a few minutes your 24 hours will be up.
In just over 3 minutes.
How was it?
Intense.
Endo?
Tanaka?
- Really hard.
Hamada
- Yes?
How was it?
Emotional.
It was all possible because of Matsumoto.
He really is an amazing person.
Let's all count down the last 10 seconds together.
That was so difficult.
It was a horrible punishment game.
Meeting place?
No matter how many times I hear it,
it scares the crap out of me.
We can't be sure where they'll show up anymore.
First cracked ribs, then a rash, next a ripped ear
and now a fever.
That's it, I'm done.
Let's do it.
From 10. Ready?
Origami Fan
(That's revolting.)
(Scary.)
They've gone, Hamada.
How'd we end up here?
I was over there but I ended up here.
Even so, it's over.
How many were there?
Had to have been at least 200 of them.
24 Hour Endurance Tag.
OVER.
Thank you everybody.
So, what next?
Next competition
the four of us versus Matsumoto.
Let's guarantee a victory next time.
That's what you want?
- Yes.
I think we showed what we can do as a team.
We've become close.
I really love you guys.
Well, that's how it is.
Pass it on.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- Good job guys.
Wait, wait.
but we bonded.
- and gotten close..
Hamada's the one who pushed the button..
It's over.
You did it.
That was a tough one.
It was tough, very tough.
Just watching it was exhausting.
Good job so far.
Part 1 of a 5 part punishment.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean "1 of 5"?
I told you before.
What're you on about, 1 of 5.
There's still 2, 3...
- You're a fool!
Enough already.
Next competition it won't be, for instance, two versus three.
We're doing it like this!
Well... that's fine but,
from April, Yamazaki is...
Seriously?
Moving on?
Moving on?!
I'm not moving on.
But then there will be four of us. It'll be easier to pair up for competitions and such.
No way, it'll be four versus one,
but if you really want someone on your side, you can have Heipo.
What a weak punch line, see?
He never fails to fail.
How about fighting Downtown, 3 vs. 2?
Three versus two?
Wouldn't Hamada prefer to be over here with us?
After all we've gone through.
Depends on the situation, really.
Okay, so it'll be Downtown versus Cocorico.
Seems how it's going to be.
You're heavyweights but we'll give it a go.
Thanks for everything until now, Yamazaki.
You're welcome.
Come on, we're just kidding.
You're welling up.
Translated by John Loving.